<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>volecho.com</title>
    <link href="https://volecho.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://volecho.com" />
    <updated>2025-10-21T17:48:53+03:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Volecho.com</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://volecho.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Stray Planets - Hallucinations</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/stray-planets-hallucinations/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/stray-planets-hallucinations/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-21T17:48:53+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/82/volecho-music-magazine-25.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/82/volecho-music-magazine-25.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #5</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/dbju/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-5/paperback/product-w47jn25.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>There is something basically addictive about music that seems to have been stashed away in this universe from some other parallel one. Stray Planets, the Dublin psych, pop cult band of songwriters John Butler, have been operating for years in that place where pop hooks dissolve into daydreamed hallucinations and the distinctions between nostalgia and unreality become deliquescled. With his latest EP Are You Real, Cristobal Leedy? Slipping November 7, Butler is not concerned with creating something tidy or cool, aligned and more devoted to trying to nail the psychic buzz of a world in which even your sense of self is brokered by code. </p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/6PDwiIKWQuF6OWatYcAS93?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br><br>It's not an easy record in the traditional sense but it's richly rewarding in much the same way that a perfectly askew film lingers with you after the credits. This EP is not so much a return or a rebirth as it is an adolescence in a psychedelic terrarium that Butler never let evaporate. He has always had the presence of an underground legend who works to his own tempo, a cousin of Vinyl Williams or a mystical neighbor of Jacco Gardner. It still has that fuzzy aura you'd expect from, like, old Elephant 6 cassettes or similarly distorted '60s pop that sounds like it's been conjured up on some long-lost reel in a thrift store and re-mastered at just barely the right speed. But it all comes together here.<br><br>It is braver, more skewed, more there with never losing the logic of a dream. The EP starts with Your Revolution, a shoegaze-slated reflection full of laces, which is centered around the theme that even if artificial intelligence is as efficient as it is, it can't defeat a human just because it doesn't hurt. It is a concept that reads heavy on paper, but Butler lightens it up and makes it airy in a manner that doesn't make it any less real. If OK Computer had been penned after a session of binge, viewing TikTok deepfakes at 3 am, it would probably go a bit like this.<br><br>The guitars undulate in and out of space, and the vocals glide like a transmission lodged halfway between two frequencies. Lead single Hallucinations is the clear starting point, featuring guest vocals from Gilla Band's Dara Kiely. Kiely's vocal delivery is like he is describing the emotional breakdown of someone witnessing his face distort into something incomprehensible on a glitching AI screen. The tune has that Technicolor craziness of early Flaming Lips or that manic theatrics of The Coral at their more deranged best. It is demented, spinning, and nonsensical in a way that is completely calculated.<br><br>You can literally sense the ground spinning beneath your feet. And then there is the transient interlude Cristobal Leedy, named after a mysterious YouTube commenter who long ago referred to Stray Planets' music as "truly astonishing." Butler doesn't view it as flattery but as a metaphysical bug. He retorts with a question: Are you real? And if they are, then what am I?<br><br>In under a minute, he conveys something that rings true for anyone who has ever bared their soul in art and heard it reverberate back through a comment chain that might or might not have been penned by an actual human being.<br><br>Salvia languishes as a fevered flashback. Born of mid, to, late 2000s Capel Street, it's the missing scene from a movie between Enter The Void and Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind where the hero realizes that they might never wake up. It's both city and ethereal-sounding, the sort of song you can't help but imagine when you think of neon, rainy streets and the odd euphoria of being free from time. The nearer Artificial Love brings the entire enterprise into bittersweet relief. It's four minutes of searing arpeggios and glassy psych, pop that would not sound out of place alongside a song by Tame Impala or Temples, but the emotional center is stranger and heavier. Butler sings as someone who has come to the realisation that love from a machine is preferable to none. The concept is ridiculous, pathetic, and eerily familiar during the time of parasocial relationships, AI companions, and artificial digital personas which are all now included in how humans deal with loneliness. The song isn't cynical, however. It's like a guy dancing with a phantom that he knows doesn't exist but dancing anyway. It is what makes this EP package more interesting than so much contemporary psych, pop that Butler isn't trying to impress anyone. It's like something that he created because he had to. That surrealism tension and sincerity places it in dialogue with other albums that hover just above the borders of mainstream pop storytelling, such as Broadcast's Haha Sound, Pond's The Weather, or even portions of King Gizzard's more pop-heavy discography. There is also a sense of self-consciously playful humor here that is more reminiscent of Terry Gilliam films or the off-kilter cartoon causality of early Adult Swim bumpers.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Karen Salicath Jamal - Mary&#x27;s Blessing</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/karen-salicath-jamal-marys-blessing/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/karen-salicath-jamal-marys-blessing/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-21T17:48:50+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/81/volecho-music-magazine-24.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/81/volecho-music-magazine-24.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #5</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/dbju/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-5/paperback/product-w47jn25.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>Karen Salicath Jamali’s new piano single, Mary’s Blessing, arrives like a gentle dawn, a piece of music that feels as much like a meditation as a performance. The composition was born in a dream, and that dreamlike quality carries through every note. Early one morning, she recorded it on her Steinway piano, translating the delicate rhythms of memory and imagination into sound. There is a subdued quietude here, the feeling of being watched by the presence, a rose petal of light curling inward with every chord. The music is simple but profound, a recalling of the truth that exists in clarity and the heart's honesty. For Jamali, music has always been but an extension of inner transformation. A near-death experience in 2012 altered everything. After a head injury and three-year convalescence, she began writing and playing the piano spontaneously without ever having learned the piano properly. This happy accident uncovered a talent which has produced more than 2,500 pieces and eight complete albums, and taken her on stage at Carnegie Hall eight times. The experience left her with a profound sense of achieving sound as a unitive tissue, a bond between human existence and the rhythms of the cosmos. Mary's Blessing is a concentrated expression of that achievement: a piece that attempts to heal and soothe without uttering a sound. The single was mastered by Maria Triana, a veteran engineer whose career spans decades at Sony Music and includes collaborations with artists from Aretha Franklin and Miles Davis to Camila Cabello and Britney Spears. Triana’s precision ensures that Jamali’s delicate piano lines and subtle dynamic shifts are fully realized, giving the listener a sense of space and resonance. Jamali’s compositions often draw on spiritual and angelic themes, and Mary’s Blessing is no exception. The music emerges from a vision of protection and love, reflecting a sense of presence and guidance, like a quiet force looking over the listener. It recalls the meditative clarity of Ludovico Einaudi or the emotive, minimalist textures of Max Richter, while maintaining a distinct voice rooted in her own journey. There is also an implied filmic quality, a feeling of frozen time as in scenes from A Ghost Story or The Tree of Life, in which the affect lingers as heavily as any story.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/4p7vUm7FVaSl7DSBf1X0QS?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br><br>Her tale is not just outstanding for its artistry, but for the manner in which music was a process of survival and of recovery. The crash that necessitated her becoming a musician also redefined her understanding of consciousness and connection. Jamali often speaks about sound as an all-inclusive language that unites humans with each other, with nature, and with the cosmos. Listening to Mary's Blessing, it's easy to feel that philosophy in the music, each note a gentle reminder of oneness. For those interested in delving into comparable territories in modern piano music, her work would easily find itself alongside contemplative, storytelling musicians like Ólafur Arnalds and Nils Frahm, or even more spiritually focused ventures like Enya's ambient piano-centered pieces. Her music, though, still holds an individuality born out of living, that authenticity derived from the presence of creation—the reality that this music directly stems from dreams, intuition, and self-transformation.<br><br>Jamali is also celebrated for the manner in which her artistic vision cuts across her media. Decades as a visual artist are followed by paintings and sculptures that hang in more than 700 private collections and museum exhibitions such as the Louvre Museum. Her paintings and music tend to run on themes of energy, light, and surrounding human figures, all concepts that she now engages through music. This two-handed practice gives her playing a somatic sense of shape and space, as if every line for the piano was a brush mark on a larger, unseen canvas. Mary's Blessing is not a piano piece—it is a affirmation of contact, survival, and gentleness. It is the assertion that creativity can be an individual lifeline and a gift to others, a conduit for the transmission of light into the lives of other human beings. Jamali’s work continues to garner recognition, including numerous awards for her albums and compositions, yet the quiet, meditative quality of this single reminds us that her music’s power comes from its honesty and emotional resonance.<br><br>With this album, Karen Salicath Jamali confirms her place among today's composers whose music straddles personal biography, spiritual contemplation, and technical skill. Mary's Blessing is an entreaty to go slowly, to listen, and to feel—something of lightness and serenity in a world that doesn't very often.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>NEEB: Taking Flight with Soul, Groove, and Open Skies</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/neeb-taking-flight-with-soul-groove-and-open-skies/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/neeb-taking-flight-with-soul-groove-and-open-skies/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-21T17:48:45+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/80/volecho-music-magazine-23.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/80/volecho-music-magazine-23.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #5</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/dbju/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-5/paperback/product-w47jn25.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>There is a lived, in warmth to NEEB's new album Take To The Sky that is newly inspired, music recalling why the band plays music in the first place. The Hartlepool based outfit have been grinding years getting between shapes, dub, drum &amp; bass, house, jazz, but this album is like arrival. Out in October 2025, it's a late-night synthesis of soul, jazz, and ambient funk that has the calm of experience and the urgency of rejuvenation.<br><br>The album puts everything the band have accumulated in twenty years into a way that sounds simple. You can hear it in the bottom groove of "Brighter Day," the effortless glide of "All Caught Up," the percussive push of "Cave of Hands," and the title song's beautiful rise, off. There's space and groove, rhythm and space. Singer and guitarist Jasmine Weatherill's recruitment is a new kind of chemistry to NEEB, the half-crying, half-determined voice of hers, making the band's complicated arrangements human and real. Recorded in their own, self-built Mobeus Studio, Take To The Sky is more of a conversation between musicians who trust one another absolutely. Mark Hand's synth and Rhodes textures provide richly textured underpinnings for the album, precision and swing being delivered by Mark Lloyd on drums. It is Tony Waite's production that holds it all together with a kind of cinematic clarity that never goes over the top.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/2qnV9PKoIAHyrbhlSH721i?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p> </p>
<p>On certain tracks, the addition of percussionist Martin Ditcham, a Talk Talk and Sade veteran, brings the extra glow, the feel of the rhythm being performed by someone who understands the restraint that is beauty. It's the type of album that ends up that awkward middle ground between the club and the dimly lit living room. It's for the kids who danced when they were young but now get enjoyment out of a good deep groove and a nice glass. There's an echo of The Cinematic Orchestra, a little of the essence of early Zero 7, and even a few moments that have a touch of Groove Armada's Black Light. But NEEB's sound remains distinctive, based on British jazz funk but with a morose, lethargic slow burn that you feel compelled to keep playing straight through without skipping a beat. This isn't a temporary novelty. NEEB have climbed the hard way. They've toured with Zion Train, Pee, Wee Ellis, Gong, The Egg, and Alabama 3, among others, and played from the Glastonbury Avalon Stage all the way to Solfest and Freerotation. They've been described as "the speccy white boys" in Mixmag with a sympathetic wink, and included on compilations such as Sounds of the Funky Underground, a title which now has to be both a reference to their origins and an account of how they've survived. But Take To The Sky is different. It's bold without swagger, refined without sacrificing the grime. Perhaps it's Weatherill who, upon joining, transitioned NEEB from three-piece to a relaxed and more song-oriented collective. Her voice adds intimacy to the band's rhythmic progression. You feel it in the way her lyrics overlap with keys and percussion — little truths swaddled in a melodic blanket. There's a line in "Brighter Day" where she croons like she's smiling through the mic, and you know this is what hope sounds like when you've labored for it instead of assumed it.<br><br>The album sits well among contemporary UK jazz-soul releases from artists such as Yazmin Lacey, Alfa Mist, and Tom Misch, but NEEB's experience working within electronic music sets them ahead. Under the jazzy chord progressions and ominous basslines, there is always some kind of distant hum of the dancefloor — the echo of a kickdrum, the throb of a night still uncompleted. It's the same genetic material that once fueled their breakbeat and techno adventures, only slowed down and reflective.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Kayla Ramos - Hard to say goodbye</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/kayla-ramos-hard-to-say-goodbye/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/kayla-ramos-hard-to-say-goodbye/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-21T17:48:40+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/79/volecho-music-magazine-22.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/79/volecho-music-magazine-22.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #5</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/dbju/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-5/paperback/product-w47jn25.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>Kayla Ramos sings heartbreak and performs it like a climactic event immersed in golden, hour light. Her debut release, "Hard to Say Goodbye," is a cinematic pop ballad which encapsulates the tender moment of holding on versus letting go, where every breath in feels like the edge of something soon to end. With heart-wrenching, emotive vocals and glistening contemporary production by Grammy-nominated producer and composer Dante Lattanzi (Caelum Music Production), the song bursts with raw emotion, telling instantly to those who crave realism over glamour. A welcome addition to sentimental pop playlists, love songs anthologies, and cinematic vocal compilations, but better still, it brings us the artist who will never shy away from feeling it all. Grown up in San Jose and born in California, Ramos was brought up amidst a range of influences—classical recitals, church choirs, musical theater, hip, hop cyphers, jazz improvisational sessions, and early 2000s pop confessionals. She sang even before she could create words into sentences and was already writing songs on piano and guitar at 13, coalescing poetry, philosophy, and lived experience into sounds half-whispered like diary entries. Whether booking tables in neighborhood bars or headlining on stage in theater, Ramos cultivated a voice that could swell with the grandeur of an orchestra one beat and shake with the intimate quiet of a whisper the next.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/7gSx91t1cVproJEk4e1YaW?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p> </p>
<p>Her voice now resides in a space where vulnerability is resistance and nostalgia is an act of brash storytelling. Imagine the emotional honesty of Lana Del Rey, the self-searching fervor of Fiona Apple, the lyrical songcraft of Taylor Swift, and the vocal exactness of Ariana Grande, but Kayla is never imitative. Her voice is soft but determined, delicate but not fragile, a glass heart clutched hard in shaking hands. Collaborating with Dante Lattanzi, Ramos has hit the next art heights. "Hard to Say Goodbye" is a page turn, green, unsettling, affectively generous. It's not a debut that screams to be heard; it waits patiently, looping like an unreturned voicemail or the final sentence of a letter you were never supposed to write.Guiding Hard to Say Goodbye, you find yourself wondering if she writes cinematically,  chords ring placed instead of located, as if she is building affective shots. The production never tries too hard. Instead, it gives her voice room to feel human, slightly vulnerable at the edges. Lattanzi’s touch adds modern weight without drowning her sincerity. Fans of artists like Gracie Abrams or early Billie Eilish might recognize the intimacy, while lovers of Ariana Grande’s vocal control will clock Kayla’s quiet strength. But even with those touchpoints, she doesn’t echo anyone too closely. Her gentleness does not apologize. Her holdback is deliberate.<br><br></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>JLP: Strength in the Shout</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/jlp-strength-in-the-shout/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/jlp-strength-in-the-shout/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-21T17:48:34+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/78/volecho-music-magazine-21.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/78/volecho-music-magazine-21.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #5</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/dbju/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-5/paperback/product-w47jn25.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>You can feel it from the initial burst of the drums, the first forceful snip of the guitar, the first gasp before the words come. Monster, their latest single, doesn't waste time, plunging headlong into the battered center of survival. It's raw, taut, and possesses a kind of emotional connection that only derives from having lived through it. Monster is about breaking out of an abusive relationship, getting a balance between vulnerability and hard-won power. The lyrics are like listening to someone whisper their way through the dark, fragile but unflinching. And then there's the chorus, desperate, explosive, yet somehow liberating. You can hear the release in Jelena Petener's voice as it fluctuates from shaking to soaring, a performance that is both exhausted and defiant. Everything dissolves in a fiery controlled blaze by the time the bridge comes around, leaving only the soft whisper of relief. There is something unashamed and retro about Monster that calls to mind how classic rock once shared personal tales with no shame. It blends the emotional openness of Alanis Morissette's Jagged Little Pill with the intensity of early Paramore. But JLP's not retro, it's their own language. Funk section makes the rhythm dirty, guitars produce that low, rich, full bodied sound you've got associated with arena floors, and Jelena's singing cuts through the mix like reality cutting through noise. You get the impression this is not a radio-friendly song; it's one fashioned for liberty.</p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/0JpNFDj99Dy1AjIL4FNGvK?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p>JLP formed the way all great bands do — by accident. Luka and Jelena Petener, musical complements and brother and sister in the very best sense, started in an acoustic duo with living room jam sessions. Luka, guitar-strumming fan of ACDC, Guns N' Roses, and Slash, contributed riffs and attitude. Jelena, piano-trained and choir voice, provided melody and dramatic depth. Somewhere in the process on a hot summer evening in Croatia, a jam session took on another form. That spark blossomed into a full band, and before long, they were packing Vienna's clubs, from Szene Wien to the huge Nova Rock Festival, with music that is tidy-sounding but still alive. Strong and Loud We Shout It Out, their motto, is not a T-shirt slogan to be placed upon anyone's chest. It is a credo. Each song has that same rhythm, a blend of grime, happiness, and faith in the reality that music is supposed to move the body and the conscience. JLP's tunes address the world around them: peer pressure, inner conflict, the era we are in. But they never lose their capability for enjoying themselves. You can tell, even when they are worst, that they still have fun. Monster is in the same league. It's a track for anybody who's ever been stuck, anybody who's screamed their way back into themselves.</p>
<p>There's build and release like in a movie, imagine the tension of Black Swan or the emotional fire of The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo. It's music that doesn't cower from darkness but won't be afraid of finding a beat of light there. If you wish to follow JLP's family tree, you might place them alongside acts such as Halestorm, Florence + The Machine, or Nothing But Thieves, bands and artists who live for dynamics, who understand how to turn hurt into something that is commensurate with a triumph. But JLP still sound quintessentially local, based on Vienna's precision-meets-passion hybrid. Their live shows make that even clearer: they work towards perfection, certainly, but never give up the spontaneity that brings rock music to life. It's not perfection; it's authenticity.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Aly Berry Released A Matter So Small</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/aly-berry-released-a-matter-so-small/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/aly-berry-released-a-matter-so-small/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-21T17:48:29+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/77/volecho-music-magazine-20.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/77/volecho-music-magazine-20.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #5</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/dbju/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-5/paperback/product-w47jn25.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p class="align-center">London's jazz evenings have a knack for unearthing voices that are simultaneously timeless and fresh. In the soft darkness of a Mayfair club, one such voice started turning heads — smoky, smooth, and coolly self-assured. That is Aly Berry, a British singer-songwriter with a jazz-influenced sound whose presence is like a tip of the head towards old-school glamour in contemporary contexts. Her new single, A Matter So Small, is the third from her imminent debut album, and it's a comfortable introduction to her world: equal measures of romance and introspection, all wrapped in late-night velvet.</p>
<p class="align-center"><br><br><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/5cKQvzBmGmmwUoUp0ZQYI7?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center">From the North of England originally, Aly made the leap that would be her tale. At eighteen, she departed home to London — youthful, driven, and set to make her mark upon two dynamic worlds: music and modeling. She had previously been modeling since a teenager, but the city's creative vibrancy welcomed her on a deeper level. London's jazz scene, with all its grime and glory, was her school room and playground.<br><br>It was where she had her initial encounter with Paul Higgs, an old-time jazz composer and trumpet player with a moviemaking sensibility and intimate familiarity with timeless form. What began as an informal working relationship became a mutually understood language artistically. With him, she started composing and performing, blending her sultry vocals with his rich arrangements. The collaboration became a legitimate recording business — a debut album that sounds like a dialogue between eras, fusing mid-century sophistication from jazz with the integrity of contemporary singer-songwriters. And the titles of the players indicate just how much respect this album commands. Scott Hamilton, if not one of the finest working saxophonists in contemporary jazz today; Dave Green, a bass player with a resume running across decades; Neil Bullock on drums, rhythm genius; and Paul Higgs himself, setting the direction aurally. This isn't an oldies band. This is a collection of players who know feel, and how to tell imitation from magic.<br><br><br>It's subtle, the sort of song where room and silence help to tell part of the story. Aly's voice never insists on being heard above the mix; she yields, she invites, she offers things to think about. There's subtle confidence in her phrasing, you can tell she has listened to the masters, but she's not attempting to copy. Where Norah Jones had served coffeehouse introspection and Amy Winehouse brought back smoky defiance, Aly Berry seems the singer who could walk the middle ground between them, marrying intimacy and sheen in her own way. Where jazz is typically stuck in amber or subjected to fusion experimentation, Aly's is the refreshing common-sense approach. She is not trendy. Her voice takes on the heavy grain of an analog record in a dark room, but with a burst of lucidity that's unmistakably modern. Picture the mournful elegance of Chet Baker Sings remade in the soundtrack-sounding timbres of Vesper by Massive Attack, tempered but deeply affecting. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top 5 Releases 10-21-25</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/top-5-releases-10-21-25/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/top-5-releases-10-21-25/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-21T12:30:03+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/76/Top-Tracks-2xl.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following features are now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/76/Top-Tracks-2xl.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following features are now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #5</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/dbju/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-5/paperback/product-w47jn25.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Leo XIV: Dancing Through the Wreckage</strong><br><br>Chicago's Leo XIV is not only dropping records, he's slowly luring himself out of the wreckage in front of our very eyes and making us hear the engine roaring back to life. His newest single Feel, the successor to his initial Midas, is the instant an artist comes to terms after years in hibernation. It starts as a 2 a.m. revelation at night and develops into something that sounds like the kind of track you'd hear when you're alone at the small hours when your mind is racing too energetically. Constructed around an unstoppable acid bass line which pulsates like an unstoppable heartbeat that you can't switch off, the track moves with a loose but determined pace, combining hypnotic grooves with vocals that are otherworldly yet optimistic. There's a low-key intensity at play here, the kind of tension you find in early The Weeknd singles or James Blake's most emotionally vulnerable moments.<br><br>Leo XIV, the work of Dylan Leo Azadi, is a declaration of vulnerability unvarnished. There is no legend-building at work here, merely one individual piecing himself together from depression, addiction and anxiety with melody as sustenance. He is not attempting to sound like he's been attuned to the cosmos, he is attempting to remain upright. Feel syncs with instinct, it begins in the dark and travels towards something more like light. Attempt to see it as nesting between Frank Ocean's Blonde in its introspection and FKA twigs' pulse-drunk shadowdance. This is music for the ones who've put themselves on pause and are now restoring play even if their hands still tremble. With sophomore release Cold Open due in 2026, Leo XIV is less interested in show and more interested in emotional accuracy. Feel isn't a song, it's the sound of a person reminding themselves that they're still there.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/4UhlD1GnhQmV8H5KbA3JHb?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<hr>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Shervin Boloorian: A Voice Built for Quiet Revolutions</strong><br><br>My Free Heart, the new single from Iranian-born Bali-based musician and sound healer Shervin Boloorian, is the sort of song that doesn't compete for your attention, it settles in. His voice is positioned with a lived-in peace, as if defined by rest as much as action. He's not reaching for high drama or singles-list peak, but something more complex: peace that stays after the music ends. The English rendition carries a soft call, but the Persian rendition carries another level of emotional depth in putting the song in heritage and remembrance.<br><br>Boloorian's work has always broken the space between performance and healing space. His latest album I Hear You, Mother Earth won Global Peace Song Awards, and his Rumi-inspired album was blessed by Coleman Barks, a rare blessing from one who has experienced the power of words. But My Free Heart isn't religious drama. It's contemplative power in song, and it sounds less like a sweeping sermon and more like something you'd hear late in a movie from someone who sits alone in contemplation. If you enjoy the sensitivity of artists like José González or the calming rhythm of Trevor Hall, this song has the same feel.<br><br>Boloorian emerges from a location that does not seek the limelight but union. His international presence, from Balinese yoga rooms to off-the-radar performances overseas, has produced a sound that is never in haste. My Free Heart is a call to action to recall that tranquility can be paradoxical, particularly on a world that hardly pauses.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/5KLX9LpyDgSphK7v0tM2uJ?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<hr>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Deflecting Ghosts: Grit, Fury and the Will to Stand Up</strong><br><br>Risen by Kansas-based Deflecting Ghosts features a fist-in-a-clenched-fist vibe around melody. It is a song that is constructed on urgency, a swift punch at complacency with lyrics that question the world's current deterioration and not some obliquely suggestive of same. You can sense the strains of alternative metal and rock running through the track, the unvarnished intensity of Breaking Benjamin's early days, the purging grit of Nothing More, and an attitude for endurance drawn from decades of tough-won strife.<br><br>The band didn't begin inside a high-sheen studio with an entourage of executives dictating their sound. It began as Luke Fitzgerald's fiefdom, his own thing, when his old band broke up, and grew into full-blown force when Rhema became the bass player and Austin joined as drummer. That these are songs penned in the home studio gives them insurgent credibility, this is rebellion chronicled through actual walls and small rooms, not factory-raised angst.<br><br>Recorded and processed with varying degrees of success by New Years Day's Jeremy Valentyne and Brandon Wolfe, Risen becomes a compromise of heaviness and clarity, delivering each emotional blow with accuracy. Rhema's basslines reverberate with spirals of pain reserve and determination, and Austin's drumming is savage, as if hammered out to rid something from inside, rather than to awe. If rock in its best should be akin to mutual survival, this group rides hard for that conviction.<br><br>For the fans who were missing when rock music was still human and got beat up, imagine Chevelle introspection with the ferocity of pre-millen Thrice, Risen reminds that heavy can be kind.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/20jqFuoWxYySohcEP1kmOD?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<hr>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Stray Planets: Pop Fractals and Psychedelic Echoes</strong><br><br>Are You Real, Cristobal Leedy? is not just an EP, it's experiencing a miniature cinema in someone's brain where every track warps the fabric of time. Dubliner John Butler, trading as Stray Planets, writes like he's splicing scenes of 60s psychedelia, shoegaze-washed dream sequences and latenight indie film together. The result is a five-track experience that feels both warped and strangely familiar, like an old record you’re sure you’ve heard before but can’t place.<br><br>Working once again with producer Rían Trench, Butler elevates his cult reputation with something deeply imaginative. Your Revolution opens with an era-bending shoegaze wash that questions whether machines will ever feel rebellion the way humans do. Hallucinations, with the lead vocals of Gilla Band's Dara Kiely, is like an AI breakdown viewed on a malfunctioning TV screen. Interlude Cristobal Leedy drifts on self-doubt, recalling that weird YouTube-comment experience where the person has a compliment for your work and you're left wondering if they even exist. Salvia twists through a Capel Street 3 a.m. fever dream. And Artificial Love ends in bittersweet glamour, questioning if synthetic affection is at times easier than actual connection.<br><br>Vinyl Williams, Jacco Gardner or the spaced-out goofiness of early Ariel Pink supporters will be equally entranced. Butler isn't guru or hero figure, just a guy in pursuit of sound that is half-forgotten, half-dreamed. This EP would be scored just as stunningly for an A24 film or some quirky special effects sci-fi love tale where love is a little too robotic and a little too material all at once.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/6PDwiIKWQuF6OWatYcAS93?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<hr>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Rose Ringed: Euphoria Written in Mourning</strong><br><br>Mylène, the first album by Amsterdam producer, drummer and jazz pianist Rose Ringed, is one of those albums defined by loss but filled with motion. A tribute to his mother, a jazz ballerina who died when he was 11, the album is both despair and illumination — grief turned into rhythm instead of stagnation. Where others would keep quiet in sorrow, Rose channelled catharsis through ecstatic electronic melody, building tracks that blaze and pulse with the resolve of one dancing through pain, not staying in it.<br><br>Rose Ringed's music is an emotional intensity mixed with dance-biability drawn from the freedom of trance and the block-by-block narrative of producers such as Bicep and Paul Kalkbrenner. It is not dance music per se, it is memory in arpeggio and chord progression listenable like latenight therapy sessions. You can sense the imprint of early reference points such as Enya and Hans Zimmer under the beat, which lends even the more forceful parts some gravity.<br><br>His path from drummer to jazz pianist to producer lends the music form and improvisational spirit. The fact that his ascension has reached as high as events such as Tomorrowland, Loveland and ADE only goes to show how this emotional authenticity speaks far and wide. Mylène is a man who senses he is finally hitting at the heart of what drives him, not ambition, but heritage.<br><br>Rose doesn't attempt to do tragedy. He's turning it into gasoline. It's the sort of record you play past midnight, when memory aches but the rhythm sweeps you along.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/1KML3dPprByep3tRnYSJDj?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Noah Zayden Lights Up the Night with “No Sale La Luna”</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/noah-zayden-lights-up-the-night-with-no-sale-la-luna/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/noah-zayden-lights-up-the-night-with-no-sale-la-luna/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-20T00:58:25+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/75/volecho-music-magazine-19.jpg" alt="" />
                    With his latest release No Sale La Luna, Noah Zayden steps back&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/75/volecho-music-magazine-19.jpg" alt="" />
                <p data-start="255" data-end="734">With his latest release <em data-start="279" data-end="296">No Sale La Luna</em>, Noah Zayden steps back into the spotlight like someone who knows exactly where he’s headed. Fresh off the heat of his previous single <em data-start="432" data-end="439">Fuego</em>, the rising artist returns to NxtNow Music with a track that feels like a midnight confession soaked in rhythm, romance, and restless energy. If <em data-start="585" data-end="592">Fuego</em> was the spark that caught attention, <em data-start="630" data-end="647">No Sale La Luna</em> is the reminder that Noah didn’t just get lucky — he’s building momentum with purpose.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="255" data-end="734"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/4Dn1cgzfY6sJFXiaWpgbf6?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p data-start="255" data-end="734">The track lives in that sweet spot where Latin urban grooves collide with modern pop sensation. The beat pulses like city lights flickering in the distance, steady and hypnotic, while Noah’s vocals float between smooth seduction and emotional urgency. There’s this vibe of chasing something just out of reach, desire, clarity, maybe even redemption, and the moon refusing to rise becomes the poetic backdrop for that tension.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>HELLRAZOR: Frostbitten Riffs and Riot-Ready Metal Rising from the North</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/hellrazor-frostbitten-riffs-and-riot-ready-metal-rising-from-the-north/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/hellrazor-frostbitten-riffs-and-riot-ready-metal-rising-from-the-north/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-20T00:53:42+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/74/volecho-music-magazine-18.jpg" alt="" />
                    Raised on riffs in the North, born of the North, HELLRAZOR are&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/74/volecho-music-magazine-18.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Raised on riffs in the North, born of the North, HELLRAZOR are a metal/hard rock giant who play as if they're attempting to resurrect the dead and have them headbang. Their sound crashes like a wrecking crew: guitars swinging frantically between chainsaw savagery and earworm hookiness, drums thundering maniacally over blackened skies, bass thudding like bones being rumbled beneath your feet, and vocals that kick their way right into the chest.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vf43zldvxmE" title="hellrazor - Sands Of Time" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p><br><br>This is not gnat noise. This is honed pandemonium with hooks that cling long after the amps have been killed. HELLRAZOR takes an inspiration from the height of metal's hard-core roots, i.e., the raw power and boorish energy of early Priest or Metallica — but carries it forward to the modern era with the fire and attitude of modern rock and metalcore. You have fist-raising anthems designed for smoke-filled clubs, tattooed fists raised aloft, screams intended to be yelled by strangers who become gang members for a moment.<br><br>Their sound alternates between storm-bringer fury and unadulterated, over-the-top, cinematically-informed melodrama, in effect, a soundtrack to a motorbike gang arriving at the end of the world with lightning-filled skies and no plans on losing their momentum. There's intensity to the performance, but no slouching; the band is well aware of when to tighten the bolt and when to let the fury unleash.<br><br>That campy bite? That's vibe, that's not camp. Consider Ghost's horror-fixture showmanship meeting Avenged Sevenfold's punch-in-the-face brutality of early days. Riffs cut like a knife, choruses blaze like fire. No ballads. No filler. Just intent on steroids.<br><br>HELLRAZOR sounds like the live performance, sweat, strobes, boots thudding over monitors, and a front row full of screamin' fans yellin' out every lyric like they're livin' it. An unworried attitude is spreading throughout, the same one that evokes the hell-bent rebellion of classic metal without going so far as to retro.<br><br>This band is not faking it dressed up in costume as metal. They are metal,living it, bleeding it, and laying it down with enough power to incinerate a frozen town during a blackout. Plug the sound. Turn it up to eleven. If your heart fails to start pounding by the time the chorus kicks in, take your pulse — you may already be in the graveyard.<br><br>But fear not. HELLRAZOR seems to taunt that they are going to give you one last ride.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Mike Shouse&#x27;s Triumphant Return: &quot;Jaded&quot; Revives the Spirit of Instrumental Rock</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/mike-shouses-triumphant-return-jaded-revives-the-spirit-of-instrumental-rock/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/mike-shouses-triumphant-return-jaded-revives-the-spirit-of-instrumental-rock/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:15:36+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/73/volecho-music-magazine-17.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/73/volecho-music-magazine-17.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>A decade and a half is a long time to have been out of sight in the realm of guitar. But when Kentucky bred shredder Mike Shouse finally emerged from hiding, he didn't reappear, he exploded. His new release, Jaded, released through Deko Entertainment, is a sonic boom re-entry that balances on the precipice between technical skill and emotional resonance. It's a living record, grounded in technique but entirely free, and inhabited by some of the most respected figures in guitar lore: Tony MacAlpine, Ron "Bumblefoot" Thal, and Michael Angelo Batio.<br><br>Kentucky native, subsequently schooled at Hollywood's Guitar Institute of Technology, Shouse has been among the most innovative and skilled guitarists of his peer group for years. His previous albums, Enter the Soul (2001) and Alone on the Sun (2010), had also been praised for their unflinching combination of melody and precision, absolute proof that virtuosity and storytelling could go hand in hand. Jaded carries on that tradition, a purely instrumental album that is cinematic and intimate at the same time.<br><br>"This album is a rebirth for me in many ways," Shouse says. There is a feeling of rebirth all the way through all the songs. You catch it in the mournful sting of Romeo Is Gone, the sweaty thrill of Let's Go, and the jaunty swagger of Smiley Faced Emoji. Even the final offering from the album, Upon Looking Back, carries the repressed assurance of an artist who has worked the highs and lows of artistic life and yet still blazes to perform.<br><br>Each visiting guitarist brings his own timbre to Shouse's compositions. Tony MacAlpine's smooth, classically aligned phrasing adds a sense of sophistication. Bumblefoot's erratically shifting tone, bristling with sharp edges and elasticity, sometimes hinting at the brink of mania, keeps the listener on edge. And Batio, the speed master of all time, brings blunt fire to the party, blasting the album's energy into orbit. But be warned: Jaded is Shouse's band from start to finish. The record sounds unified because his performance is the constant, melodic whenever it has to be, explosive whenever it needs to be, and expressive at all times.<br><br>The production, skillfully nurtured by Nashville's Billy Decker, provides the album with its glossy yet organic-sounding production. Drummer Charlie Zeleny (and collaborator with Jordan Rudess and Terry Bozzio) and Impellitteri bassist James Amelio Pulli complete the team, delivering the guitar fireworks with rhythmic weight. The result is an album that walks a fine line between technical proficiency and emotional expression, something that few instrumental albums achieve.<br><br>Hearing Jaded is somewhat akin to opening a time capsule from the height of the guitar hero days, the Surfing with the Alien and Passion and Warfare period, but it's not retro. Rather, it's respectful of that era's heritage and sounds totally of the moment. There's an undertone of sincerity that prevents it from becoming pastiche. Unlike some instrumental rock albums, which sound like showcases for technique, Shouse's playing is narrative, about loss and renewal and thanks.<br><br>Critics elsewhere in the world have already noticed. Iggy Magazine of France has labelled the album "a fresco sound that is both technical and visceral." Music Review World has proclaimed it "a technical wonder and an emotional journey." And Revista Sound Loop of Argentina has stated, "Shouse triumphantly returns with an album that pushes the boundaries of the instrumental and sets a new benchmark for the genre." Such aren't empty encomiums. They’re recognition of an artist who has matured without losing his spark.<br><br>For those who live for the thrill of hearing a guitar really talk, Jaded is the reminder of what six strings can do in capable hands. Joe Satriani, Steve Vai, and Paul Gilbert enthusiasts will be home in a nanosecond, but Shouse's melodic, expressive playing carves out his own niche. The tune Bucket of Bolts (see it here<br>) is the perfect beginning point: all muscular and lighthearted, with a rhythm section enjoying themselves almost as much as the guitarist himself.<br><br>Jaded is not a comeback. It's a statement, that real musicianship does not die, that guitar instrumental rock can still thrill, and that sometimes laying it down is the way to come back more powerful. Shouse has forever been a master craftsman, but this record proves he's a writer, employing tone and phrasing to say what words cannot.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>F</strong><strong>ollow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
