<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>volecho.com</title>
    <link href="https://volecho.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://volecho.com" />
    <updated>2025-10-06T10:17:20+03:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Volecho.com</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://volecho.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Sean MacLeod Returns with “Cool Charisma”; A Shimmering Slice of Indie Pop Brilliance</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/sean-macleod-returns-with-cool-charisma-a-shimmering-slice-of-indie-pop-brilliance/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/sean-macleod-returns-with-cool-charisma-a-shimmering-slice-of-indie-pop-brilliance/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-06T10:17:20+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/60/volecho-music-magazine-4.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/60/volecho-music-magazine-4.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p><br><br>If you’ve been anywhere near Dublin’s indie scene over the past few decades, the name Sean MacLeod will ring a few nostalgic bells. A founding member of the much-loved Cisco, MacLeod helped shape a distinctly Irish flavor of jangly, melodic pop that blended the sincerity of folk with the confidence of classic rock. And now, with his latest single Cool Charisma out in October 2025, he shows his skill at writing classic pop hooks hasn't faded whatsoever.<br><br>Cool Charisma perches on a sheeny wave of glistening guitar hooks and hookiness that lodges in the brain, the type of tune that should be background to some late-summer montage — windows rolled down, city lights whizzing past, and a tune that wouldn't quit your head. Sheeny indie pop with substance, constructed from a bouncy call-and-response hook that's a serotonin fix for anybody who loves melody-apologetic songwriting.<br><br>There's something inherently timeless to MacLeod's music, but not retro or nostalgic. His music touches the core of the legends — The Beatles, The Beach Boys, and Motown — but interprets them with a contemporary sensibility that's intelligent rather than derivative. He swaddles warmth and wit in his words, layering hope with questions regarding meaning and identity. The melodies bring you in; the lyrics keep you there.<br><br>MacLeod's background informs his work. As a hub figure for Cisco, he cut with U2's former producer Paul Barrett and saw the band achieve local success and international acclaim with their album No. 1. Although Cisco eventually went under, MacLeod continued on his own, cutting multiple solo albums and developing his sound into something highly personal. With each release, his next moved further into revealing yet another aspect of his musical expertise — half classicist, half experimenter, half philosopher.<br><br>If you listen to Cool Charisma, you can sense the layers peeling away in the moment. Under its glossy exterior lies something reflective, nearly otherworldly, as if MacLeod is posing questions about what charm is, precisely, in an age of image and diversion. The groove is catchy, but there's always something more simmering beneath the surface — a rhythm that has become the signature of his songcraft.<br><br>It's easy to envision Cool Charisma cozied up in the same batch as acts like Crowded House, The Shins, or Belle and Sebastian — music that loves melody and message together. There's something in there too that's reminiscent of retro movie energy, something that would slide readily into a coming-of-age film or a bittersweet romantic comedy. Imagine High Fidelity but in contemporary Dublin, or the golden-painted optimism of Almost Famous reproduced under Irish skies.<br><br>And there is more to come. MacLeod will be putting out New Start in Spring 2025 — an innovative era-mapping album — and the experimental piece We Don't See What That We Don't See, which demonstrates his continued curiosity and reluctance to stay in one groove of genre. That ability to challenge himself, to balance pop urgency with more considered deliberation, is part of the reason that his work is so compelling.<br><br>Sean MacLeod doesn't sound in this case like a man in pursuit of trends, or of clocks. He sounds like a man contented in the work of creation itself — still inquisitive, still on the prowl for that magic chorus, still penning songs that sound like they're good for your bones. Cool Charisma is not another album single; it's evidence that pop, when crafted correctly, can still be magic.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Rusty Reid Uncovers a Forgotten Rock Treasure with The Unreasonables</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/rusty-reid-uncovers-a-forgotten-rock-treasure-with-the-unreasonables/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/rusty-reid-uncovers-a-forgotten-rock-treasure-with-the-unreasonables/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-06T10:15:43+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/59/volecho-music-magazine-3.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/59/volecho-music-magazine-3.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #3</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/gtyt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1994035" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p><br><br>Occasionally, music history presents us with the tale of opening a time capsule. Rusty Reid's The Unreasonables is just such a treasure — a forgotten double album of sharp hooks, insurgent melodies, and unapologetic rock attitude, made decades past and only now given its life. It is no retro project; it is a rebirth. Four decades or so on from when it was first adhered to and put on the back burner, the album is an epiphany and a miracle, a reminder of what could have been and what still very much is.<br><br>Reid, an American singer-songwriter from Texas living in the Pacific Northwest today, is a seasoned artiste for his introspective indie-folk and country-rock discography. But The Unreasonables shatters that vision. This is not a thinking or philosophical record. It's an elemental, sweat-drenched explosion of rock and roll — lusty, raw, alive. No sweeping manifestos, no incendiary epics. Simply a band tearing along at full cry, sawing out riffs and melodies with the kind of freedom you get when you don't think anyone's paying attention.<br><br>It starts with Attitude Change, a catchy, sassy pop-rock jangle that gets the tone just right — hooky, confident, and frayed at the edges. It's the sort of track that would've fit neatly between Tom Petty and The Pretenders on FM radio in the early '80s, the sort you crank up loud in the car with the windows down. Piece of the Action comes with swing and swagger, sultry rhythm and sneer grin. Shock Me turns it up, a thudding come-on tune that's like a neon light turning on, and Let's Just Talk chills the temperature just enough to show the doubt behind the bluff.<br><br>It's easy to imagine The Unreasonables having held their own during their era — much the same as groups like The Cars, Dire Straits, and The Romantics all did the best they could to straddle radio-friendly hooks with subtlety strangeness. And yet, hearing it today, there's still something contemporary to it too. The snappiness of the melodies, the rough-around-the-edges sincerity, the lack of overproduction — it's precisely what modern rock could use more of.<br><br>There is also something oddly cinematic about this re-discovery. The tale of a lost group, an unreleased album that did not get heard, and a musician who carried that specter in silence all these years — it's like a sub-plot from Almost Famous or a strand out of Richard Linklater's Everybody Wants Some!!. You can almost envision a stack of reels unopened in a garage, the tape slightly gritty but otherwise unmolested, waiting for someone to press play once more.<br><br>Rusty Reid has never written with intent, usually putting politics or philosophy in his work, but The Unreasonables takes all that away. It is the sound of passion — passion over dogma, beat over brain. What is remarkable is how up-to-date it still is. Melodies have not aged at all. Guitars are crunchy and thumping. Vocals come alive with sarcasm and humor.<br><br>Reid's decision to finally put out The Unreasonables is both nostalgic and defiant. In an era of music culture beset by algorithmic sheen and streaming numbers, here's an album from a previous age of purpose — where a group could plug in, play from the heart, and let the tape run. It's sloppy, human, and full of personality.<br><br>For readers of old-style rock storytelling, The Unreasonables lie between the peppery bite of The Kinks and blue-collar heartland romance of Bruce Springsteen's early albums. It has that same stubbornness and humanity — songs by people who weren't attempting to be famous, but real.<br><br>Hearing it today is like discovering a letter written some time in the past but with the ability to speak to the present. It's not revival. It's confirmation that great music never truly dies — it merely awaits the moment when it will be re-rediscovered.<br><br>And here is finally, then: The Unreasonables. Rusty Reid and his long-forgotten band didn't disappear — they were patiently waiting for the world to catch up.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Shrubs Ride a Retro Wave with Infectious New Single &quot;Fall Behind&quot;</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/the-shrubs-ride-a-retro-wave-with-infectious-new-single-fall-behind/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/the-shrubs-ride-a-retro-wave-with-infectious-new-single-fall-behind/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-06T10:12:55+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/58/volecho-music-magazine-2.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/58/volecho-music-magazine-2.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p><br>Houston's indie and psych rock scene has always been fertile soil for groups unwilling to compromise experimentation with looking over their shoulders, and The Shrubs are revealing their hand as one of the city's most forward-thinking voices. Since its inception by chief songwriter, guitarist, and producer Miguel, the band has carved out a niche that places introspection beside play, DIY ethics beside pop gloss. Its latest single, Fall Behind, out September 19, 2025, demonstrates that the band can evolve while remaining uncompromisingly themselves.<br><br>Recorded in the Flowers on the Wall, Fall Behind is an intentional shift from the melancholy atmosphere of The Shrubs' earlier music to a brighter, more energetic and eclecticism. The song takes cue from surf rock textures, recalling the sizzling-summer-guitar strums of The Bambi Molesters and The Ventures. But it never does feel like an imitation. Instead of avoiding the past, though, Miguel's precise songwriting and production mix nostalgia with modern sensibilities to create a retro and still newly current sound. Analogue recording technology yields warmth and texture, giving the single a retro tone that coexists with its brash guitar riffs and bright rhythmic momentum.<br><br>The group's do-it-yourself aesthetic is also at the core of what they're all about. Although they occasionally supplement their sound by adding a string quartet, The Shrubs prefer to produce everything in-house, writing, recording, and producing it themselves. This gives their music raw intimacy and detail, a deliberate control of tone and atmosphere that bigger studios dissipate. On Fall Behind, everything is measured and life-sounding—the guitars tend to sparkle, the rhythm section moves forward with energy, and Sophie Mallory's vocals float smoothly on top, adding a touch of humanity to surf-inspired hooklines.<br><br>Lyrically, Fall Behind is reflective and optimistic in equal proportion, offering themes of introspection, development, and tension between then and now. Six years of songwriting chops since 2019, when the track was composed, have yielded a sharp skillset in pairing narrative complexity with earworm hooks on Miguel's behalf. The energy of the track is contagious, so it's equally adept to quiet home listening as hangout dancing or cruises along sunny interstate highways.<br><br>The Shrubs' path is just one part of the larger resurgence of analog-sounding indie bands that incorporate vintage sounds with new attitudes, much like current psych-pop artists like Mild High Club or Temples. For those into surf rock revivalists like La Luz or early Tame Impala, The Shrubs will feel like home in terms of texture, but they add their own Texas flair—a earthy warmth and sense of humor that make the music fun and accessible. Their earlier output, seen as widely observed in placements such as the One Wheel electric skateboard commercial, had already shown itself capable of striking a chord beyond niche usage, and Fall Behind does it again while extending further into an experimental audio strategy.<br><br>The live band configuration, led by Miguel and his brother Josh on drums, with Sophie Mallory on vocals, has been made strong by testing and adaptation. The chemistry among the trio is working, and it allows for a fluidity that leaves room for both considered production choices and abrupt jolts of creativity. On Fall Behind, it's clear that The Shrubs are not content to ride previous success-they want to push themselves, refine their craft, and explore fresh musical ground while being respectful of the textures and tones that have defined them.<br><br>For indie rock fans with substance and soul, Fall Behind is a rich, immersive listen. Combine it with albums like La Luz's Weirdo Shrine, Mild High Club's Timeline, or even the guitar-driven cuts on Tame Impala's Innerspeaker for a playlist that walks the line between retro warmth and contemporary psych energy. Visually and culturally, it recalls the sun-bleached color of films like Rushmore or The Endless Summer, where mood, melody, and the curiosity of youth intersect seamlessly.<br><br>Fall Behind is more than a single song; it's an encapsulation of a band assured in its identity, but eager to explore. As The Shrubs mature and mature, their audience can look forward to songs that are laughingly introspective, modern and eternal, capturing the spirit of indie rock while pushing its unlimited potential. This new offering is an invigorating testament to the band's transformation and a tantalizing glimpse at what's to come from Houston's intriguing psych rock trio.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>STYLEX Brings Dance Floors to Life with His Unique Tech House Energy</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/stylex-brings-dance-floors-to-life-with-his-unique-tech-house-energy/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/stylex-brings-dance-floors-to-life-with-his-unique-tech-house-energy/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-06T10:11:32+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/57/volecho-music-magazine-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/57/volecho-music-magazine-1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>With so much talent on the scene, it has not taken long before STYLEX emerged on the radar as one of the artists to watch in house and tech house. Merging inspiration from genre icons such as Carl Cox with the sleek, contemporary production of Martin Ikin, he brings the fire with his lively live shows, catchy basslines, and thrusting beats. Combine inspiration from influencers such as James Hurr, Mark Knight, and Jewel Kid, and what you have is a sound both familiar and uncompromisingly energetic, a signature sound that is certain to take hold from the initial beat.<br><br>STYLEX's studio work illustrates acute sensitivity to rhythm and melody, and the capacity to create tracks ready to feature on the club floor yet emotionally engaging. Early singles such as Got This and Bandolera on Mustache Crew Records stamped him as a producer who could weave catchy hooks with driving energy, and Corrupt on AK Cartel further deepened his repertoire. His vocal-driven single Falling Deep on G Mafia Records uncovered a less typical side, injecting emotional richness otherwise delivered only by punchy, percussive beats.<br><br>His new release, Feel The Heat on Krafted Digital, is an optimal-impact tech house peak-hour floor-filler. Every synth stab, every percussive strike, and every cyclical bassline is programmed with one intention only to get a crowd moving, so standing still is out of the question. There is a cinematic aspect to the production, too, evoking memories of Hakkasan frequent flyers' high-octane performances but infused with STYLEX's own unique stamp, so repeat plays are mandatory. The set is reminiscent of a conversation between the dance floor and the booth, an unspoken recognition that the energy is reciprocated, not coerced. <br><br>STYLEX is also a master behind the decks. As host of Data Transmission Radio's Tech House Unleashed show, he previews his sets that reveal sharp ears and deep respect for the genre's heritage. His live sets are captivating, with seamless segues, witty layering, and an emphasis on feeling the room. While his DJing is only three years old, he possesses the composure and maturity of a seasoned pro with him, exuding confidence while still being in touch with the crowd.<br><br>For those who want more of his sound, Feel The Heat is sitting easily in the same place as Martin Ikin's Hooked or Jewel Kid's Bangs, offering an equally frantic, club-oriented experience. Those familiar with Carl Cox's early days of festival anthems or Mark Knight's floor-smashing tech house will hear the familiar nods of STYLEX's production style, but his music is also fresh and uncompromising in its own right. Aside from tracks and concerts, his work is the crowd high of electronic music — the sensation of dancing in masses to a beat that will not let you sit down.<br><br>STYLEX persists as an evolving force, marrying rush-hour choruses with moments of vocal declaration and melodic suspense. His rise in recent years portends a career that could define global dance floors, not just as a DJ or producer, but as one voice with a vision. With each release, he stakes his claim to being an artist that understands both the technical and emotional potential of electronic music, and makes it impossible to turn away from what's coming next.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Stephanie Happening Crafts a Defiant Alt-Pop Anthem with “Smash Hits”</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/stephanie-happening-crafts-a-defiant-alt-pop-anthem-with-smash-hits/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/stephanie-happening-crafts-a-defiant-alt-pop-anthem-with-smash-hits/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-06T10:09:54+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/56/volecho-music-magazine.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/56/volecho-music-magazine.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>London’s alt-pop scene has a new voice rising from its cinematic undercurrents. Stephanie Happening, known for translating resilience and identity into electrifying music, returns with Smash Hits, a single that feels both intimate and expansive. The track balances raw emotional honesty with production that’s as polished as it is exhilarating, a combination that positions Stephanie not just as a singer-songwriter but as a storyteller for a generation navigating reclamation and self-discovery.<br><br>From the first shimmering synth, Smash Hits asserts itself as a survivor-coded anthem. It captures that precise moment of breaking free, of shedding past constraints and reclaiming power, whether on screen, on stage, or in the private theaters of personal growth. Bold hooks meet soaring textures, creating a soundscape that is cinematic without ever feeling distant. It’s a track that’s built to move the body while speaking directly to the heart, a balance that few artists navigate so confidently.<br><br>Stephanie Happening’s work is inseparable from their lived experience. As an artist managing life with Dissociative Identity Disorder, their music carries a rare emotional specificity and layered storytelling. Every beat, every vocal turn is informed by themes of survival, resilience, and identity reclamation. Smash Hits continues this thread, pairing the euphoria of a danceable rhythm with the weight of lived experience, creating music that functions as both escape and reflection.<br><br>Listeners familiar with artists like Rina Sawayama or Christine and the Queens will recognize a similar fearless blending of pop sensibilities with theatrical storytelling. Yet Stephanie’s voice feels uniquely their own — unflinching, urgent, and unapologetically real. The track invites comparisons to the cathartic moments in films like Promising Young Woman or the visual storytelling of contemporary music videos from FKA twigs, where empowerment and defiance play out in vivid, layered ways.<br><br>The production of Smash Hits is both cinematic and immediate. Synth layers shimmer and pulse with kinetic energy, while the hook lands with a satisfying snap, demanding both attention and participation. The single demonstrates Stephanie’s keen ear for sync-ready moments, the kind of track that could score a montage of self-realization or play in a club where the collective energy mirrors the song’s narrative of liberation.<br><br>What makes Smash Hits stand out is its ability to be both personal and universal. While the song carries the specificity of Stephanie’s lived experience, its themes of empowerment, healing, and self-definition resonate broadly. It’s music that affirms identity while inviting listeners to move, to feel, and to witness themselves in the story being told.<br><br>Stephanie Happening continues to shape a distinctive space in alt-pop, where the cinematic and the personal meet, where hooks are weapons of reclamation, and where emotion drives the rhythm. Smash Hits is a declaration of presence, a moment of defiance that encourages listeners not only to dance but to confront and embrace their own truths. For those seeking alt-pop that is both visceral and reflective, this track aligns with the work of contemporary innovators while staking out its own luminous territory.</p>
<p> </p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top 5 Releases 10-4-25</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/top-5-releases-10-4-25/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/top-5-releases-10-4-25/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-04T18:57:29+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/55/Top-Tracks.jpg" alt="" />
                    STYLEX (UK): Turning Heat Into Beat There are songs that just make&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/55/Top-Tracks.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><strong>STYLEX (UK): Turning Heat Into Beat</strong><br><br>There are songs that just make you move, and then there are songs that get the room to move. STYLEX's latest single Feel The Heat on Krafted Digital does just that. It's almost a pulse rather than a song,  a manufactured frenzy of the basslines, percussion, and nights-after nights' tension that is well-suited for the concrete dance floor and red lights. The UK producer has been honing his craft in the house and tech house audience with a groove-heavy, attitude-filled sound, but the thing that really distinguishes him is how he integrates those retro influences, Mark Knight's hard-as-nails drum programming, Martin Ikin's push into something living and current.<br><br>Prior to the studio, STYLEX discovered the true language of dance floors at Hakkasan, where he honed his timing as a resident DJ, knowing a crowd doesn't merely listen, they respond. His radio show, Tech House Unleashed on Data Transmission, is just as frenetic, a transmission of sweat and beat that never pauses to catch breath. Feel The Heat is followed by a Eastern Resident remix, turning the track into something trance-like and liquid, the post-dawn reflection of the main set tempest.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/12pdWeCkdLLMkoZgd4KvFL?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br>If you’ve been hooked on the industrial pulse of D. Ramirez or the late-night swagger of James Hurr, this release deserves a spot on your queue. It hits that sweet spot between club and consciousness, like the sound you’d catch between sets at Printworks or during the chase scene of a Nicholas Winding Refn film. In a scene obsessed with the next drop, STYLEX reminds us that rhythm is still the real story.<br><br><strong>The Shrubs: Surf, Static, and Second Winds</strong><br><br>The Shrubs are not shy about nostalgia — they're bringing it back with a nod. Fall Behind replaces their former slow-burning melancholy with a spoonful of surf rock that seems to have splashed straight from a VHS that has seen some sun. It's close, brightly hued, and low-key, with guitars that shine like sunlight off chrome and a rhythm section that rides the self-assured laconicism of a band that's found its groove. From their own studio, Flowers on the Wall, the song sounds as though it was made in their living room, all warmth and hiss, the kind of glitches that make old records sound genuine.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/6FVjrnNveFv04z66lrq0nW?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br><br>You can see The Ventures in their twang, perhaps a trace of The Bambi Molesters in the phrasing with reverb, but The Shrubs don't use the retro hand for novelty. They use it for feel. There's a feeling of camaraderie in their sound, the sibling rapport between Josh and Miguel, the comfortable groove that comes from playing with someone who gets your sentence done for you.<br><br>It’s hard not to think of Fall Behind in cinematic terms. Imagine a Sofia Coppola character taking a solo drive through small-town streets at sunset, or an early Tarantino montage where everything seems to hum with hidden energy. If you’ve had La Luz or Allah-Las on repeat, this one will slip right into your rotation. The Shrubs might call Houston home, but this record feels like the coast, endless, free, and full of echo.<br><br><strong>Stephanie Happening: Soundtracking the Self</strong><br><br>There is something enthralling about Stephanie Happening's Smash Hits. It hovers midway between confession and film anthem, throbbing to synths that glitter like city lights at 3 a.m. The Londoner has a talent for rendering weighty subjects, identity, trauma, survival, into songs that could soundtrack a whole film. It is music that wants to heal but will not shy away from the grime.<br><br>Stephanie's music is in the tradition of artists such as MUNA, Chvrches, and Christine and the Queens, smartly emotive, deeply personal, but built for the headliner. You can picture Smash Hits ending a teen coming-of-age film or foreshadowing a moment of quiet rebellion on Euphoria. There's revolution in every note, but release too, the kind that creeps up on you when you can finally lay down the veneer of all being okay.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/6RwcSRQBFFEKNQURz8S8cz?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br><br>Dissociative Identity Disorder chronicler that they are, Stephanie imposes fragmentation upon them. Their music is not chaos but control, a mosaic cut of existence. The production is vivid, but the voice slices through like truth in breaking silence. If ever you've ever needed music that's raw but cinematic, Smash Hits is that outsider type of song that doesn't capture the moment so much as lingers with you long after the lights remain on.</p>
<p><strong>wht.rbbt.obj: Noir Rock and the Final Station</strong><br><br>wht.rbbt.obj of Chicago are wrapping up their NATO Call Sign Trilogy with Oscar Bravo Juliett, and the third act of this cinematic movie sounds like it's been in the works in hideaway. Every song has the sound of being encoded, full of peril and desire, a mix of raw soul and rock grime native to smoky rooms and final cigarettes. Frank and River Rabbitte, a married couple, exchange tension and chemistry, their music caught between Amy Winehouse at her most provocative and The Black Keys at their grimiest.<br><br>The album closes out a stretch started by Whiskey Hotel Tango and Romeo Bravo Bravo Tango, and this third installment comes along like closing credits ,black, raucous, and lovely in its destruction. Oh, and Monsters of Nothing (The FURY Edition) is on the way, a collaboration with Chi-town's FURY that distills their noir to something more electric.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/0PI8MYoL8duo6Caac8kfrH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br><br>You might just picture Oscar Bravo Juliett cutting a neo-noir clip, envision Drive, Sin City, or a late-night Peaky Blinders offshoot. It's music with the rhythm of the city and the pain of the people still with it. If rock still has peril attached to it, wht.rbbt.obj show that it has not been domesticated.<br><br><strong>Rusty Reid: The Long Shadow of The Unreasonables</strong><br><br>Sometimes an album seems to have waited for the world to catch up with it. Rusty Reid's The Unreasonables was recorded years and years ago, sat in a dusty corner waiting to be released, a melodic rock time bomb that cuts just as cleanly through today's playlists. It's huge and stripped and feeling, like something that easily could have nestled on either side of Tom Petty or The Cars on a late-80s mix tape.<br><br>Rusty, operating out of the Pacific Northwest these days, abandons the political and philosophical bent of earlier work for something more stripped-down. The songs are ad-lib, lust, attitude, the strained nervous jump of a band that played because they wanted to. Attitude Change rocks like a saloon song, Piece of the Action hangs loose with Stones-like cool, and Shock Me bangs with a jukebox-and-late-night-play beat.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/1nF30rOkQmQDkFji7aFmXB?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br><br>You can stack The Unreasonables back-to-back with Fleetwood Mac during the Rumours era or early Cheap Trick, rock filth sheathed in pop savvy. It's easy to imagine the album restored to life in some akin to Almost Famous or an updated Stranger Things set piece, distilling the mood of reckless abandon. For a forty-year-lost record, it sounds incredibly vital, a rediscovery that sounds like a reminder of the way things were back in the good old days of rock and roll before we all became too clever with it.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Eleri Ward Steps Into Her Own With Internal Rituals</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/eleri-ward-steps-into-her-own-with-internal-rituals/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/eleri-ward-steps-into-her-own-with-internal-rituals/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-29T13:05:00+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/35/Untitled-design-2.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/35/Untitled-design-2.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://online.pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/bzyq/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1983467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a><br><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address><hr style="color: var(--text-primary-color); font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);"><address class="align-center"> </address>
<p>Eleri Ward has already established herself as a one-woman Stephen Sondheim interpreter. Her acoustic folk albums A Perfect Little Death and Keep a Tender Distance reinterpreted the master's songs in horrorscopic personal language, catching The New York Times' and Forbes' attention and landing her on tour with Josh Groban. But on her first album of originals, Internal Rituals, released Sept. 26, Ward shines the light on herself. What comes across is an album that is grand and close, the voice of a showy voice re-writing its own script.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p><br>On 12 tracks, Ward bounds across the stripped-down folk that marked her Sondheim arrangements and into a more lush, more adventurous sound. Ethereal electronics swirl around intricately layered vocals, and glimpses of future-jazz, indie-pop, and heavenly ambience drift through the arrangements. At their center is her voice, a limber soprano that glides between registers, throbbing with feeling on a par with a string instrument. Though her covers albums demonstrated her facility as an interpreter, Internal Rituals reveals her to be a writer of vision and tough vulnerability.<br><br>The melodies themselves are drawn from the intensely personal, memories, astrological charts, emotional cycles, and they never sound narcissistic. Instead, they happen as intimate confidences, born of the shared heartbeat of love, fear, loss, and rebirth. There You Go implies karma is a blessing, with the hindsight recognition of gratitude. Float contains the nightmarish exhilaration of freedom. Venusian Light radiates self-love. Someone, Something New travels even further, mapping the complicated terrain of Ward's relationship with her biological father and the way trauma can repeat itself through generations.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/2tDDozfRiM8hb85ptdVKUt?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p>Her own solo single, Run, is a turnaround. Propulsive synths and piano drive her delivery as she performs the thrum of throwing off outdated shackles. You know listening that Ward isn't so much announcing a new beginning so much as fashioning one. That feeling of momentum, of arrival, permeates the album as an entirety.<br><br>The title of the album, Internal Rituals, is fitting. The songs are reckonings and release rituals, almost personal healing rituals done on behalf of the listener. Ward has spoken about learning to make beats and produce D.I.Y. herself, taking control of her sound for the first time as a songwriter. You can hear the independence on the album. It isn't over-produced or aloof, it pulsates with the urgency of someone finding voice in the moment.<br><br>Ward's journey to this location has been steeped in performance for a long time. A five-year-old multi-instrumentalist, she went through the Chicago Academy for the Arts and Boston Conservatory before finding her career as an accomplished stage actor and recording artist. She played off-Broadway in Only Gold, acted in the American Repertory Theater's Gatsby, and most recently took center stage at the Miu Miu Tales &amp; Tellers fashion show. But Internal Rituals is not so much about displaying range as it is about taking up space. It is not the voice of an interpreter or a purveyor of other people's words—it is the voice of an artist finding herself in full.<br><br>There are times on the record that evoke the cinematic splendor of Björk or the unearthly fragility of Imogen Heap, but Ward is not imitating. She is building a sound world where dramatics and closeness exist together, where electronic beats can walk hand in hand with folk sympathies, and where the near becomes large enough to become communal.<br><br>Internal Rituals is not a debut album. It's an entry into adulthood. Through these songs, Ward moves beyond interpreter to designer of her own musical world, asserting that the desire which she had hitherto expressed through Sondheim was her own as well. And now, at last, she can express it in words.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sons of Racketeers Mine History and Revolution in &quot;Beat The Press Gang&quot;</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/sons-of-racketeers-mine-history-and-revolution-in-beat-the-press-gang/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/sons-of-racketeers-mine-history-and-revolution-in-beat-the-press-gang/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-26T12:31:13+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/53/volecho-music-magazine-13.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/53/volecho-music-magazine-13.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #3</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/gtyt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1994035" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address><hr>
<p>Certain songs are torn from the moment, and others tug at the string of the past to show us how little things have actually changed. Sons of Racketeers' latest track "Beat The Press Gang" does both. Rooted in the violent past of press gangs at sea—whereby men were bullied or kidnapped into the service of English warships—the song also becomes a protest anthem in the present, one that hauntingly resonates with a world where children are still conscripted into wars they never chose.<br><br>To the ear, on initial listening, "Beat The Press Gang" is music to a folk story. The opening tangles into acoustic texture, a campfire storyteller drawing you in before the storm hits. And then the song breaks out into something more, bigger, and a whole lot more angry. Electric guitars slice in, drums push the rhythm ahead, and vocals soar into a virtuosic call to action. It's a change that reflects the tension of its subject—the subdued inception of a story that bursts forth into rebellion.<br><br>There is something epic in the building of this song. It's not much of a stretch to see it as the score to a historical epic like Master and Commander, but with an added injection of modern tension that would fit nicely into the hard-luck grind of Peaky Blinders. The folk roots keep it grounded in a tradition of tales of working lives, but the rock power charges it into the modern day, making the struggle concrete.<br><br>Lyrical-wise, Sons of Racketeers eschew sermonizing. They tap instead into the emotional content of the story. You feel the terror of men being turned out of their houses, the rage of losing power, and the fleeting burst of outrage in not taking it lying down. That's the human element that resonates with you. It's not sailors in the historical past—it's anybody today and now who are being drafted, displaced, or threatened with wars they never enlisted in.<br><br>The din reminds one of groups such as The Decemberists, who for a long time have blended folk heritage and rock narrative, but Sons of Racketeers venture further into electric fire. One hears a bit of The Pogues in the folk-punk edge of the song, and even Led Zeppelin when the band heads into its harder riffs. It's a hybrid that is raw-sounding and planned at the same time, as if the song was composed to be played live in a dense place where the audience can stomp and bellow along.<br><br>In a way, "Beat The Press Gang" is more than an album—it's a testament to what is possible in folk rock. It's protest music without slogans, history class without textbooks, and rock without the glaze. It doesn't try to be background music, but instead makes you feel the weight of its tale.<br><br>For those who adored the blaze of The National's "Bloodbuzz Ohio," the sweeping historical sagas of The Decemberists, or the tempestuous anger of Wolfmother, this song will be a refreshing addition to the playlist. And for those who have ever challenged authority, seethed at injustice, or simply craved a song that speaks to some primal urge, "Beat The Press Gang" comes with energy.<br><br>Sons of Racketeers have taken a black page from the past and made it a song that's as vibrant and contemporary as anything. It's a message that the past bites back, and that with just the right blend of folk and rock, it still does.</p>
<p> </p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bran.AI Glows With Promising New Ballad &quot;Same Light&quot;</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/branai-glows-with-promising-new-ballad-same-light/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/branai-glows-with-promising-new-ballad-same-light/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-26T12:46:30+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/52/volecho-music-magazine-12.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/52/volecho-music-magazine-12.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #3</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/gtyt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1994035" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>There are songs that are made for the dance floor, songs made for the trip home, and then those which leave you standing still where you are with the might of their honesty. Bran.AI's new song "Same Light" falls into the third category, a soulful ballad with that kind of timelessness you'd come to expect from an artist bold enough to bare their heart. It is one of perseverance built on and one of belief that there is always somebody out there in hard times who can catch and reflect your light back at you.<br><br>The power of "Same Light" is in its restraint. Bran.AI can croon along with untroubled clarity, with only a line committing itself that is both deeply personal and ubiquitously relatable. The arrangement is bare-bones enough to allow the vocal muscle to be the centre point but full enough to give the ballad some broad sonic scope. It's got the intimacy of a whispered secret but the grandeur of a film score, the sort of song that might soundtrack a climactic moment in a romance drama or one of those Netflix tearjerkers where the characters finally reveal what we, the audience, already knew anyway.<br><br>Essentially, "Same Light" is a love song, but not in the superficial manner of fleeting attraction. It is about what type of connection follows hurt, follows loss, follows disappointment. It is about understanding that someone else not just sees your scars but has some too, and somehow you both fit because of it, not despite it. That idea has the same emotional currency as timeless ballads such as Adele's "Someone Like You" or Lewis Capaldi's "Before You Go," where love and heartbreak blend into something greater than both.<br><br>Pop culture is full of stories that echo the spirit of “Same Light.” Think of Jesse and Céline in Richard Linklater’s Before Sunrise, characters who seem destined to meet against all odds, or the way Greta Gerwig’s Little Women lingers on the quiet inevitability of soulmates finding each other through circumstance. Bran.AI’s ballad fits into that tradition, a reminder that even when the road feels unbearably long, something—or someone—waits at the end of it.<br><br>For fans of emotionally resonant songwriting, "Same Light" will find a home between more recent releases such as Gracie Abrams' The Secret of Us, or the raw emotional closeness of Noah Kahan's acoustic songs. And yet there is also a shimmering optimism that's nearer to Coldplay's stadium love anthems, those songs that make the stadiums nod along in harmony. Bran.AI manages to bridge those worlds somehow—hushed enough to sound confessional, but big enough to sound communal.<br><br>"Same Light" comes at a time when so much of the world seems to be in shambles, and perhaps that is why it is so powerful. Love songs are usually throwaways, but this is not. It sticks. It gives hope. It gives something to cling to, if only long enough for a few moments.<br><br>Bran.AI can call the song a message of hope, but it's every bit an entreaty—as in, have hope in connectivity, persevere through hardship, know that someone somewhere is making their way towards you under the same light.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Reetoxa Turnes Truth into Celebration With New Single</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/reetoxa-turnes-truth-into-celebration-with-new-single/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/reetoxa-turnes-truth-into-celebration-with-new-single/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-26T12:46:34+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/51/volecho-music-magazine-11.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/51/volecho-music-magazine-11.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #3</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/gtyt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1994035" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>Occasionally, a song appears that's larger than the amount of time it exists for. Reetoxa's latest release "Papa Loves Ladyboys" is just such a song—equal measure party anthem and social commentary. At its surface, it's a sparkling rock-pop track with a certain dancefloor magic. Beneath, it's an intensely personal tale of love, acceptance, and the bravery it takes to live openly, whatever your age.<br><br>The inspiration is as profound as suggested by the title. The song was born through a grown-up relative of the artist who, having lived in seclusion for years, revealed his true self to his family and accepted himself in the society of LGBTQ+. Instead of making the moment a ballad out of nostalgia, Reetoxa turns the tables and chooses to release joy, laughter, and liberation. The end result is a song that's both emotional and catch, making an act of confession one of freedom.<br><br>How "Papa Loves Ladyboys" works is that it's evenly split between sincerity and play. It's not burdened with sadness. Rather, it's on hue, rhythm, and playful tenderness, proving that even tales of adversity can be reworked as triumphs. It's as if the song runs in parallel with these anthems for joy and truth: Scissor Sisters' gay camp rebellion, Mika's campy but pinpointed storytelling. Camp, it's catchy, and evidence of music's long tradition of being one of the most effective ways of redefining how we speak about identity.<br><br>Sonically, the single is pretty far in the direction of dance-pop, with snarling synth lines, thudding percussion, and a beat that insists on movement. But it's not empty calories—the song is a sugar high with an anchor. The lyrics, sung winking and smiling, have the weight of acceptance, and the production keeps that weight from ever feeling heavy. It's the sort of tune you might find coming from a nightclub, a Pride parade, or even the midst of a family kitchen shindig, where its message of love and self-truth resonates equally.<br><br>Themed, the drop is in dialogue with pop culture's ever-perennially celebratory choruses of queer joy. Heartstopper and Pride are reminders that queer stories don't have to be tragedies—queer stories can instead be light, light and full of sound. Reetoxa's single is likewise invigorating: a nod that acceptance can be a dance chart-topper and not necessarily a dirge.<br><br>For those pop fans with something different in their bonnet, "Papa Loves Ladyboys" will sit nicely alongside the likes of Years &amp; Years, Troye Sivan, or even classic Kylie Minogue. It is silly, but it is not bubblegum. It is near, but it is not close in. It is the kind of single that you can't help but want to overanalyze while at the same time throwing your arms up in frustration.<br><br>Finally, "Papa Loves Ladyboys" is freedom disguised as a party, and it's why it's so powerful. Reetoxa has taken a private family tale and turned it into an anthem that overshoots—it's one that declares that regardless of who you are, it's never too late to discover the light, to laugh, and dance yourself into truth.</p>
<p> </p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
