<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>volecho.com</title>
    <link href="https://volecho.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://volecho.com" />
    <updated>2025-01-07T00:53:12+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Volecho.com</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://volecho.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>VANARIN’s Mesmerizing New Release: A Taste of Their Upcoming Third Album</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/new-music/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/new-music/</id>

        <updated>2025-01-07T00:53:12+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/20/Untitled-design.jpg" alt="" />
                    As anticipation builds for VANARIN’s highly awaited third album under the Dischi Sotterranei label, the British-Italian band continues to make&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/20/Untitled-design.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>As anticipation builds for VANARIN’s highly awaited third album under the Dischi Sotterranei label, the British-Italian band continues to make waves across the music world. Already earning accolades and securing their spot among the most compelling acts of the moment, VANARIN’s recent feature on the prestigious BBC platforms has solidified their rising-star status. Now, to ease the wait for their next big release, the band is gifting fans with a new single “What We Said”.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/6j2186lsxzwtnEEeDA76tm?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br>This latest track is a mesmerizing psych ballad, anchored by an entrancing piano progression that takes center stage. Layered atop is the frontman’s hypnotic voice, which weaves a spellbinding rhythm, undulating and intoxicating as it explores the haunting aftermath of a love lost. Like a mantra, the lyrics obsessively question the meaning behind a lover’s parting words, plunging the listener into a dreamy yet poignant introspection.</p>
<p class="align-center"><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.ibb.co/WgkyQB1/VANARIN-Artwork-Credit-by-Rebeca-Margescu.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="VANARIN-Artwork-Credit-by-Rebeca-Margescu" border="0"></p>
<p><br><br>Fans of Tame Impala’s Currents will feel the familiar pull of melancholic yet circular lyrics, while those who appreciate The Beatles’ experimental era will be drawn to the artful manipulation and pitch-shifted vocal sections. But that’s not all—the track’s lush sonic landscape is further enriched by a warm, soulful bass line and vintage-inspired guitar phrases that seem to echo straight out of the 1960s.<br><br>What truly sets VANARIN apart is their meticulous attention to detail. Every element of “What We Said” unfolds with a fresh, unexpected twist, creating a soundscape that feels innovative yet timeless. It’s this masterful balance that makes their signature style unmistakable and keeps their audience coming back for more.<br><br>With such a tantalizing preview, VANARIN’s third album promises to be a standout moment in contemporary music—one that fans and critics alike will be eager to experience.</p>
<p> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Twinnie’s Bold New Era: The Country-Pop Starlet Unleashes “Hypothetically”</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/twinnies-bold-new-era-the-country-pop-starlet-unleashes-hypothetically/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/twinnies-bold-new-era-the-country-pop-starlet-unleashes-hypothetically/</id>

        <updated>2024-10-22T21:41:13+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/17/unnamed.png" alt="" />
                    Twinnie has just released the bouncy music video to her latest single, "Hypothetically," which made its world premiere in an&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/17/unnamed.png" alt="" />
                <p>Twinnie has just released the bouncy music video to her latest single, "Hypothetically," which made its world premiere in an exclusive at Daily Mail. The music video stars the talented Twinnie in a striking leopard-print romper capture precisely the playfulness and fearlessness of the song. She's a commanding presence-think a world where this songstress is drawing in viewers "into her world of flirtatious fun," according to Daily Mail.<br><br>"Hypothetically" arrived September 20, 2024, and has already garnered rave reviews. As best put by Nashville Socialite, it's an "absolute knockout" of fresh country-pop peppered with a healthy dose of 90s girl-power nostalgia. Twinnie's carefree yet reflective lyrics meander through love, possibilities, and the unspoken "what-ifs," while channeling her trademark warmth and confidence-a mix of strengths and vulnerabilities not unlike those embodied by none other than Shania Twain herself. Meanwhile, Music City Melodies drew the parallel between it and Jessie James Decker by mentioning that Twinnie's flirtatious lyrics are a reflection of Decker's bold style-an inspiring quality urging everybody to be brazen.<br>like</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RzMCKsLznr4?si=Ub3zuFzIURPpt1xJ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p>This single marks a new turn for Twinnie, where she leaves her "sad-girl" phase for a more fun and confident sound. Co-written with Reid Sorel and Grace Gunn, "Hypothetically" teases themes from her forthcoming sophomore album, Something We Used To Say, due out on November 8, 2024.<br><br>Off the back of her new album, Twinnie has announced a small, intimate tour of the UK this November, stopping off in London, Brighton, Manchester, York and Glasgow. Her Manchester show has already sold out.</p>
<p><br>Last year, Twinnie joined the cast of Emmerdale to play Jade, the mean boxing promoter. On her latest role, Twinnie says: "Life has been crazy juggling acting and music, with lots of back and forth between Nashville and Yorkshire, but I'm loving every second of it!<br><br>No stranger to acting, Twinnie has a history on British television with roles in the shows Doctors and Hollyoaks, where she received much acclaim for her portrayal of Porsche McQueen, whose storyline tackled critical social issues like childhood sexual abuse.<br><br>Twinnie became the first British artist to sing the American National Anthem at the stadium of Nashville SC, GEODIS Park, stamping her credentials as a global star with an infectious dynamism.<br><br>Twinnie's life story has been very far from ordinary. At her tender age, she had acted among giants like Glenn Close and Robin Thicke while her West End performances in Chicago and Rock of Ages hinted at the shining star she was to become. Since the launch of her solo career in 2020, she consistently blew minds with her genre-defying sound and continues to inspire, recently performing at AmericanaFest's "Stella + Friends: The Power of Women in Music."</p>
<p>Hypothetically" is only the beginning of her exciting new chapter.<br><br></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Online Magazine Issue #1</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/online-magazine-issue-1/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/online-magazine-issue-1/</id>

        <updated>2024-07-11T00:32:34+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/16/new-issue-1.png" alt="" />
                    We are so excited to share with you the first issue of the online Volecho magazine! You can download below&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/16/new-issue-1.png" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">We are so excited to share with you the first issue of the online Volecho magazine! You can download below and support us!</p>
<h2 class="align-center"><a href="https://www.patreon.com/volechomag/shop/volecho-online-magazine-1-265296?utm_medium=clipboard_copy&amp;utm_source=copyLink&amp;utm_campaign=productshare_fan&amp;utm_content=join_link" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Volecho Issue #1</a></h2>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>CHIEF STATE Releasing 5-song acoustic EP on April 5</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/chief-state-releasing-5-song-acoustic-ep-on-april-5/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/chief-state-releasing-5-song-acoustic-ep-on-april-5/</id>
            <category term="Music"/>

        <updated>2024-02-17T21:10:15+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/15/chief-state.jpg" alt="" />
                    Vancouver, BC pop punk trailblazers, Chief State, unveil their latest release - a 5-song acoustic EP that promises to redefine your&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/15/chief-state.jpg" alt="" />
                <p align="left">Vancouver, BC pop punk trailblazers, <strong>Chief State</strong>, unveil their latest release - a 5-song acoustic EP that promises to redefine your connection with their music. Set to release via <strong>Mutant League Records</strong> in April 2024, <strong>"The Acoustic EP"</strong> invites listeners to rediscover Chief State's catalog through a captivating and intimate lens.</p>
<p align="left">The first single "Living Out A Lie" will be released on February 21.</p>
<p align="center"><strong>Pre-save 'The Acoustic EP' here:</strong> <a href="https://email.cloud.secureclick.net/c/6813?id=22149820.58045.1.fd3f4a097b6d39b5765a202c5ef4168e" target="_blank" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://email.cloud.secureclick.net/c/6813?id%3D22149820.58045.1.fd3f4a097b6d39b5765a202c5ef4168e&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1708280673119000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1cp-qZTTAner-sUt87zZBq" rel="noopener">https://orcd.co/chiefstate</a></p>
<p align="left">Of the EP's first single and video, "Living Out A Lie", front man <strong>Fraser Simpson</strong> says, <em>"As the name suggests, this song is about the feeling of your life being a lie, self-doubt, faking it until you make it, imposter syndrome. Something I constantly struggle with. I’ve made a lot of choices to get where I am today and often I’m not sure if I’m actually being true to myself. The song also speaks directly about doubt in previous relationships, whether my heart was actually in it. The video, created by the brilliant Lindsey Blane, really tied this idea together and we deliberately ended it before knowing the answer to the guy’s proposal. I think we’re all a little glossy on the surface, we show what we want to show but once it comes down to a life changing choice, like shown in the video, the truth will come out."</em></p>
<p align="left">In honor of Valentine's Day, Chief State and Mutant League Records have launched a limited edition "Valentines Day" shirt design, available exclusively through the Mutant League <a href="https://email.cloud.secureclick.net/c/6813?id=22149820.58046.1.ecfcdb1534ee1c836307b7ea8daa6c6d" target="_blank" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://email.cloud.secureclick.net/c/6813?id%3D22149820.58046.1.ecfcdb1534ee1c836307b7ea8daa6c6d&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1708280673119000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0AOtc6H_AlFxh_C1NKHgxj" rel="noopener"><strong>webstore</strong></a>.</p>
<p align="left">All V-day shirt purchases through April 5th will receive a handwritten lyric by Fraser Simpson of Chief State, along with a song from the upcoming EP.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Conquest of Madness: Aguirre and the Perils of Power</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/aguirre-the-wrath-of-god/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/aguirre-the-wrath-of-god/</id>
            <category term="Cinema"/>

        <updated>2024-10-22T17:30:51+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/14/aguirre-the-wrath-of-god.jpg" alt="" />
                    Werner Herzog, director of Aguirre, the Wrath of God, sought a location atop a mountain near Machu Picchu in Peru&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/14/aguirre-the-wrath-of-god.jpg" alt="" />
                <p> </p>
<p>Werner Herzog, director of Aguirre, the Wrath of God, sought a location atop a mountain near Machu Picchu in Peru to shoot the opening scenes. He led his cast and crew of 450 people, together with a procession of horses, pigs, and llamas, up the mountainside. His group slogged down an ancient stairway carved into the rocks by the Incans centuries ago, traveling through dense jungle on steep footing made slick by rain. Clouds blanketed the entire mountain, shrouding everything in dense, moist fog, allowing no visibility. Even the local upland tribes got vertigo-stricken at 14,000 feet, but the players withstood the conditions in their heavy costume armor and Spanish conquistador clothing.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9LqdXayZ6Q0?si=iyBRtObuml7TJMpS" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p>The journey appeared impossible. Herzog had to persuade his crew to keep going, to keep ascending higher and higher along a vertical drop of almost 2,000 feet. Herzog was concerned that their efforts had been in vain when they arrived at their destination. The clouds eventually cleared, and daylight broke through. Herzog got his shots, capturing a line of actors, barely specks in the frame, descending down the Incan stairway between a severe mountain slope and a cloud of fog. Herzog believed a miracle had occurred. He reflected on his good fortune, saying, "It was on this day that I definitely came to know my destiny." Ironically, it was that kind of mad determination and assumption of fate that pushed his film's zealous protagonist, Lope de Aguirre.</p>
<p>Before he was recognized for filming documentaries like Grizzly Man (2005) and Encounters at the End of the World (2008) about people consumed by passion in remote, unattainable locales, Herzog made narrative films about the same subject, demonstrating that he shared their obsession. Aguirre, the Wrath of God was Herzog's first such picture, as well as his first international hit outside of his own West Germany. His 1972 film depicts a failed Spanish voyage to find El Dorado, the legendary Incan city of gold.</p>
<h3>A fever dream</h3>
<p>On the surface, the film looks to be a traditional period adventure about the fight between humans and nature, with Spanish conquistadors venturing into the unknown to collect treasure, only to be defeated by the unconquered forest. However, upon closer observation, the entire picture is set in a fever dream of obsessive urges. After all, what better example of crazy than conquistadors marching off in a specified direction with hundreds of troops and resources in tow, hoping to discover a place whose location is unknown and, ultimately, does not exist? Many of Herzog's greatest films feature rebels against both humanity and nature.</p>
<p>They strive for an unachievable goal, possibly out of pride or vanity, but they are eventually swallowed and regurgitated by Nature. Herzog knew these obsessions better than most; he later experienced them when filming Fitzcarraldo (1982), as well as countless other tales and documentaries, including Aguirre, the Wrath of God. He exhibits his own obsession by directing this ambitious film to follow his subject into the heart of darkness, rather than filming on a studio lot or a safer place.</p>
<p class="align-center"><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.ibb.co/mbV6fC2/image.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="image" border="0"></p>
<h3>Detachment from reality </h3>
<p>Herzog never meant to make Aguirre, the Wrath of God into a historical account of Lope de Aguirre's life and times. In reality, his initial concept for the picture was inspired by a children's book that included a brief segment on Aguirre. What captivated the director the most was the figure's complete craziness. When Aguirre joined Don Pedro de Ursúa's expedition to find El Dorado, he already had a reputation for being a vicious and ruthless conquistador. On the trip, Aguirre overcame his superiors and took command. In a manic letter discovered during Herzog's research, Aguirre denounces King Felipe II of Spain, declaring him "dethroned and stripped of all rights," and renaming himself "the Wrath of God."</p>
<p class="align-center"><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.ibb.co/XZ8Qmrr/image.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="image" border="0"></p>
<p>He went on to declare himself "the new Emperor of El Dorado and New Spain" and led his captured expedition into the unknown. Finally, he arrived at the Atlantic, no closer to discovering El Dorado, and all but a few of his followers had died. This daring, this detachment from reality while immersed in nature, drew the director in, and Herzog determined to recreate it in his film. "Aguirre is one of history's great losers," the filmmaker once stated in an interview, and the concept of Aguirre's unusually fixated worldview layered his screenplay more than actual reality. "The entire script is pure invention," Herzog revealed in an interview. What he meant to represent was not facts and dates, but the frame of mind attributed to Aguirre, the type of adventurer who seeks a wealth of riches while also pursuing his own death.</p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bolaji Badejo: The Actor Behind the Xenomorph </title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/bolaji-badejo-the-actor-behind-the-xenomorph/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/bolaji-badejo-the-actor-behind-the-xenomorph/</id>
            <category term="Cinema"/>

        <updated>2024-02-10T14:24:56+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/13/alien.jpg" alt="" />
                    With a height of 208 cm (6'10"), Bolaji Badejo embodied the Alien in "Alien." He became the stereotypical monster, dressed&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/13/alien.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>With a height of 208 cm (6'10"), Bolaji Badejo embodied the Alien in "Alien." He became the stereotypical monster, dressed in an outfit that included elongated limbs and a skeletal, biomechanical appearance.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/WC_0vbh54XI?si=hjlJ3Q6NmDb9WqCo" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p><br>Using skillful cinematography to enhance the Alien's unsettling aura through camera angles, lighting, and framing, the special effects crew amplified this effect.<br><br></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xpKi41a1rJI?si=ULsZU9J6cfymRMph" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p><br>Following his move to Nigeria in 1980, Badejo turned down roles in the "Alien" sequels, which resulted in a greater use of puppetry and animation in these movies. That movie "Alien" is still his only credit.<br><br>He established an art gallery in Nigeria in 1983 before he unfortunately died at the age of 39 from sickle cell illness in 1992.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>San Diego&#x27;s Strike Twelve Release &#x27;Last Band Standing’</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/san-diegos-strike-twelve-release-last-band-standing/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/san-diegos-strike-twelve-release-last-band-standing/</id>
            <category term="Music"/>

        <updated>2024-10-22T21:56:42+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/12/3.jpg" alt="" />
                    San Diego/Temecula punks Strike Twelve have released the new album 'Last Band Standing' via Thousand Islands Records. Watch the video&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/12/3.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="">San Diego/Temecula punks Strike Twelve have released the new album 'Last Band Standing' via Thousand Islands Records.</p>
<p class="">Watch the video for "Baseball Bat" here: <a href="https://youtu.be/NmmM301ezr4">https://youtu.be/NmmM301ezr4</a>.</p>
<p class="">Video shot by Danny, Joey, Matty, and Melisa. Edited by Aaron Bruski.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NmmM301ezr4?si=uzPtW6eOmn2MZHQ2" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p class="">Guitarist/vocalist Matty T says, "'Baseball Bat' involves a violent physical release caused by prolonged emotional suppression. Sometimes I just can’t bite my tongue any longer and before I open my big mouth it’s better to physically exert myself."</p>
<p class="">Strike Twelve is</p>
<p class="">Matt Turek (“Matty T”) - guitar / vocals</p>
<p class="">Joe Treister (“Joey T”) - bass / vocals</p>
<p class="">Dan Bahou (“Danny B”) - drums</p>
<p class="">Danny B, Matty T and Joey T of So-Cal punk rock band Strike Twelve have been playing live at your local dive since 2003. Whether they’re first or last in the lineup, they will undoubtedly be the band having the most fun. They love what they do and they love doing it with each other, which is why all three members have stuck with the band since the beginning. With an unmatched chemistry that can only be developed with twenty years of friendship, it’s safe to say that this isn’t just a phase. Their new album Last Band Standing will be out in summer 2023 on Montreal-based Thousand Islands Records, and hopefully it will help to take their excellent adventure to the international stage.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Problem Daughter have released a brand new song and music video titled &quot;Self Amusing Smile&quot;</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/problem-daughter-have-released-a-brand-new-song-and-music-video-titled-self-amusing-smile/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/problem-daughter-have-released-a-brand-new-song-and-music-video-titled-self-amusing-smile/</id>
            <category term="Music"/>

        <updated>2024-02-09T21:00:51+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/11/2.jpg" alt="" />
                    Salt Lake City, UT punks Problem Daughter have released a brand new song and music video titled "Self Amusing Smile", the first&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/11/2.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Salt Lake City, UT punks <a href="http://www.facebook.com/problemdaughter" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><strong>Problem Daughter</strong></a> have released a brand new song and music video titled "Self Amusing Smile", the first track is off their forthcoming album "Grow Up Trash" due out March 22nd on Wiretap Records (North America) and Bearded Punk Records (EU).</p>
<p>Check out the video and single, which is available today (Jan 25th) on all digital streaming sites. Problem Daughter last released their debut full length "Fits Of Disorganized Boredom" in 2016 via Dying Scene Records.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DEJJediASNU?si=i0qEz5steavN19Rd" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p>Started by high school friends in 2008, Problem Daughter plays some of the best blue collar, punk-rock grit and misery juxtaposed with catpop-punkpunk melodies you'll ever hear.</p>
<p>Named as the state of Utah's representative on <em>Kerrang's</em> 'United States of Punk', the best punk bands from every US state. Not regulated to a mere two chords and screaming, the quartet take everything great about punk and pack it into songs varied in structure and melodies that never grow redundant. Their music smells like a sweaty basement show, tastes like cheap beer on a lamp-lit porch and feels like not wanting to go home at the end of the night.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>LA&#x27;s Grave Secrets Release New Single &quot;Bad Blood&quot;</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/las-grave-secrets-release-new-single-bad-blood/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/las-grave-secrets-release-new-single-bad-blood/</id>
            <category term="Music"/>

        <updated>2024-02-09T21:00:57+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/10/1.jpg" alt="" />
                    Los Angeles-based four-piece band Grave Secrets are sharing their latest single "Bad Bood," out now on Wiretap Records. Grave Secrets&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/10/1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="">Los Angeles-based four-piece band Grave Secrets are sharing their latest single "Bad Bood," out now on Wiretap Records.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VB98Zljf_p4?si=kvD2QipSPutaRm0O" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p class="">Grave Secrets seamlessly melds melodic punk &amp; hardcore influences. Every member is a profound lover of nostalgic sounds with a modern touch. Grave Secrets works exclusively works with Alex Estrada (Joyce Manor &amp; Touche Amore) at his Pale Moon Ranch studio. Wiretap Records will release the band's upcoming album later this year.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>NYC&#x27;s Baby Got Back Talk Release New EP &#x27;Wince, Repeat&#x27; via Wiretap Records</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/nycs-baby-got-back-talk-release-new-ep-wince-repeat-via-wiretap-records/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/nycs-baby-got-back-talk-release-new-ep-wince-repeat-via-wiretap-records/</id>
            <category term="Music"/>

        <updated>2024-02-09T21:01:03+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/9/VOLECHO-2.jpg" alt="" />
                    Stream Here: https://open.spotify.com/album/3TYIuWrlEpMoKubbBOJrN2?si=WszqKSgSQSCX99f9jX2ubg '17 Black Alternative Bands Leading The Next Generation' - Alternative Press 'Top 8 Punkest Bands on the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/9/VOLECHO-2.jpg" alt="" />
                <h1 data-shrink-original-size="42"> </h1>
<div class="body">
<p class=""> </p>
<p class=""><strong>Stream Here:</strong> <a href="https://open.spotify.com/album/3TYIuWrlEpMoKubbBOJrN2?si=WszqKSgSQSCX99f9jX2ubg">https://open.spotify.com/album/3TYIuWrlEpMoKubbBOJrN2?si=WszqKSgSQSCX99f9jX2ubg</a></p>
<p class=""><em>'17 Black Alternative Bands Leading The Next Generation' - Alternative Press</em></p>
<p class=""><em>'Top 8 Punkest Bands on the Planet'- Afropunk</em></p>
<p class="">Photo: Kate Hoos</p>
<p class="">New Your City alterna-punks Baby Got Back Talk are debuting their new EP 'Wince, Repeat' EP, out now on Wiretap Records.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JZFpxUHQ6qw?si=bUVH9sR5w9TFPLwm" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
