<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>volecho.com</title>
    <link href="https://volecho.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://volecho.com" />
    <updated>2025-09-16T21:11:16+03:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Volecho.com</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://volecho.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Get Featured</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/get-featured/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/get-featured/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-16T16:06:09+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    If you're interested in getting featured in our magazine, website or blog&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>If you're interested in getting featured in our magazine, website or blog you can submit your music via <strong><a href="https://app.musosoup.com/submit/volechomag" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Musosoup</a></strong> and <strong><a href="https://app.one-submit.com/direct-submit/26717/2358/5525/Volecho-Magazine-blog-Music-Promotion" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">One Submit</a></strong>.</p>
<p>For more details message us at: <a href="mailto:volecho@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volecho@gmail.com</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Interview with Neverskin</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/interview-with-neverskin/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/interview-with-neverskin/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-16T21:10:39+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/36/Untitled-design-3.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/36/Untitled-design-3.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://online.pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/bzyq/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1983467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a><br><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address><hr>
<p><strong>How did it feel to reunite musically after 20 years since Ambiossis?</strong><br><br>Clint: It actually was interesting. We didn't really hang out anymore for such a long time and I myself hadn't done anything with music for about 8 years.<br><br>One day I was jogging and listening to tunes when all of a sudden our old band Ambiossis popped up, whilest we did not upload the music on Spotify and I did not select it. So while I was running and one of the tracks kicked in, I was thinking, 'I wonder how Remy is doing?'. So I send him a message and we met up and basically expressed wanting to make some tunes in general.<br><br>The whole process went weirdly natural and was so smooth, the first track was lyrically and vocally written and recorded before the end of the next week, so we basically had our base down in no time.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p><br><strong>What was the spark that led to creating "Snatched"?</strong><br><br>Remy: We were sitting around while I jammed some grooves on my guitar. It reminded us of the old-school nu-metal we grew up with a groove that makes your head bop and gives you the urge to run through the streets for no reason at all. The verses and choruses came naturally, because back when we had a band together from 2003 to 2006 (Ambiossis), we already blended groove, rap verses, and big ballad-like choruses. It felt like we simply picked up where we left off in 2006.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/5HMwEqcFmgJ9BOyudzx6jr?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><strong>What emotions do you hope listeners take from "Snatched"?</strong><br><br>Clint: I of course, hope it gives people a positive or helpful feeling or emotion, but honestly, any emotion will do. As long as people feel a certain way about what we made. Feel free to love the track, we hope you do, but also feel free to hate it or dislike it. Music is universal and the beauty of it, is that it connects with some and doesn't with others. There is enough to go around :) But of course, we make music and share it for people to hopefully connect to it and love it.<br><br><strong>Why did you choose to record in home studios instead of a traditional setup?</strong><br><br>Remy: With so many instruments being multi-sampled in the best studios, and plugins -especially guitar amps- sounding better than ever, particularly in the last five years, I personally don’t feel the need to record in a traditional studio. I have great memories of working in them, but it’s just not convenient for me. Recording at home saves money and removes time pressure. I've been recording demos at home since around 2000, and by 2003 I was already using a guitar amp sim floorboard for both live gigs and home sessions.</p>
<p><strong>How has your creative process evolved since your early band days?</strong><br><br>Remy: It’s quite similar, but with all great sounding plugins and libraries these days I just start out with synths / weird sounds / drums before I even do guitars, because it sparks guitar riff idea's. Back then, we just had some rough guitar parts and vocal sketches as demos, often guessing what the final product would sound like. Now, while recording it almost sounds like the end product, which sparks more idea's. But we still sit around working out the guitar parts like the early days and Clint have his lyrics done in a couple of hours and he sends his vocal-demo the next day, so that stayed the same.<br><br><strong>What’s next for Neverskin after this debut single?</strong><br><br>Clint: Well, lets say we hope to reach as many people as we can with our debut single 'Snatched' first off.<br><br>Next step will be the release of our second single. I won't spoil to much about that one yet. Long term, we're more or less winging it and basing it on how people receive it. So although there are no plans yet, we could end up going live, recording an EP or album, or perhaps keeping it on the low. Let's see...</p>
<p><strong>If you could describe your music in three words, what would they be?</strong><br><br>Clint: Oh that is a though one. I guess, 'Emotional' (full of all types of emotion), 'Free' (not limited by boundaries, we make what we feel, could be this now and something completely different later), 'Expressive' (lyrics are metaphorical, the music is whatever we feel like we want it to be)</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Eleri Ward Steps Into Her Own With Internal Rituals</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/eleri-ward-steps-into-her-own-with-internal-rituals/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/eleri-ward-steps-into-her-own-with-internal-rituals/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-16T21:06:45+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/35/Untitled-design-2.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/35/Untitled-design-2.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://online.pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/bzyq/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1983467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a><br><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address><hr style="color: var(--text-primary-color); font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);"><address class="align-center"> </address>
<p>Eleri Ward has already established herself as a one-woman Stephen Sondheim interpreter. Her acoustic folk albums A Perfect Little Death and Keep a Tender Distance reinterpreted the master's songs in horrorscopic personal language, catching The New York Times' and Forbes' attention and landing her on tour with Josh Groban. But on her first album of originals, Internal Rituals, released Sept. 26, Ward shines the light on herself. What comes across is an album that is grand and close, the voice of a showy voice re-writing its own script.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p><br>On 12 tracks, Ward bounds across the stripped-down folk that marked her Sondheim arrangements and into a more lush, more adventurous sound. Ethereal electronics swirl around intricately layered vocals, and glimpses of future-jazz, indie-pop, and heavenly ambience drift through the arrangements. At their center is her voice, a limber soprano that glides between registers, throbbing with feeling on a par with a string instrument. Though her covers albums demonstrated her facility as an interpreter, Internal Rituals reveals her to be a writer of vision and tough vulnerability.<br><br>The melodies themselves are drawn from the intensely personal, memories, astrological charts, emotional cycles, and they never sound narcissistic. Instead, they happen as intimate confidences, born of the shared heartbeat of love, fear, loss, and rebirth. There You Go implies karma is a blessing, with the hindsight recognition of gratitude. Float contains the nightmarish exhilaration of freedom. Venusian Light radiates self-love. Someone, Something New travels even further, mapping the complicated terrain of Ward's relationship with her biological father and the way trauma can repeat itself through generations.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/2tDDozfRiM8hb85ptdVKUt?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p>Her own solo single, Run, is a turnaround. Propulsive synths and piano drive her delivery as she performs the thrum of throwing off outdated shackles. You know listening that Ward isn't so much announcing a new beginning so much as fashioning one. That feeling of momentum, of arrival, permeates the album as an entirety.<br><br>The title of the album, Internal Rituals, is fitting. The songs are reckonings and release rituals, almost personal healing rituals done on behalf of the listener. Ward has spoken about learning to make beats and produce D.I.Y. herself, taking control of her sound for the first time as a songwriter. You can hear the independence on the album. It isn't over-produced or aloof, it pulsates with the urgency of someone finding voice in the moment.<br><br>Ward's journey to this location has been steeped in performance for a long time. A five-year-old multi-instrumentalist, she went through the Chicago Academy for the Arts and Boston Conservatory before finding her career as an accomplished stage actor and recording artist. She played off-Broadway in Only Gold, acted in the American Repertory Theater's Gatsby, and most recently took center stage at the Miu Miu Tales &amp; Tellers fashion show. But Internal Rituals is not so much about displaying range as it is about taking up space. It is not the voice of an interpreter or a purveyor of other people's words—it is the voice of an artist finding herself in full.<br><br>There are times on the record that evoke the cinematic splendor of Björk or the unearthly fragility of Imogen Heap, but Ward is not imitating. She is building a sound world where dramatics and closeness exist together, where electronic beats can walk hand in hand with folk sympathies, and where the near becomes large enough to become communal.<br><br>Internal Rituals is not a debut album. It's an entry into adulthood. Through these songs, Ward moves beyond interpreter to designer of her own musical world, asserting that the desire which she had hitherto expressed through Sondheim was her own as well. And now, at last, she can express it in words.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>JA Lena Releases Bold New Single “Ana Elli Hena”</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/ja-lena-releases-bold-new-single-ana-elli-hena/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/ja-lena-releases-bold-new-single-ana-elli-hena/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-16T21:10:49+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/34/volecho.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/34/volecho.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://online.pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/bzyq/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1983467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a><br><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address><hr style="color: var(--text-primary-color); font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);"><address class="align-center"> </address>
<p>When Serbian singer and performer JA Lena proclaims Ana Elli Hena—"I Am the One Here", she is not doing so for fun. It is a confident act of artistic assertion. This is a Serbian artist singing Egyptian Arabic, drawing on Balkan dynamism and oriental beats into a sound as obstreperous as it is spellbinding. It's the newest entry in her increasing body of work, and one that may be her most brazen so far.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p>JA Lena has been gathering steam for the last several years with songs such as Katila and Gamila, both of which gave listeners a sense of her unique approach to blending traditions. Those songs promised much, but Ana Elli Hena leaves no doubt. The production is crisp, layered with throbbing percussion and melodies that sound ancient yet new, while her vocal performance cuts through the mix with conviction. It is more than a statement about sound, though. It is a statement about presence.<br><br>There is something compelling in how Lena moves between worlds. Having grown up in Serbia, she was immersed in the raw passion of Balkan music, a tradition founded on intricate rhythms and emotional directness. In Ana Elli Hena, she brings that heat to Arabic performance, where the modal scales and cyclical rhythms of Egyptian music provide her with something new to challenge. Rather than reducing those styles to something bland, she keeps tension between them alive. The song flourishes there.<br><br>This cross-cultural bridging is not just about musical structure, but also about point of view. In deciding to sing in Egyptian Arabic alone, Lena positions herself to be challenged and celebrated. For the Arab community, there is intrigue in listening to a foreign artist adopt the language and perform it with such passion. For audiences in the Balkans, there is excitement in witnessing one of their own venture so much farther than anticipated. In both instances, the end result is connection. She will not remain in one lane, and it is that refusal that is essentially what provides her voice power.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/1QaIGEG2l2mZE5WwXPLADq?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br>Themed, Ana Elli Hena is about taking up space in a world which continually attempts to define and confine women's being. The name alone is a statement: "I am the one here." The refrain throughout the song holds almost incantatory authority, as if addressed to an audience, an enemy, and a self simultaneously. A song of strength, it is indeed, but one of survival also. It resists erasure by being impossible to overlook.<br><br>The song also has a cinematic feel. One can picture it scoring a climactic scene in a movie, a confrontation, say, or a moment when the hero finally takes hold of their authority. So it is that Lena's work draws to mind such artists as Sevdaliza, whose Persian-Dutch heritage drives similarly boundary-pushing experimentation, or even M.I.A., who blended Tamil origins with London's underground culture. As they do, Lena employs pop formats and club-friendly beats as a medium for something more profound, something pegged to history, language, and identity politics.<br><br>Ana Elli Hena finds herself in a moment in culture where global pop has become more permeable. Think about how Rosalía constructed El Mal Querer from flamenco heritage into a global pop album, or the way Stromae transformed Belgian chanson into electronic anthems. JA Lena is not part of a trend, but she is part of this movement of artists not willing to let geography confine them. Serbian and Arabic traditions are not different boxes to her, but sparks waiting to ignite one another.<br><br></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>TRALALAS Find Fire in the Fragile With “Burns”</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/tralalas-find-fire-in-the-fragile-with-burns/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/tralalas-find-fire-in-the-fragile-with-burns/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-16T21:10:55+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/33/Untitled-design-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/33/Untitled-design-1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://online.pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/bzyq/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1983467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a><br><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>In the hauntingly silent darkness of their July drop Winter on the Vine, Danish dark-pop group TRALALAS come back with Burns, a song that is its own subdued inflammatory. While the initial single mapped the cycles of transformation and clenched quiet of complicity, Burns turns in. At three and thirty seconds, it's close but sweeping, an exploration of the capriciousness of human relationship and the manner in which feelings ricochet back and forth between gain and loss, proximity and distance.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p><br>With songwriting and frontman Morten Alsinger as its core, TRALALAS construct their sound more as a group constructing atmosphere. You can feel it in the textures—warm analog production, Heidi Lindahl's ghostly harmonies twisting around Alsinger's voice, Christina Schmidt Damm's calm keys, Thomas Golzen's bass and guitar lines twining around the beat, and Francis Nørgaard Jensen's restrained percussion. Featuring Thomas Li on co-production, the track inhales with accuracy, every moment suspended between light and shadow.<br><br>Alsinger describes his writing as essayistic, and so it is. These are not free-floating lyrics. They are statements of mind abbreviated in action, inner voice expelled. His invocation of Montaigne—"I write from the dark against the light"—does as much to record not just the ethos of Burns but the larger enterprise being constructed on in TRALALAS' self-titled debut album out in October. The group don't require simplistic answers or moralities. They require perspective, the place where you end up when you stay with brokenness long enough for its rough edges to get in your face.<br><br>In that way, Burns is a companion piece to Winter on the Vine. Together, the two singles map out the territory for an album that will be an inner examination of vulnerability and intensity, composed not in slogans but in slow-burning patience. If Winter on the Vine was a lesson in circles, then Burns is about embers left over, the way love, friendship, and loss slice us open and leave us walking around the ashes searching for shape.<br><br>The music is in the dark-pop style of someone like Zola Jesus, Agnes Obel, or the more subdued edges of Depeche Mode, but TRALALAS form their own sound. The music is electric and muted, cinematic but not overwrought. It's the kind of song that doesn't sweep you in with bombast but sweeps you in with sound, until you find yourself leaning forward just to hear the next turn.<br><br>And at the end of Burns, there is left not just the lyric or the hook but the space between them. It is a record that requires repeat listens not because it is catchy in the traditional way, but because it leaves an emotional residue. And in that which remains, half shadow, half flame, you begin to see what TRALALAS are constructing towards: an album which harnesses the vulnerability as fuel rather than extinguishes it.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Marzanna Breathes Strange New Life Into the Familiar</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/marzanna-breathes-strange-new-life-into-the-familiar/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/marzanna-breathes-strange-new-life-into-the-familiar/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-16T21:11:00+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/32/Marzanna.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/32/Marzanna.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://online.pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/bzyq/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1983467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a><br><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>Marianne Nowottny has been a chameleon of a sort for all her working life. A composer, she has spent decades bending her voice to unearthly colors, stretching the limits of phrasing and atmosphere. Now, playing in her longtime alter ego Marzanna, she's pushed the cover album format in an album that is both predestined and unexpected. Plainly named Marzanna, the album combines covers of Kate Bush, David Bowie, Joni Mitchell, Siouxsie and the Banshees, and others' songs, songs that have intrinsic strong signatures, but here drawn into darker, dreamier landscapes.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br>Covers aren't unfamiliar ground for Nowottny. She has dropped them around in her catalogue in records and live shows, Yazoo, Anne Murray, the Beatles, Nico, the Platters, Johnny Cash, Astrud Gilberto. But never has she given herself over entirely to the form. That's a central decision. It's not going back from writing to record an entire album of other people's work, but to claim a different type of writing: one that's informed by attentive listening, on shaping familiar melodies into new space until they're sounds like ghosts talking in new tongues.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/4fdAOtFptYOG82sR6iIaOd?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br>She prolongs syllables so they hang, and shortens others with snapping sparks. That alone will set a mood, a mood where even the most familiar songs feel haunted, reborn. Hearing Marzanna sing Bowie or Joni Mitchell is to hear like the song is recalling itself in a dream, rewriting the edges of memory.<br><br>The making of the record wasn't easy. By the artist's own account, it nearly didn't happen at all. The five-year cycle of stoppages, respins, and technological catastrophes, crashed hard drives, misplaced songs, the plodding grind of start-over, should have killed the project a hundred times over. Instead, they imparted a sort of ruggedness. What ultimately came in sounds worn down by effort but unexpectedly calm, as if the perseverance it took to complete it infused the recordings themselves.<br><br>Marzanna did not embark on this trip alone. She extended a hand, calling in musicians and friends of all corners of the globe to carry their voices, their instruments, and themselves. That sense of camaraderie pervades the album, though mood continues ever her own. These are songs, also, with their revered beginnings concealed behind the illusion that they're being shared in hushed tones from room to room.<br><br>What is interesting about Marzanna is not that it reimagines the cover album, but that it tackles the concept uncharacteristically seriously. Rather than attempting to out-play the originals or play them ironically, Nowottny utilizes them as portals, familiar gateways that open up into foreign, fog-filled rooms. And in doing so, she demonstrates something about covers that is commonly lost: that they are not imitation or retro, but conversation. About how one hears a song differently from another's past, their phrasing, their suffering, their joy.<br><br>Through this album, Marzanna flips inside out the songs we thought we knew by heart, so we may hear them, as if for the very first time. It's not copy. It's revivification. And it echoes on long after the final note disappears.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Moletrap Find Their Voice With Mid Welsh, Pt 1</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/moletrap-find-their-voice-with-mid-welsh-pt-1/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/moletrap-find-their-voice-with-mid-welsh-pt-1/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-16T21:11:05+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/31/moletrap.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/31/moletrap.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://online.pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/bzyq/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1983467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a><br><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>From the Cambrian moors to Bristol's streets of strife, Moletrap are sounding as tough and vital as the terrain that brought them up. The band release Mid Welsh, Pt 1, a five-track EP which manages to both use the crash of guitars and the gentle determination of Mid Wales itself. It is a record, not an album. It is a reckoning with identity, with language, and with what it's like to be from somewhere history books and pop culture have forgotten.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p>The EP is the product of being in good form. Early singles such as Rhagofn and Middle of the Land were widely hailed for their blend of melodic pop sensibilities and bone-crunching heaviness. BBC Introducing described the music as "un-ignorably great" and vowed "a thousand mosh pits await." Which isn't hype. There is a sense of urgency to these songs that evokes the sense of getting on with it of early Manic Street Preachers, combined with the restless energy of current alt-rock bands like Idles.<br><br>What gives Mid Welsh, Pt 1 its bite is not so much the dynamics of the guitars or the authority of the vocals as the earthiness of experience. The members of the band met initially in Welsh-language school, where they once attempted to escape. When they left, all they could do was escape from what they had called "the least settled part of Wales and England." Years later, however, music beckoned them back to their roots. They've discovered their own history, traced the unmarked routes of the Cambrians, and challenged how colonisation and erasure have left their mark on the Welsh language.<br><br>All that tension is crammed into every one of those songs. Nation of Sanctuary hails Wales' openness to the world, while Rhagofn cautions against smugness in respect of work remaining to be undertaken. Taffy and What a Beautiful Place gaze inward on issues of heritage and belonging, while the title track is more like a reclaimed anthem. Every cut is full of both urgency and sensitivity, as though the band are grasping something delicate even as they crank the volume to eleven.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/4dBkAxAKrRa1w7DZNCuSvf?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br>Moletrap's sound is full of contradiction in the finest sense. They are bilingual but international, refined but abrasive, politicized but intensely personal. Their riffs crash and churn like the mountains to which they continually refer, but the melody soars with hooks that stick long after the distortion wears off. That dichotomy is what makes Mid Welsh, Pt 1 not only a potent debut album but an important cultural statement.<br><br>The band openly talk about the chaos of their musical creation, of jam sessions turned into something far larger. They credit BBC Horizons and all the DJs, writers, and communities that raised them up. That humility only makes the music more powerful. Moletrap are not faking to be saviors of Welsh heritage, but as three friends with guitars, drums, and resolve getting back to where they belong.<br><br>Listening to Mid Welsh, Pt 1, you can hear a band still working out their mythology but sounding as though already they have something profound in their hands. Their music is heavy enough to rattle halls but intelligent enough to contain a lesson in history in its chords. Ultimately, Moletrap do just what they aim to do. They sound like the Cambrian Mountains rolling downhill, unstoppable, unquietable.</p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>New Magazine Articles</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/new-magazine-articles/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/new-magazine-articles/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-16T21:11:16+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/30/Untitled-design-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/30/Untitled-design-1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://online.pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/bzyq/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.peecho.com/print/en/1983467" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a><br><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Our new magazine will be available in print and online on 9/17/25</strong></p>
<hr>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.ibb.co/BKwzq5n6/image.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="image" border="0"></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/6pXf07QiFjFQtHSI5rNhJl?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.ibb.co/mrT4xgS7/Ramonster.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Ramonster" border="0"></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/59nk45Ichnyi9kKda3hfLj?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Anaïs &amp; The Hoops Finds Her Voice in Growing Pains</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/anais-and-the-hoops-finds-her-voice-in-growing-pains/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/anais-and-the-hoops-finds-her-voice-in-growing-pains/</id>

        <updated>2025-09-11T12:06:06+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/29/Untitled-design.jpg" alt="" />
                    Anaïs &amp; The Hoops, a newly risen star from Brooklyn, is here&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/29/Untitled-design.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Anaïs &amp; The Hoops, a newly risen star from Brooklyn, is here with the release of her EP, Growing Pains, out on all streaming platforms today. With Growing Pains, Anaïs takes her signature blend of indie pop, jazz, and folk, carrying it in a collection of nostalgia, playfulness, and pure energy.<br><br>For three years, Anaïs had worked on the six-song EP. After some time, she engaged Ben Coleman in the production, along with collaborators from the band and fellow New York musicians, so that each track would bear a particular collaborative flair. The spirit of togetherness even extended outside the immediate band, with her mom helping out in refining the lyrics for Anaïs's first-ever French-language piece, "Passe le temps"; meanwhile, a poem by her friend Alex Brady is incorporated into the track "Cool." "It's been fun to cobble together," she shares. "Basically, every song was touched by someone in or around the live band."<br><br>Identity, nostalgia, and self-discovery are themes Anaïs continues to delve into on Growing Pains. The songs capture the struggle of growing up while still wanting to clutch onto that kid who used to be. "These songs were some of the first I wrote that truly felt like me," says Anaïs. "Most of these songs came together after I moved from Californ..."</p>
<p> The record comprises six tracks that feel deceptively warm and sincere, somewhere between indie pop, touches of jazz, and subtly inflected with folk, the kind of record one can almost touch, almost live with. Each track drops a shade into a different memory. </p>
<p>In the time since her streaming footprint has been widening and social following mounting, Anaïs has built much repute as a highly magnetic live act. She has sold out her own headline shows, played at NXNE Music Festival in Toronto, and opened for the likes of Jade Bird and Thunder Jackson.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Anaïs &amp; The Hoops is the project of Brooklyn-based, San Diego-raised singer and songwriter Anaïs Lund. She got her start performing in jazz clubs and restaurants before finding her own musical footing in 2019, when she began writing the songs that would shape her project, Anaïs &amp; The Hoops. With her jazz-inflected vocals, sharp yet vulnerable lyrics, catchy pop melodies, and a captivating retro aesthetic, Anaïs &amp; The Hoops is quickly establishing herself as one of indie music’s most distinctive new voices.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="align-left">A different release, full of surprises and unique elements taken from albums we love, with so many interesting influences in the sound. It is a unique jazz creation with exceptional vocals and a tremendous rhythm. The instruments resemble a well-oiled machine with a steady rhythm and precision of movement, which nevertheless sounds so natural and beautiful.</p>
<p class="align-center"><br><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" data-testid="embed-iframe" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/3uDOV2wz4myUGk2jgtZbaw?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div> <br><br></p>
<p>The end result is a beautiful accompaniment of musical calls that flatter Anaïs' voice with a beautiful mix of different sounds, even including a guitar with light fuzz. If we had to describe this release, we would say that it is a breath of fresh air, especially in an era of fast songs and hits aimed at immediate recognition and artistic popularity. A breath of fresh air born from a band that knows jazz and music in general.</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center">Follow our playlist for more songs, albums and new releases</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" data-testid="embed-iframe" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Dax Faces the Mirror in “Man I Used To Be”</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/dax-faces-the-mirror-in-man-i-used-to-be/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/dax-faces-the-mirror-in-man-i-used-to-be/</id>

        <updated>2025-08-25T03:20:52+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/28/volecho.jpg" alt="" />
                    With Man I Used To Be, Dax steps into a new chapter&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/28/volecho.jpg" alt="" />
                <p data-start="50" data-end="497">With <em data-start="55" data-end="73">Man I Used To Be</em>, Dax steps into a new chapter of his career, one that trades bravado for reflection and rapid-fire bars for something closer to a prayer. Known first as a rapper with relentless delivery and sharp punchlines, he now turns his voice inward, creating a track that feels more like a confessional than a performance. The song is raw, slow-burning, and completely unafraid of silence, allowing space for every word to sink in.</p>
<p data-start="499" data-end="1020">The heart of the track lies in its honesty. Dax addresses his past struggles with addiction and the regret that still lingers. He does not hide from the damage, nor does he glorify it. Instead, the lyrics read like a letter to his younger self, a direct confrontation with the man who once made choices that threatened to derail everything. The vulnerability here is striking. Hip hop has always made room for confession, but Dax delivers his with a mix of sorrow and resolve that feels different from his earlier work.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="499" data-end="1020"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" data-testid="embed-iframe" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1v6KfzL3Tw4jt6eYM9l0Fk?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p data-start="1022" data-end="1511">What makes <em data-start="1033" data-end="1051">Man I Used To Be</em> stand out is the way it frames change. The song is not just about admitting mistakes. It is about the uncomfortable but necessary act of moving forward without erasing the past. Dax balances grief with gratitude, admitting how far he fell while also pointing to the faith that lifted him back up. His references to God are not heavy-handed, but they are central. They serve as proof that redemption is not an abstract concept for him. It is a lived reality.</p>
<p data-start="1513" data-end="1864">The production mirrors this shift. Instead of dense beats or flashy arrangements, the track is anchored in soulful textures and a steady rhythm that gives Dax’s voice space to carry the weight of the story. Each line lands with gravity, but there is also a sense of release in the delivery, as if saying these things out loud is part of the healing.</p>
<p data-start="1866" data-end="2348">The track signals a willingness to step outside the comfort zone of genre and persona, to make music that is not just catchy but necessary. In this way, <em data-start="2074" data-end="2092">Man I Used To Be</em> connects to the lineage of personal confessionals from artists like NF, Logic, and even 2Pac at his most reflective. Beyond rap, it recalls the emotional candor of gospel and the stark storytelling of singer-songwriters who let their pain shape the art.</p>
<p data-start="2350" data-end="2681">For listeners, the song works as more than autobiography. It becomes a mirror. Anyone who has struggled with self-destruction, regret, or the slow climb toward change will hear echoes of themselves. The track does not offer easy solutions, but it does offer company in the struggle, which is often the most powerful form of hope.</p>
<p data-start="2683" data-end="3030" data-is-last-node="" data-is-only-node="">With <em data-start="2688" data-end="2706">Man I Used To Be</em>, Dax proves that growth can sound just as gripping as ambition. It is a reminder that vulnerability, when spoken plainly and set to music, can carry as much force as any verse meant to dominate a stage. This is not the sound of a rapper chasing hits. It is the sound of a man facing himself, and inviting us to listen in.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
