<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>volecho.com</title>
    <link href="https://volecho.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://volecho.com" />
    <updated>2025-08-25T03:20:52+03:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Volecho.com</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://volecho.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Dax Faces the Mirror in “Man I Used To Be”</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/dax-faces-the-mirror-in-man-i-used-to-be/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/dax-faces-the-mirror-in-man-i-used-to-be/</id>

        <updated>2025-08-25T03:20:52+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/28/volecho.jpg" alt="" />
                    With Man I Used To Be, Dax steps into a new chapter of his career, one that trades bravado for&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/28/volecho.jpg" alt="" />
                <p data-start="50" data-end="497">With <em data-start="55" data-end="73">Man I Used To Be</em>, Dax steps into a new chapter of his career, one that trades bravado for reflection and rapid-fire bars for something closer to a prayer. Known first as a rapper with relentless delivery and sharp punchlines, he now turns his voice inward, creating a track that feels more like a confessional than a performance. The song is raw, slow-burning, and completely unafraid of silence, allowing space for every word to sink in.</p>
<p data-start="499" data-end="1020">The heart of the track lies in its honesty. Dax addresses his past struggles with addiction and the regret that still lingers. He does not hide from the damage, nor does he glorify it. Instead, the lyrics read like a letter to his younger self, a direct confrontation with the man who once made choices that threatened to derail everything. The vulnerability here is striking. Hip hop has always made room for confession, but Dax delivers his with a mix of sorrow and resolve that feels different from his earlier work.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="499" data-end="1020"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" data-testid="embed-iframe" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1v6KfzL3Tw4jt6eYM9l0Fk?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p data-start="1022" data-end="1511">What makes <em data-start="1033" data-end="1051">Man I Used To Be</em> stand out is the way it frames change. The song is not just about admitting mistakes. It is about the uncomfortable but necessary act of moving forward without erasing the past. Dax balances grief with gratitude, admitting how far he fell while also pointing to the faith that lifted him back up. His references to God are not heavy-handed, but they are central. They serve as proof that redemption is not an abstract concept for him. It is a lived reality.</p>
<p data-start="1513" data-end="1864">The production mirrors this shift. Instead of dense beats or flashy arrangements, the track is anchored in soulful textures and a steady rhythm that gives Dax’s voice space to carry the weight of the story. Each line lands with gravity, but there is also a sense of release in the delivery, as if saying these things out loud is part of the healing.</p>
<p data-start="1866" data-end="2348">The track signals a willingness to step outside the comfort zone of genre and persona, to make music that is not just catchy but necessary. In this way, <em data-start="2074" data-end="2092">Man I Used To Be</em> connects to the lineage of personal confessionals from artists like NF, Logic, and even 2Pac at his most reflective. Beyond rap, it recalls the emotional candor of gospel and the stark storytelling of singer-songwriters who let their pain shape the art.</p>
<p data-start="2350" data-end="2681">For listeners, the song works as more than autobiography. It becomes a mirror. Anyone who has struggled with self-destruction, regret, or the slow climb toward change will hear echoes of themselves. The track does not offer easy solutions, but it does offer company in the struggle, which is often the most powerful form of hope.</p>
<p data-start="2683" data-end="3030" data-is-last-node="" data-is-only-node="">With <em data-start="2688" data-end="2706">Man I Used To Be</em>, Dax proves that growth can sound just as gripping as ambition. It is a reminder that vulnerability, when spoken plainly and set to music, can carry as much force as any verse meant to dominate a stage. This is not the sound of a rapper chasing hits. It is the sound of a man facing himself, and inviting us to listen in.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ana Luna’s Slow-Burning Confession</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/ana-lunas-slow-burning-confession/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/ana-lunas-slow-burning-confession/</id>

        <updated>2025-08-16T01:18:16+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/27/Untitled-design.jpg" alt="" />
                    Ana Luna’s new single Can We Pretend We Just Met at a Bar? does not ask for your attention. It&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/27/Untitled-design.jpg" alt="" />
                <p data-start="42" data-end="523">Ana Luna’s new single <em data-start="64" data-end="102">Can We Pretend We Just Met at a Bar?</em> does not ask for your attention. It pulls you in the way late-night conversations do, with a quiet voice that says just enough to keep you leaning closer. Out today on all streaming platforms, the track deepens the emotional space she carved with earlier releases like <em data-start="372" data-end="388">Daddy’s Empire</em> and <em data-start="393" data-end="412">Dance in a Trance</em>. It is another step toward a debut album that already feels like it will be heavy with atmosphere and truth.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="42" data-end="523"><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.ibb.co/PZfrXFK4/unnamed-2.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="unnamed-2" border="0"></p>
<p data-start="525" data-end="1073">The production here is warm and cinematic, moving with the kind of slow-burn rhythm that never rushes its own heartbeat. Layers unfold in deliberate turns, each one letting Ana’s voice linger in the space it needs. She sings in a tone that feels equal parts intimate and wounded, the sound of someone turning over a thought again and again until it becomes both familiar and unbearable. You hear not just the longing in her delivery but also the quiet acceptance beneath it, a sense that she has already lived through the scene she is describing.</p>
<p data-start="1075" data-end="1612">Ana calls the song a conversation with herself. It is about holding on to a version of the past that feels softer than the truth, about blurring memory and reality in an attempt to make sense of loss. In her words, she imagined the relationship as she wished it could have been, faced how it really was, and confronted the reason she stayed longer than she should have. That contradiction sits at the core of the song. The exterior of love can be hypnotic, keeping you tethered to something even as your inner voice pleads for an exit.</p>
<p data-start="1614" data-end="2065">Born in Ukraine, raised in Paris, and now living in Los Angeles, Ana Luna writes with the range of someone who has collected places, faces, and private heartbreaks. She first kept her music to herself while chasing acting roles, but in college she gave in to what she calls the deeper pull. Her sound folds together dream pop shimmer, alt-rock shadows, and the stripped honesty of a ballad, creating something that feels both grounded and unearthly.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="1614" data-end="2065"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" data-testid="embed-iframe" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/2TBQYE0b55ZvUt5KCJHZUE?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p data-start="2067" data-end="2499"><em data-start="2067" data-end="2105">Can We Pretend We Just Met at a Bar?</em> fits into a lineage of slow, bruised storytelling. It could sit alongside Lana Del Rey’s <em data-start="2195" data-end="2210">Cinnamon Girl</em>, Cigarettes After Sex’s <em data-start="2235" data-end="2239">K.</em>, or Sharon Van Etten’s <em data-start="2263" data-end="2288">I Love You But I’m Lost</em>. Like those tracks, it asks you to sit in a moment rather than escape from it. The song rewards stillness. It offers a space where pain and beauty can occupy the same measure without canceling each other out.</p>
<p data-start="2067" data-end="2499">Photo Credit: Noah Hoffman (<a href="https://twitter.us14.list-manage.com/track/click?u=942fde0b78cdd6bf718a77eff&amp;id=48117443a0&amp;e=920b55f0ef" target="_blank" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://twitter.us14.list-manage.com/track/click?u%3D942fde0b78cdd6bf718a77eff%26id%3D48117443a0%26e%3D920b55f0ef&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1755382196751000&amp;usg=AOvVaw15EbDMYjcrW-hkRJshR8vt" rel="noopener">@conversingwithaliens</a>)</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Paperwhite’s &#x27;Reach&#x27; Is a Dream Pulled Into Focus</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/paperwhites-reach-is-a-dream-pulled-into-focus/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/paperwhites-reach-is-a-dream-pulled-into-focus/</id>

        <updated>2025-08-11T19:13:38+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/26/unnamed-5.jpg" alt="" />
                    After years of quiet and a world reshaped by distance, Paperwhite returns with Reach, a five-song collection that feels like&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/26/unnamed-5.jpg" alt="" />
                <p data-start="55" data-end="534">After years of quiet and a world reshaped by distance, Paperwhite returns with <em data-start="134" data-end="141">Reach</em>, a five-song collection that feels like it kept evolving even when we could not hear it. The sibling duo, Katie and Ben Marshall, have always worked in a space where feeling matters as much as sound. This time, though, their music lands with a different kind of presence. Not louder or heavier, just clearer. More grounded. Like they have carried the weight of time and turned it into melody.</p>
<p data-start="536" data-end="1009">At the center of <em data-start="553" data-end="560">Reach</em> is <em data-start="564" data-end="578">Looking Back</em>, a track that holds its breath in the best way. It started early in the pandemic but only found its final shape with the help of composer Philip Sheppard. His string arrangements stretch through the track with quiet purpose. They do not overpower the synths. They move through them like something remembered rather than added. The result is a sound that feels both fragile and full, something built from memory rather than design.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="536" data-end="1009"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" data-testid="embed-iframe" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/3bz2WVtIw2Fr0fwrqc4Bs0?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p data-start="1011" data-end="1487">That is the strength of the entire EP. <em data-start="1050" data-end="1057">Reach</em> sounds like it was made by people who lived inside their ideas for a while before speaking them out loud. It holds moments gently. Nothing feels rushed. Katie’s vocals move with soft confidence, floating over Ben’s production in a way that gives space for emotion without losing structure. These are not songs meant to escape into. They are songs meant to sit with, especially in the in-between hours when silence feels too loud.</p>
<p data-start="1489" data-end="1997">Ten years have passed since <strong>Paperwhite </strong>introduced themselves with <strong><em data-start="1555" data-end="1563">Escape</em></strong>. Back then, their sound fit neatly into a wave of glossy synth-pop made for headphone daydreams. You can still hear traces of that in the shimmer of this new EP. But there is more here. Organic layers. Soft acoustic touches. Lyrical choices that sound less like poetry and more like truth spoken plainly. It is pop music, but not in a way that pushes for attention. It is music that lets the listener come forward on their own terms.</p>
<p data-start="1999" data-end="2378">There is a kind of patience in these songs that feels rare. Nothing here grabs at you. Instead, <em data-start="2095" data-end="2102">Reach</em> draws you in slowly, offering detail after detail the more you listen. It rewards stillness. These tracks are meant for early mornings or late nights, for quiet drives or open windows. They settle in without asking for anything, then stay with you in a way that feels earned.</p>
<p data-start="2380" data-end="2733">Paperwhite still sound like themselves, which is saying something in a genre that often moves too fast to remember what came before. Listeners who love CHVRCHES or Japanese House will feel at home here, but <em data-start="2587" data-end="2594">Reach</em> does not borrow. It remembers. It reflects. It builds something personal out of familiar textures, using light and shadow with equal care.</p>
<p data-start="2735" data-end="3059">The EP never rushes to its point. It trusts that you will get there. In a culture built on short attention spans, this feels quietly bold. Every song has room to breathe. Every lyric lands softly but carries weight. With each listen, what first felt dreamy becomes more detailed. What seemed simple reveals something deeper.</p>
<p data-start="3061" data-end="3350">This is not a loud return. It is not a comeback with fireworks or declarations. It is something more honest. A steady hand reaching back out after time apart. A project that carries both softness and strength. A sound that knows where it came from and does not pretend to be anything else.</p>
<p data-start="3352" data-end="3551" data-is-last-node="" data-is-only-node="">With <em data-start="3357" data-end="3364">Reach</em>, Paperwhite proves that you do not have to chase the moment to create something lasting. You just have to mean it. These songs do. And they stay with you long after the final note fades.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Avery Lynch Strikes Again with Poignant New Single “the boys who don’t know what they want”</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/avery-lynch-strikes-again-with-poignant-new-single-the-boys-who-dont-know-what-they-want/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/avery-lynch-strikes-again-with-poignant-new-single-the-boys-who-dont-know-what-they-want/</id>

        <updated>2025-03-31T00:57:55+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/25/unnamed-2.jpg" alt="" />
                    Avery Lynch unveils her latest emotional masterpiece, “the boys who don’t know what they want,” out today via RECORDS. Known&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/25/unnamed-2.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="" data-start="103" data-end="436">Avery Lynch unveils her latest emotional masterpiece, “the boys who don’t know what they want,” out today via RECORDS. Known for her soul-stirring, piano-driven ballads, Avery has amassed over 100 million streams, cementing her place as a voice of raw, relatable storytelling.</p>
<p class="" data-start="438" data-end="988">With its minimalist production and hauntingly beautiful vocals, “the boys who don’t know what they want” captures the frustration and vulnerability of navigating almost-relationships—those confusing connections where words and actions never quite align. “The title says it all,” Avery explains. “I wrote this about those situations where someone acts like they want a relationship but won’t commit—or the ones who want it but won’t act on it. It’s not necessarily sad, just a reality we’ve all seen and don’t want to keep experiencing.”</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="438" data-end="988"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/7ejsOM6vM20LCgU6vyvYkN?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="" data-start="990" data-end="1242">A sister-song to her fan-favorite track “you’re just a guy,” this latest release reinforces Avery’s ability to turn life’s everyday heartaches into poetic reflections, striking a chord with listeners who have been in the same emotional limbo.</p>
<p class="" data-start="1244" data-end="1656">Originally from Pennsylvania, Avery began composing music at just seven years old, with the piano as her storytelling companion. Now based in Los Angeles, her signature sound—delicate yet deeply expressive—remains at the heart of her artistry. Every song starts with Avery at her piano, crafting heartfelt demos that evolve into the lush, melancholic soundscapes fans have come to love.</p>
<p class="" data-start="1658" data-end="2024">Described as a “happy girl filled with sad songs,” Avery weaves personal experiences, pop culture, and emotional nuance into every lyric. With acclaim from outlets like Just Jared and EARMILK and a growing army of devoted listeners, her recent signing with RECORDS (Sony Music) marks a new era—one that promises even greater heights for this rising star.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Maddie Regent Unveils the Hauntingly Beautiful “Turtleneck” Ahead of Debut Album</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/maddie-regent-unveils-the-hauntingly-beautiful-turtleneck-ahead-of-debut-album/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/maddie-regent-unveils-the-hauntingly-beautiful-turtleneck-ahead-of-debut-album/</id>

        <updated>2025-03-31T00:31:55+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/24/unnamed-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    New York City-based indie-pop artist Maddie Regent continues to captivate with her latest single, “Turtleneck”, a mesmerizing preview of her&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/24/unnamed-1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="" data-start="92" data-end="325">New York City-based indie-pop artist <strong data-start="129" data-end="146">Maddie Regent</strong> continues to captivate with her latest single, <strong data-start="194" data-end="210">“Turtleneck”</strong>, a mesmerizing preview of her upcoming debut album, <em data-start="263" data-end="289">On the phone with my mom</em>, set for release on <strong data-start="310" data-end="322">May 16th</strong>.</p>
<p class="" data-start="327" data-end="723">Building on the <strong data-start="343" data-end="369">magnetic vulnerability</strong> of past singles like <em data-start="391" data-end="401">The Wolf</em>, <em data-start="403" data-end="429">You Could Break My Heart</em>, and <em data-start="435" data-end="449">Sleeptalking</em>, <strong data-start="451" data-end="467">“Turtleneck”</strong> immerses listeners in Maddie’s signature <strong data-start="509" data-end="535">dreamy indie-pop world</strong>. Guided by her crystalline vocals, the track weaves a delicate tapestry of <strong data-start="611" data-end="661">shimmering melodies and introspective lyricism</strong>, effortlessly blending <strong data-start="685" data-end="720">whimsy with raw emotional depth</strong>.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="327" data-end="723"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/0Yo2uQgPAi9zlvBuUEttny?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="" data-start="725" data-end="1165">At its heart, <strong data-start="739" data-end="755">“Turtleneck”</strong> explores the <strong data-start="769" data-end="808">disorienting aftermath of a breakup</strong>, where the past feels safer than the present. “It’s about how lost you can feel after leaving a relationship,” Maddie shares. “There’s a temptation to anchor yourself in memories rather than face reality.” The song’s ethereal yet melancholic soundscape perfectly embodies this push and pull, capturing the emotional limbo between <strong data-start="1139" data-end="1162">heartbreak and hope</strong>.</p>
<p class="" data-start="1167" data-end="1532">Originally from Toronto and now based in <strong data-start="1208" data-end="1225">New York City</strong>, Maddie discovered songwriting at just 12 years old, using music as an emotional outlet to navigate her anxieties. Since her debut in 2021, she has released two critically praised EPs, <em data-start="1411" data-end="1424">MISS REGENT</em> and <em data-start="1429" data-end="1450">Girl of Your Dreams</em>, earning recognition from tastemakers like <strong data-start="1494" data-end="1513">Atwood Magazine</strong> and <strong data-start="1518" data-end="1529">EARMILK</strong>.</p>
<p class="" data-start="1534" data-end="1849">With longtime collaborator <strong data-start="1561" data-end="1575">Cade Hoppe</strong>—her partner in both music and life—Maddie has carefully crafted a sound that fuses <strong data-start="1659" data-end="1713">catchy pop hooks with deeply personal storytelling</strong>. Now, with <em data-start="1725" data-end="1751">On the phone with my mom</em>, her most ambitious project to date, <strong data-start="1789" data-end="1848">Maddie Regent is poised for a breakthrough year in 2025</strong>.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sunsetto Unveils His Debut Album: The Sun, The Moon &amp; The Big Machine</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/sunsetto-unveils-his-debut-album-the-sun-the-moon-and-the-big-machine/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/sunsetto-unveils-his-debut-album-the-sun-the-moon-and-the-big-machine/</id>

        <updated>2025-02-04T22:07:32+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/23/Untitled-design-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    Toronto’s rising alt-pop sensation sunsetto has arrived with his highly anticipated debut album, The Sun, The Moon &amp; The Big&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/23/Untitled-design-1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Toronto’s rising alt-pop sensation sunsetto has arrived with his highly anticipated debut album, <em>The Sun, The Moon &amp; The Big Machine.</em> This bold and evocative project fuses introspective lyricism with expansive production, drawing listeners into a cinematic exploration of love, ambition, and the complexities of the digital era.</p>
<p>Far more than just a collection of tracks, the album weaves a conceptual narrative around three powerful forces—warmth, passion, and the pursuit of seemingly unattainable dreams. “I wanted to tell a story through my experiences, balancing the push and pull of chasing ambitions while still yearning for something real,” sunsetto explains. “In a world where we consume so much daily, it’s easy to overlook the beauty in the present moment. This album is my attempt to capture those fleeting, often neglected emotions.”</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/5qFHOhuR64kspZz2x05LHv?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p>Recorded between Los Angeles and Toronto over the past year, sunsetto’s journey to this milestone has been met with growing acclaim. His recent singles have resonated deeply with a new generation of pop fans, his poignant storytelling and genre-blurring sound marking him as an artist to watch.</p>
<p>Among the standout tracks is <em>CROSSFIRE</em>, a poignant anthem co-written and produced by 9AM (Leon Bridges, Noah Cyrus). With haunting melodies and raw lyricism, the song encapsulates sunsetto’s signature style. “It’s about lost potential and the choices that define us,” he shares. “That feeling of being caught between dreams and reality is something I’ve lived, and I wanted to bring that honesty into my music.”</p>
<p>Blending emotional depth with sonic innovation, sunsetto is carving a distinct lane in the alt-pop space. With <em>The Sun, The Moon &amp; The Big Machine</em>, he invites listeners on an intimate journey through his world—one where every lyric, beat, and melody tells a story of passion, struggle, and self-discovery.</p>
<p>Stream <em>The Sun, The Moon &amp; The Big Machine</em> now:<br><a href="https://sunsetto.lnk.to/SMBM" disabled="disabled">https://sunsetto.lnk.to/SMBM</a></p>
<div><hr></div>
<h3><strong>Meet sunsetto: The Genre-Defying Artist Behind the Music</strong></h3>
<p>Few artists capture the spirit of their generation like Toronto-based singer, songwriter, and producer sunsetto (Kyle Mischiek). Raised on Cape Breton Island, Nova Scotia, he split his time between music and skateboarding, forging a creative path that would shape his sound. Initially dabbling in rap and beat-making during high school, he refined his craft at prestigious songwriting camps led by GRAMMY® and JUNO Award-winning songwriter Gordie Sampson (Carrie Underwood, Keith Urban).</p>
<p>His breakout moment came in 2020 with the viral success of his debut single <em>don’t leave</em>, amassing hundreds of thousands of streams and catching the attention of tastemakers like EARMILK and Fashionably Early. His distinctive fusion of dance, rap, R&amp;B, and modern country—paired with lyrics that oscillate between euphoria and deep introspection—has solidified his place in the alt-pop landscape.</p>
<p>This year’s string of releases, including <em>PLANS</em>, <em>POTENTIAL</em>, <em>GREEN TEXTS</em>, <em>DON’T LEAVE ME BEHIND</em> (feat. Sinéad Harnett), <em>BIG MACHINE</em>, and <em>SHE’S THE WHOLE WORLD</em>, showcases his evolving artistry and connection to a new wave of pop listeners. Now, with <em>The Sun, The Moon &amp; The Big Machine</em>, sunsetto embarks on his most ambitious chapter yet—one that cements his status as a force to be reckoned with in modern music.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>VANARIN’s Mesmerizing New Release: A Taste of Their Upcoming Third Album</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/new-music-by-vanarin/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/new-music-by-vanarin/</id>

        <updated>2025-01-07T01:21:42+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/20/Untitled-design.jpg" alt="" />
                    As anticipation builds for VANARIN’s highly awaited third album under the Dischi Sotterranei label, the British-Italian band continues to make&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/20/Untitled-design.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>As anticipation builds for VANARIN’s highly awaited third album under the Dischi Sotterranei label, the British-Italian band continues to make waves across the music world. Already earning accolades and securing their spot among the most compelling acts of the moment, VANARIN’s recent feature on the prestigious BBC platforms has solidified their rising-star status. Now, to ease the wait for their next big release, the band is gifting fans with a new single “What We Said”.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="100%" height="352" style="border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/6j2186lsxzwtnEEeDA76tm?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br>This latest track is a mesmerizing psych ballad, anchored by an entrancing piano progression that takes center stage. Layered atop is the frontman’s hypnotic voice, which weaves a spellbinding rhythm, undulating and intoxicating as it explores the haunting aftermath of a love lost. Like a mantra, the lyrics obsessively question the meaning behind a lover’s parting words, plunging the listener into a dreamy yet poignant introspection.</p>
<p class="align-center"><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.ibb.co/WgkyQB1/VANARIN-Artwork-Credit-by-Rebeca-Margescu.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="VANARIN-Artwork-Credit-by-Rebeca-Margescu" border="0"></p>
<p><br><br>Fans of Tame Impala’s Currents will feel the familiar pull of melancholic yet circular lyrics, while those who appreciate The Beatles’ experimental era will be drawn to the artful manipulation and pitch-shifted vocal sections. But that’s not all—the track’s lush sonic landscape is further enriched by a warm, soulful bass line and vintage-inspired guitar phrases that seem to echo straight out of the 1960s.<br><br>What truly sets VANARIN apart is their meticulous attention to detail. Every element of “What We Said” unfolds with a fresh, unexpected twist, creating a soundscape that feels innovative yet timeless. It’s this masterful balance that makes their signature style unmistakable and keeps their audience coming back for more.<br><br>With such a tantalizing preview, VANARIN’s third album promises to be a standout moment in contemporary music—one that fans and critics alike will be eager to experience.</p>
<p> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Twinnie’s Bold New Era: The Country-Pop Starlet Unleashes “Hypothetically”</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/twinnies-bold-new-era-the-country-pop-starlet-unleashes-hypothetically/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/twinnies-bold-new-era-the-country-pop-starlet-unleashes-hypothetically/</id>

        <updated>2024-10-22T21:41:13+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/17/unnamed.png" alt="" />
                    Twinnie has just released the bouncy music video to her latest single, "Hypothetically," which made its world premiere in an&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/17/unnamed.png" alt="" />
                <p>Twinnie has just released the bouncy music video to her latest single, "Hypothetically," which made its world premiere in an exclusive at Daily Mail. The music video stars the talented Twinnie in a striking leopard-print romper capture precisely the playfulness and fearlessness of the song. She's a commanding presence-think a world where this songstress is drawing in viewers "into her world of flirtatious fun," according to Daily Mail.<br><br>"Hypothetically" arrived September 20, 2024, and has already garnered rave reviews. As best put by Nashville Socialite, it's an "absolute knockout" of fresh country-pop peppered with a healthy dose of 90s girl-power nostalgia. Twinnie's carefree yet reflective lyrics meander through love, possibilities, and the unspoken "what-ifs," while channeling her trademark warmth and confidence-a mix of strengths and vulnerabilities not unlike those embodied by none other than Shania Twain herself. Meanwhile, Music City Melodies drew the parallel between it and Jessie James Decker by mentioning that Twinnie's flirtatious lyrics are a reflection of Decker's bold style-an inspiring quality urging everybody to be brazen.<br>like</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RzMCKsLznr4?si=Ub3zuFzIURPpt1xJ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p>This single marks a new turn for Twinnie, where she leaves her "sad-girl" phase for a more fun and confident sound. Co-written with Reid Sorel and Grace Gunn, "Hypothetically" teases themes from her forthcoming sophomore album, Something We Used To Say, due out on November 8, 2024.<br><br>Off the back of her new album, Twinnie has announced a small, intimate tour of the UK this November, stopping off in London, Brighton, Manchester, York and Glasgow. Her Manchester show has already sold out.</p>
<p><br>Last year, Twinnie joined the cast of Emmerdale to play Jade, the mean boxing promoter. On her latest role, Twinnie says: "Life has been crazy juggling acting and music, with lots of back and forth between Nashville and Yorkshire, but I'm loving every second of it!<br><br>No stranger to acting, Twinnie has a history on British television with roles in the shows Doctors and Hollyoaks, where she received much acclaim for her portrayal of Porsche McQueen, whose storyline tackled critical social issues like childhood sexual abuse.<br><br>Twinnie became the first British artist to sing the American National Anthem at the stadium of Nashville SC, GEODIS Park, stamping her credentials as a global star with an infectious dynamism.<br><br>Twinnie's life story has been very far from ordinary. At her tender age, she had acted among giants like Glenn Close and Robin Thicke while her West End performances in Chicago and Rock of Ages hinted at the shining star she was to become. Since the launch of her solo career in 2020, she consistently blew minds with her genre-defying sound and continues to inspire, recently performing at AmericanaFest's "Stella + Friends: The Power of Women in Music."</p>
<p>Hypothetically" is only the beginning of her exciting new chapter.<br><br></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Online Magazine Issue #1</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/online-magazine-issue-1/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/online-magazine-issue-1/</id>

        <updated>2024-07-11T00:32:34+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/16/new-issue-1.png" alt="" />
                    We are so excited to share with you the first issue of the online Volecho magazine! You can download below&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/16/new-issue-1.png" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">We are so excited to share with you the first issue of the online Volecho magazine! You can download below and support us!</p>
<h2 class="align-center"><a href="https://www.patreon.com/volechomag/shop/volecho-online-magazine-1-265296?utm_medium=clipboard_copy&amp;utm_source=copyLink&amp;utm_campaign=productshare_fan&amp;utm_content=join_link" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Volecho Issue #1</a></h2>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>CHIEF STATE Releasing 5-song acoustic EP on April 5</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/chief-state-releasing-5-song-acoustic-ep-on-april-5/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/chief-state-releasing-5-song-acoustic-ep-on-april-5/</id>
            <category term="Music"/>

        <updated>2024-02-17T21:10:15+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/15/chief-state.jpg" alt="" />
                    Vancouver, BC pop punk trailblazers, Chief State, unveil their latest release - a 5-song acoustic EP that promises to redefine your&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/15/chief-state.jpg" alt="" />
                <p align="left">Vancouver, BC pop punk trailblazers, <strong>Chief State</strong>, unveil their latest release - a 5-song acoustic EP that promises to redefine your connection with their music. Set to release via <strong>Mutant League Records</strong> in April 2024, <strong>"The Acoustic EP"</strong> invites listeners to rediscover Chief State's catalog through a captivating and intimate lens.</p>
<p align="left">The first single "Living Out A Lie" will be released on February 21.</p>
<p align="center"><strong>Pre-save 'The Acoustic EP' here:</strong> <a href="https://email.cloud.secureclick.net/c/6813?id=22149820.58045.1.fd3f4a097b6d39b5765a202c5ef4168e" target="_blank" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://email.cloud.secureclick.net/c/6813?id%3D22149820.58045.1.fd3f4a097b6d39b5765a202c5ef4168e&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1708280673119000&amp;usg=AOvVaw1cp-qZTTAner-sUt87zZBq" rel="noopener">https://orcd.co/chiefstate</a></p>
<p align="left">Of the EP's first single and video, "Living Out A Lie", front man <strong>Fraser Simpson</strong> says, <em>"As the name suggests, this song is about the feeling of your life being a lie, self-doubt, faking it until you make it, imposter syndrome. Something I constantly struggle with. I’ve made a lot of choices to get where I am today and often I’m not sure if I’m actually being true to myself. The song also speaks directly about doubt in previous relationships, whether my heart was actually in it. The video, created by the brilliant Lindsey Blane, really tied this idea together and we deliberately ended it before knowing the answer to the guy’s proposal. I think we’re all a little glossy on the surface, we show what we want to show but once it comes down to a life changing choice, like shown in the video, the truth will come out."</em></p>
<p align="left">In honor of Valentine's Day, Chief State and Mutant League Records have launched a limited edition "Valentines Day" shirt design, available exclusively through the Mutant League <a href="https://email.cloud.secureclick.net/c/6813?id=22149820.58046.1.ecfcdb1534ee1c836307b7ea8daa6c6d" target="_blank" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://email.cloud.secureclick.net/c/6813?id%3D22149820.58046.1.ecfcdb1534ee1c836307b7ea8daa6c6d&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1708280673119000&amp;usg=AOvVaw0AOtc6H_AlFxh_C1NKHgxj" rel="noopener"><strong>webstore</strong></a>.</p>
<p align="left">All V-day shirt purchases through April 5th will receive a handwritten lyric by Fraser Simpson of Chief State, along with a song from the upcoming EP.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
