<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>volecho.com</title>
    <link href="https://volecho.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://volecho.com" />
    <updated>2026-02-02T23:16:25+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Volecho.com</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://volecho.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Oaken Wires Leave Their Mark with Footprints</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/oaken-wires-leave-their-mark-with-footprints/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/oaken-wires-leave-their-mark-with-footprints/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-02T23:16:25+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/138/volecho-music-magazine-66.jpg" alt="" />
                    There’s a certain intimacy found with a song that seems like it&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/138/volecho-music-magazine-66.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">There’s a certain intimacy found with a song that seems like it was born out of casual experiment rather than hard work and dedication, and this is precisely what the song Footprints by Oaken Wires has managed to pull off. Born out of an old track on Jake Oaken Lee’s laptop, a track that had been sitting around for a long time, the song was sent over to Tim from CutWires, and what the pair managed to come up with was a track that was not exactly folk and not exactly electronic, but a wonderful amalgamation of the two, full of life and energy.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/4cnNVm276YX9Dh89waOm3J?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><br><br>The song itself has a certain level of weightiness without being too heavy. At its heart, the song is about sticking together through the hard times, about seeing the end but still holding on, and the delicate art of passing the baton on into the next chapter of life. The emotions are immediate and felt, with a certain warmth and openness found with Jake’s vocals, paired with the occasional waves of electricity found with the instrumentation from Tim. It’s a wonderful balance between being uplifting and being sad at the same time, a balance found with few songs today in the world of alt-pop.<br><br>Stylistically speaking, Oaken Wires place themselves in a world in which alternative pop, electronic music, and folk rock meet. You can clearly hear the influence of Primal Scream’s early days of experimentation with rock music, Bon Iver’s folk-pop sensibilities, and the Beta Band’s or Alt-J’s experimental approach to music. You can also clearly hear the influence of Youth Lagoon in the way in which Oaken Wires approach the world of electronic music not as a gimmick but as a means of expressing the emotional content of the song’s narrative.<br><br>It is also worth noting that Footprints marks the beginning of Oaken Wires as a musical entity. After Tim’s remix of Jake’s song “Reach Out” in the summer of 2025, the two musicians quickly came to realize that the potential of the collaboration between the two was much greater than simply a remix of one song. Oaken Wires is based in Tottenham, North London, and this urban sensibility is what makes Footprints such a compelling piece of music, grounding the ethereal qualities of the song in the textured qualities of the musicianship.<br><br>If this song is your cup of tea, then fans of The National’s melodic but subdued approach to music, Bon Iver’s folk-electronica sound, or Alt-J’s playful approach to music production will find much to love here. Footprints also has a cinematic quality to it similar to some of the less intense moments of movies such as Manchester by the Sea or Garden State in which the story is not necessarily advanced but the emotional subtext of the scene is what really makes the movie come alive. When you listen to this song, it’s almost like a series of scenes playing out before your very eyes.<br><br>With their song "Footprints," the Oaken Wires demonstrate that collaboration can lead to something akin to alchemy. The song, which began life as a dormant recording, has become a song of connection, transition, and emotional depth. There is a promise here, the debut of a new project with a willingness to explore the edges of sound while maintaining the importance of the human voice. For those who have followed the journey of the modern alt-pop or experimental folk rock sounds, the Oaken Wires are a duo to watch, a duo that has the ability to take the familiar and make it not only alive and relevant, but necessary. "Footprints" is available on all major platforms and is a confident introduction to the ongoing story of the Oaken Wires.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top Releases 2-2-26</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/top-releases-2-2-26/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/top-releases-2-2-26/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-02T22:56:48+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/137/Top-Tracks-2xl.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/7M6gHTw7vTSG5wpJiprvjr?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/6E6xjuibAQnsrlA1jRnO5q?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/4YS4PxSjCFDoRGGbsmTR0W?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/3LX0KsjaK8Qtkc2eMHZUKd?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1Tis3dJsOeKNGDcdf0E9CH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1Gdda2svzKz43K21QwDxWu?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Grey &amp; Purple Songbook and the price tag on freedom</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/grey-and-purple-songbook-and-the-price-tag-on-freedom/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/grey-and-purple-songbook-and-the-price-tag-on-freedom/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-02T22:33:11+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Grey &amp; Purple Songbook have never seemed interested in offering easy answers,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Grey &amp; Purple Songbook have never seemed interested in offering easy answers, and their January 16, 2026, release *Ten to Fifteen Million*’s “All I Need” certainly proves that point within the first few lines of the song. This is not a song that is chasing hooks for their own sake or a slogan masquerading as a work of art. This is a conversation, a gentle one, about money, freedom, and the odd bargain we all make without ever signing a contract or a dotted line. Grey &amp; Purple Songbook is an Oslo, Norway-based outfit that doesn’t really seem to work like a band in any conventional sense of the word. Instead, it’s a long-form writing project that just happens to exist within a musical context. This is an outfit that relies heavily on text and storytelling, in which lyrics do all of the heavy lifting and melodies serve only to provide a context for them to exist in. “All I Need” from *Ten to Fifteen Million* certainly feels like it’s in that world, in which a gentle pace and a quiet demeanor serve to make a point about the world in which we find ourselves. The title of the song is certainly a pointed one, one that feels ridiculous and even a little funny until it’s slowly explained in the course of the song. In a world in which we prize our individuality and our freedom above all else, it’s a price tag that continues to climb higher and higher. There’s no rant, no big speech, just a gentle circling of the point to be made, one in which the figures are allowed to hang in the air for a moment and in which we can come to terms with just how unremarkable it is to consider a price tag of millions for our individuality.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/2wTCbCBkp5ToOLiFiRhS85?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br><br>Musically, the track is equally understated. The production leaves space for the lyrics to breathe, preferring mood to muscle. There’s a relaxed confidence to the track, a sense that the listener will follow along. It’s a hallmark of the Grey &amp; Purple Songbook that a song about ideas needs no clutter. It’s an intimate sound, almost like listening to someone talk to themselves late at night, when the din of the day finally fades away.<br><br>What makes this song work is that it refuses to simplify the issue. It does not pretend that money is not an issue, nor does it pretend that freedom exists outside of a system. Instead, it finds a middle ground that most people live in. The desire to be free, to be independent, countered with the knowledge of how dependent everything is on money. The belief in choice, countered with the knowledge of how few choices really exist. It’s a song about democracy without taking a side.<br><br>Grey &amp; Purple Songbook have built a name on this kind of writing, where emotion and thought are woven together. Their discography reads like a collection of short stories, each one using sound as a way to slow the reader down. There are similarities here with other artists who use their songs as literature, from the latter days of Leonard Cohen’s albums to the quiet parts of Nick Cave’s discography, where the questions are more important than the answers. There are also similarities with the Nordic minimalism and the cool clarity of Scandinavian cinema. There are films like Oslo, August 31st, or parts of Roy Andersson’s films, where the quiet weight of life is a powerful force.<br><br>Ten to Fifteen Million’s All I Need also fits comfortably in a recent tradition of releases that are more concerned with interrogating success and worth than celebrating them. Think of records that ponder what is left when success is no longer an option, or when the finish line keeps moving. This is a song that doesn’t offer solace, but it does offer truth, and that is becoming a rare thing indeed.<br><br>There is something rather wonderful about the way that Grey &amp; Purple Songbook resists the temptation to dress up the message of the album. It is a production that stays focused. It is a vocal performance that stays grounded. There is no reaching for drama that has not been earned. It is an album made by people who are comfortable enough in their ideas to allow them to speak for themselves alone.<br><br>In an era where so much of the music we are given is designed to be scrolled past quickly, Ten to Fifteen Million’s All I Need asks for your attention, but it asks for it as a favor rather than a command. It asks you to engage with it, to think about it, to let it disturb you a little. Grey &amp; Purple Songbook reminds us that songs are capable of being more than a way of distracting ourselves from the world. <br><br>It is not an album that sets out to change the world in three minutes. It is an album that asks a better question, and then leaves you alone with it. Sometimes, that is the more effective thing to do.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>When love speaks softly, Circanium listens</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/when-love-speaks-softly-circanium-listens/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/when-love-speaks-softly-circanium-listens/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-02T22:23:30+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/135/volecho-music-magazine-62.jpg" alt="" />
                    “Ballade de l’anamour” arrives like a quiet confession passed across a small&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/135/volecho-music-magazine-62.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>“Ballade de l’anamour” arrives like a quiet confession passed across a small table on a late night, when the world has settled and all that’s left are the things that matter. It’s a French song, a true French song, not because it emulates the style of the past, but because it understands the value of the past. Two voices, a guitar, a trumpet, and nothing else. Circanium knows the value of restraint over volume.<br><br>The song is deeply romantic, unapologetically so, without ever being sweet. There’s a level of melancholy here, the kind that sits lightly on the shoulder rather than weighing heavily on the heart. The guitar sets the tone, warm and intimate, and the trumpet runs the course of the song like a second narrator. It’s almost like the instruments are answering the voices rather than playing with them.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/7Dq1mAcjTOu2Gq8a6IP0N8?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br>Circanium’s influences are evident, but never obvious. The Brassens influence can be seen in the use and care given to the words. Piaf can be felt in the commitment to the emotions, the feeling that the words are personally meaningful. Goldman can be heard in the clarity of the melody, and the influences of Les Ogres de Barback and Debout sur le zinc can be felt throughout the human scale and the communal feel. There’s a strong jazz feel here, the timing and the trumpet playing are jazzy, the breathing and expanding and contracting without losing the center.<br><br>What gives *Ballade de l’anamour* its unique tone is the band’s connection to performance and circus arts. It’s present in the rhythm. It’s music that’s connected to stages, to bodies moving through space, to moments that require attention rather than spectacle. It’s a song that feels like a small theatrical piece or like a late scene from a French film where dialogue gives way to music because words are no longer enough. <br><br>The dual vocals are also important. They don’t fight each other or complement each other too well. They have a subtle tension that feels like two inner worlds brushing up against each other. They blend together and then drift apart, which feels like an extension of the idea of love as both shared and singular. It feels like something from French chanson history, but also something from more modern French music, like moments from artists like Pomme and Clara Yse, where there’s a quiet intimacy to the work. <br><br>The production work on the song is simple and for a reason. Every element feels like it’s there for a purpose. The trumpet does not outstay its welcome. The guitar does not embellish. It gives space for the words to land, even if you don’t fully understand them. Emotions can be just as powerful as words here.<br><br>Ballade de l'anamour is part of a tradition of music that prioritizes presence over production sheen. If you're a fan of music that sounds designed to be consumed in a single sitting, with the lights turned low, then this will likely be up your alley. If you're a fan of movies such as "Les Parapluies de Cherbourg" or the quieter scenes from "Le Fabuleux Destin d'Amélie Poulain," you'll know this feeling right away.<br><br>You can feel that nothing is theoretical with Circanium’s music. It is all experience-based. And that is why the song seems to linger after it is over. It is not a song that tries to craft a hook that will stay with you after it is over. It is a song that settles in a different way, a way that is closer to memory.<br><br>In a world filled with music that is built for speed and distraction, Ballade de l’anamour is a song that asks you to take a different pace. It asks you to pay attention, to remember that romance is a delicate and poetic concept that is often unresolved. Circanium understands this is a rare and precious space and approaches it with a sense of respect.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ferdinand Rennie and the art of the big, honest ballad</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/ferdinand-rennie-and-the-art-of-the-big-honest-ballad/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/ferdinand-rennie-and-the-art-of-the-big-honest-ballad/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-02T22:19:30+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/134/volecho-music-magazine-61.jpg" alt="" />
                    Some songs are quiet and unassuming. Others are bombastic and attention-grabbing. Then&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/134/volecho-music-magazine-61.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">Some songs are quiet and unassuming. Others are bombastic and attention-grabbing. Then there are those that are just plain meant to be. Unbelieving Eyes is most certainly in the last category. Produced and co-produced by Ferdinand Rennie and Alan Vukelic and Nate Kohrs, this is less of a single and more of an event. It is as if this song has been waiting in the wings for Rennie and he has finally come along. Written by Sharon Vaughn, Niklas Edberger, Jeff Franzel, Alan Vukelic, and Ferdinand Rennie himself, Unbelieving Eyes is a true ballad in the way that word should be used. It is full of trust and trust in the right things. The melody is strong and true. The production is tight from the first notes. It gives Rennie room to roam and builds towards a full and sweeping chorus without ever getting too out of hand. This is pop balladry at its best, and it is more in line with late-era Leonard Cohen or the emotional honesty of Sarah McLachlan than it is with anything remotely mainstream. The voice of Ferdinand Rennie is strong and true. Years of stage and studio time have honed him into an instrument of pure craft. There is an authority here, yes, but there is also an honesty. He sings Unbelieving Eyes as if he has learned patience and restraint. Nothing is ever forced. Nothing is ever extraneous.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/4gOOkcZLus7LUBxX3vprlH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div><br><br>This background explains much. Born and raised in Austria and now living on the west coast of Scotland, he has spent over thirty years moving between worlds. His work encompasses television, theatre, and studio recordings. From appearances related to Eurovision and Austrian television to starring roles in major musical productions such as Les Miserables, Elisabeth, Jesus Christ Superstar, Beauty and the Beast, and Little Shop of Horrors, he has spent his life immersed in music that requires technical skill and emotional depth. All of this informs how he works through a recording like Unbelieving Eyes. He understands when to act and when to remain motionless and let the song shine through. There’s something cinematic about Unbelieving Eyes. It’s reminiscent of the closing scenes from some romantic epics, where time seems to pass a little longer than expected. One might think of something like The English Patient or A Star Is Born. Unbelieving Eyes would be at home during the end credits, not as background but as punctuation. While there’s not much to say about Unbelieving Eyes, there’s much to be known about Rennie himself. His versions of songs like Run, Hallelujah, Angel, and Never Enough have earned him radio play all over the world because he performs them with a level of respect rather than reinvention. His work on Chase the Sun, performed with Grammy winner Mikal Blue, or productions like A Wing and a Prayer, Someone to Remember Me, and It’s Time, all have one thing in common: clarity of feeling. His hit Christmas tune Together at Christmas also had that same level of sincerity.<br><br>Unbelieving Eyes feels like the culmination of a journey rather than a step away from it. It has the heart and soul of a theatre track but never strays far from the pop production. The production never overpowers the lyrics. It’s a difficult balance to achieve, and it’s here that the co-production shines.<br><br>There’s also something rather wonderful about the unapologetic sincerity of the track. It’s a world where irony has become a defence mechanism, and Rennie has no hesitation in being sincere. The title itself speaks of a disbelief not just with love but with grace. It’s a theme that resonates with anyone who has been around long enough to know that certainty is a rare commodity.<br><br>For the listener who likes the likes of Josh Groban, Michael Ball, and even the more subdued moments of Sam Smith, this track will feel like home. It’s a track that sits comfortably alongside the ballads from either artist. It’s also a track that reminds the listener that, despite the current state of music, there’s still room for songs that take their time.<br><br>Unbelieving Eyes doesn’t have to be revolutionary. It doesn’t have to be groundbreaking. It doesn’t have to be. It has the strength and the heart and soul of the writing, the delivery, and the trust between everyone involved. It’s a track from Ferdinand Rennie that feels like a statement of intent. It’s a man comfortable with himself and the world around him and a man deeply connected with the material. It’s a track for the listener that’s a rare find. It’s a track that demands stillness and rewards it fully.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A second life in technicolor, Luna and the Gents bring vintage pop back to play</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/a-second-life-in-technicolor-luna-and-the-gents-bring-vintage-pop-back-to-play/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/a-second-life-in-technicolor-luna-and-the-gents-bring-vintage-pop-back-to-play/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-02T22:09:41+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/133/volecho-music-magazine-60.jpg" alt="" />
                    There’s something rather brave about a band that chooses joy rather than&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/133/volecho-music-magazine-60.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>There’s something rather brave about a band that chooses joy rather than irony. Luna and The Gents don’t use vintage music as a costume or a clever trick. With *On Second Life (Part I)*, they tackle swing, jazz, rockabilly, and old pop from the 1940s and onward with genuine affection. The result is an EP that’s light on its feet and well-crafted, with a lot of well-written songs that smile rather than wink too hard. *Second Life (Part I)*, released January 23, 2026, brings together five previously released singles and a longer version of chanson “Je Ne Peux Pas T’Oublier” that serves as both a centerpiece and a quiet emotional anchor. Over six tracks, the Basel-based project produces a sound that references mid-century pop but never sounds stuck there. The grooves are great for dancing to, and the melodies are simple and accessible. The arrangements are generous to all the instruments, and nothing feels cluttered. Nothing feels like it overstays its welcome. Frontwoman Luna, whose real name is Evelyne Pequignot, carries all these tracks off with an ease that never veers off into theatrics. Her voice is light but grounded, playful but not flimsy. She knows how to work a lyric, when to emphasize and when to let it float past. That’s what keeps all this from veering off into parody. Even at its most upbeat, there’s a steady hand at work.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/66jaxHnEqGI4t5I9naC915?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br><br>The EP kicks off with a strong sense of energy and charm, reminiscent of early post-war pop music designed to lift the spirits without losing sight of the importance of feeling. The rhythms swing gently instead of hitting home with a harder edge. The guitars shimmer instead of shouting their presence. There’s a touch of country woven into the edges, subtle enough to be felt instead of heard. It’s music designed for movement, but also for close listening.<br><br>What makes Second Life (Part I) stand out is the level of care taken with the visual side of things. Each track has an official music video, creating a sense of a cohesive set that expands upon the stories hinted at through the music. The main video, Doggy, is perhaps the best representation of the EP’s overall feeling. It has a playful, vintage look to it, designed to be old-fashioned without feeling over-styled. The visuals don’t compete with the music; they’re an extension of it, allowing the listener to get inside the band’s world another way.<br><br>It’s a sense of music that feels part of a wider creative space, not a file on a music streaming service. There’s a touch of Postmodern Jukebox’s love of old forms, but without the cover versions and novelty element. There’s a sense of Caro Emerald’s early work, perhaps, or the lighter side of French pop chanson given a new lease of life for the modern home. There’s a sense of films such as Amélie or The Artist, with their love of texture, color, and gentle humor.<br><br>Je Ne Peux Pas T Oublier is worth a special mention here. Its longer form has slowed down the rhythm and given way to emotion. The French lyrics add a softness that works well against the more upbeat tracks of this EP. The arrangement remains low-key, letting the tune and vocals shine through. It’s a reminder that beneath all this swing and happiness, there is a recognition of longing too.<br><br>Second Life (Part I) also has the benefit of its format. It has six tracks, which is enough to feel like a complete piece without being overwhelming. It is like listening to a short film, rather than a series, and it is one you can easily go back to without much trouble. The fact that it is both digital and physical, on CD, is also important for people who like to hold their music, read the covers, and enjoy an album from start to finish.<br><br>Luna and The Gents are a virtual band, releasing their work solely on the internet, but it is not hard to imagine the music being enjoyed in a physical space. You can easily imagine it filling a dance floor, playing in a café on a lazy afternoon, or wafting from an open window on a pleasant summer night. They are not trying to be loud or dominant, just providing a certain atmosphere, a certain groove, and a certain level of fun without ever talking down to the listener.<br><br>In a world where music is often divided between polish and raw, Second Life (Part I) has managed to carve its own path, one based on charm and skill. It is a reminder that pop music can be fun without being empty, or nostalgic without being irrelevant. For people who want pop, want melody, want rhythm, and want a certain level of old-world charm without losing the modern touch, Luna and The Gents have created something worth spending time on.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>OGGY Finds Light in Motion on Help Me Find a Reason</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/oggy-finds-light-in-motion-on-help-me-find-a-reason/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/oggy-finds-light-in-motion-on-help-me-find-a-reason/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-29T00:18:42+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/132/volecho-music-magazine-59.jpg" alt="" />
                    London-based OGGY enters 2026 with the release of “Help Me Find a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/132/volecho-music-magazine-59.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>London-based OGGY enters 2026 with the release of “Help Me Find a Reason,” a pop-rock indie track that feels like it was made for the open road, the late night drive home, and the moment when uncertainty becomes determination. The song was written by OGGY alone, starting as a simple acoustic piece and evolving into something more complete and enlightened. The end result is a song that has a sense of forward motion, with the guitars driving forward while the melody stays firmly planted.<br><br>The strength of the song lies in its sense of purpose. OGGY writes from the heart, but the heart is open. The song deals with the importance of faith, not necessarily in anything or anyone, but in the idea of forward motion. OGGY’s vocals are strong and warm, the result of years of training and live performances throughout the city of London.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="750" height="422" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2ExJW9EiQ8E" title="OGGY - Help Me Find a Reason (Official lyrics video)" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p>Fans of Florence Welch from her earlier days, Avril Lavigne from her more introspective periods, or the latest pop-rock indie releases will find a lot to love here. There is also a sense of cinematic wonder, as if the closing scene from a coming-of-age film where the protagonist steps out into the world.<br><br>“Help Me Find a Reason” is a great introduction to OGGY’s upcoming EP, a sense of tone that is based firmly in optimism and determination. It is a sense of an artist who is comfortable with her own growth and ready to take the world by storm.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>LUNA and The Gents Step Into a Stylish Loop With SECOND LIFE (PART I)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/luna-and-the-gents-step-into-a-stylish-loop-with-second-life-part-i/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/luna-and-the-gents-step-into-a-stylish-loop-with-second-life-part-i/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-28T23:59:33+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/131/volecho-music-magazine-58.jpg" alt="" />
                    LUNA and The Gents start 2026 off right by embracing their own&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/131/volecho-music-magazine-58.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>LUNA and The Gents start 2026 off right by embracing their own universe fully. SECOND LIFE (PART I) doesn’t feel so much like an EP from a new band as it does a calling card, a collection of five familiar singles by a band with a sense of purpose, and an extended version of Je Ne Peux Pas T’Oublier that gives the project an emotional core. The band, from Basel but functioning as a virtual band, plays with the concept of time itself, blending swing, chanson, and old pop styles and updating them for a modern day.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/66jaxHnEqGI4t5I9naC915?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br><br>The songs blend from carefree grooves to quieter moments of reflection. There’s humor here, but it’s never wasted on a throwaway moment. A wink and a sweet moment are often side by side, and it’s this contrast that makes the music so appealing. Evelyne Pequignot’s vocals have a warmth and a sense of conversation, supported by guitars, keyboards, bass, and drums that focus on feel over showmanship. The production is clean and lets the music breathe, like an old studio session rather than a current playlist.<br><br>What makes this EP stand out from others is the connection between the music and the videos that each song comes with. There’s a loose narrative thread through the videos, a series of vignettes that evoke old European cinema, the kind of Jacques Demy color and romance of old, or the playfulness of old Godard, but through a modern lens. Fans of Caro Emerald, Postmodern Jukebox, or even old Zooey Deschanel soundtracks will find a lot to love.<br><br>SECOND LIFE (PART I) sounds like it was made yesterday, but it doesn’t feel dated at all. It’s pop that trusts its own charms and has a sense of skill and melody to back it up, and it makes a compelling case for this being only the first chapter.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top Releases 27-1-2026</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/top-releases-27-1-2026/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/top-releases-27-1-2026/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-27T23:51:11+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/130/Top-Tracks-2xl.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/5whYRazUStZRxwx3Y8F8Zg?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/6E6xjuibAQnsrlA1jRnO5q?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/4YS4PxSjCFDoRGGbsmTR0W?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/3LX0KsjaK8Qtkc2eMHZUKd?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1Tis3dJsOeKNGDcdf0E9CH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1Gdda2svzKz43K21QwDxWu?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top Releases 1-20-26</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/top-releases-1-20-26/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/top-releases-1-20-26/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-20T00:33:43+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/128/Top-Tracks-2xl.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/2GENucEYd4Bw0si3qqsePO?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/7aRY4u0GKgzFA2nLxewgrw?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/4YS4PxSjCFDoRGGbsmTR0W?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/3LX0KsjaK8Qtkc2eMHZUKd?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1Tis3dJsOeKNGDcdf0E9CH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1Gdda2svzKz43K21QwDxWu?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
