<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>volecho.com</title>
    <link href="https://volecho.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://volecho.com" />
    <updated>2025-10-15T00:16:37+03:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Volecho.com</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://volecho.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Mike Shouse&#x27;s Triumphant Return: &quot;Jaded&quot; Revives the Spirit of Instrumental Rock</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/mike-shouses-triumphant-return-jaded-revives-the-spirit-of-instrumental-rock/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/mike-shouses-triumphant-return-jaded-revives-the-spirit-of-instrumental-rock/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:15:36+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/73/volecho-music-magazine-17.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/73/volecho-music-magazine-17.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>A decade and a half is a long time to have been out of sight in the realm of guitar. But when Kentucky bred shredder Mike Shouse finally emerged from hiding, he didn't reappear, he exploded. His new release, Jaded, released through Deko Entertainment, is a sonic boom re-entry that balances on the precipice between technical skill and emotional resonance. It's a living record, grounded in technique but entirely free, and inhabited by some of the most respected figures in guitar lore: Tony MacAlpine, Ron "Bumblefoot" Thal, and Michael Angelo Batio.<br><br>Kentucky native, subsequently schooled at Hollywood's Guitar Institute of Technology, Shouse has been among the most innovative and skilled guitarists of his peer group for years. His previous albums, Enter the Soul (2001) and Alone on the Sun (2010), had also been praised for their unflinching combination of melody and precision, absolute proof that virtuosity and storytelling could go hand in hand. Jaded carries on that tradition, a purely instrumental album that is cinematic and intimate at the same time.<br><br>"This album is a rebirth for me in many ways," Shouse says. There is a feeling of rebirth all the way through all the songs. You catch it in the mournful sting of Romeo Is Gone, the sweaty thrill of Let's Go, and the jaunty swagger of Smiley Faced Emoji. Even the final offering from the album, Upon Looking Back, carries the repressed assurance of an artist who has worked the highs and lows of artistic life and yet still blazes to perform.<br><br>Each visiting guitarist brings his own timbre to Shouse's compositions. Tony MacAlpine's smooth, classically aligned phrasing adds a sense of sophistication. Bumblefoot's erratically shifting tone, bristling with sharp edges and elasticity, sometimes hinting at the brink of mania, keeps the listener on edge. And Batio, the speed master of all time, brings blunt fire to the party, blasting the album's energy into orbit. But be warned: Jaded is Shouse's band from start to finish. The record sounds unified because his performance is the constant, melodic whenever it has to be, explosive whenever it needs to be, and expressive at all times.<br><br>The production, skillfully nurtured by Nashville's Billy Decker, provides the album with its glossy yet organic-sounding production. Drummer Charlie Zeleny (and collaborator with Jordan Rudess and Terry Bozzio) and Impellitteri bassist James Amelio Pulli complete the team, delivering the guitar fireworks with rhythmic weight. The result is an album that walks a fine line between technical proficiency and emotional expression, something that few instrumental albums achieve.<br><br>Hearing Jaded is somewhat akin to opening a time capsule from the height of the guitar hero days, the Surfing with the Alien and Passion and Warfare period, but it's not retro. Rather, it's respectful of that era's heritage and sounds totally of the moment. There's an undertone of sincerity that prevents it from becoming pastiche. Unlike some instrumental rock albums, which sound like showcases for technique, Shouse's playing is narrative, about loss and renewal and thanks.<br><br>Critics elsewhere in the world have already noticed. Iggy Magazine of France has labelled the album "a fresco sound that is both technical and visceral." Music Review World has proclaimed it "a technical wonder and an emotional journey." And Revista Sound Loop of Argentina has stated, "Shouse triumphantly returns with an album that pushes the boundaries of the instrumental and sets a new benchmark for the genre." Such aren't empty encomiums. They’re recognition of an artist who has matured without losing his spark.<br><br>For those who live for the thrill of hearing a guitar really talk, Jaded is the reminder of what six strings can do in capable hands. Joe Satriani, Steve Vai, and Paul Gilbert enthusiasts will be home in a nanosecond, but Shouse's melodic, expressive playing carves out his own niche. The tune Bucket of Bolts (see it here<br>) is the perfect beginning point: all muscular and lighthearted, with a rhythm section enjoying themselves almost as much as the guitarist himself.<br><br>Jaded is not a comeback. It's a statement, that real musicianship does not die, that guitar instrumental rock can still thrill, and that sometimes laying it down is the way to come back more powerful. Shouse has forever been a master craftsman, but this record proves he's a writer, employing tone and phrasing to say what words cannot.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>F</strong><strong>ollow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>RedLight Resurfaces with &#x27;Homeworks,&#x27; a DIY Rock Success</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/redlight-resurfaces-with-homeworks-a-diy-rock-success/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/redlight-resurfaces-with-homeworks-a-diy-rock-success/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:15:42+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/72/volecho-music-magazine-16.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/72/volecho-music-magazine-16.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>Almost two decades in and still struggling to find their own niche in an oversaturated music scene, Marseille rock band RedLight continue to prove their pertinence with their new album, Homeworks. Released March 14, 2025, the album is a testament to the band's DIY spirit as all ten tracks were composed, recorded, and produced in guitarist Dapé's home studio in Le Rove. The outcome is an album that contains raw energy combined with meticulous attention to detail, balancing retro nostalgia and new, forward-looking experimentation.<br><br>RedLight's sound genetic code is an intriguing blend. There are whispers of Pearl Jam's honest guitar-rock, The Beastie Boys' rhythmic experimentation, and The Cure's atmospheric soundscapes, all sounded over a base of dirty melodic sensibility. Homeworks takes its cue from that heritage but has no aspirations to stay there. The addition of Seb on drums adds a new, dynamic flavor to augment the seasoned rhythm section of Dapé, lead vocalist/guitarist Londres, and bassist Guy. The chemistry of the band is well-served here, each player contributing a distinct voice that fits beautifully into the overall sound.<br><br>Tracks such as forthcoming single Idea of Mine will be crowd-pleasers, their anthemic hooks and pounding beats, but it's the eclecticism of the album that most impresses. Some of the tracks descend into introspective, melodic vamps, others blow up with strobe-like hyperactivity redolent of the Strokes' earliest forms or the chant-along factor of the Pixies. RedLight's trick is in finding these poles—acoustic and scorching crescendos—and it's the secret to making Homeworks sound so wired and alive.<br><br>The DIY look of the album is not a mere exercise in image-making; it conditions the listener. There's the impression the band is in each moment of the production, making instinct-sounding decisions rather than ones that sound too polished. It's a way of thinking that brings to mind early Arctic Monkeys or even Beck, when personality and truth may come ahead of the gloss of the studio. Guitar-friendly alternative rock enthusiasts, from The Beatles' more experimental late-period output through the raw intensity of early 2000s garage rock, will find something to cling to here.<br><br>aside from the music, Homeworks is also a work of the new DIY production potential. With each step in the recording process handled in-house, RedLight show that rock music can still be successful away from big-label machinery, making music that is at once intimate and sweeping. On the record, you can feel the hours of refining texture, building up the melody, and grabbing at the moment of accident that gives the record its vitality.<br><br>RedLight have worked their way to respect by avoiding trends while being authentic. Homeworks does not tell listeners to be the same as the band—it opens its arms, providing something both old-school and spontaneous, intelligent and uncooked. It's testament that rock music is still capable of shocking, that DIY groups can still deliver fleshed-out albums without compromise, and that artistic freedom tends to leave the most engaging outcomes.<br><br>For enthusiasts in search of an ear trip that respects the past but engages with the promise of DIY recording, Homeworks is a joyous celebration. RedLight continue to demonstrate that Marseille can produce rock with heart, attitude, and a very distinctive twist.</p>
<p> </p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>F</strong><strong>ollow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bill Barlow Passes the Baton to the Fans with &#x27;By Special Request&#x27;</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/bill-barlow-passes-the-baton-to-the-fans-with-by-special-request/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/bill-barlow-passes-the-baton-to-the-fans-with-by-special-request/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:15:52+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/71/volecho-music-magazine-15.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/71/volecho-music-magazine-15.jpg" alt="" />
                <p> </p>
<p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>Tampa singer-songwriter Bill Barlow has built a reputation over the years as the master of transposing everyday life into song, fully realized and emotionally vivid, and his latest album, By Special Request, sets that mastery in dialogue with the most important parties to the discussion: his fans. Released on October 3, 2025, the album is a carefully curated 18-song collection, each song selected by the listeners themselves. It's an odd choice in a music industry that's artist- or label-driven, and it speaks to Barlow wanting to create music that will resonate as completely with other people as it does with him.<br><br>Throughout the course of the first song, By Special Request makes its stand. Barlow floats between bluesy, introspective tunes along the lines of Emotional Journey and harder, grittier material from The Bill Barlow Project. The result is an album that glides seamlessly back and forth between introspective sentiment and acid, dry narrative. Critics have long praised Barlow's facility for conveying raw emotion, and here it's in high relief. Laugh-out-loud moments come all too quickly often followed by squirming ones, a discomfort Barlow evades with ease, a demonstration of his carefully honed lyricism.<br><br>Tunes such as "When He Speaks," which previously reached 41 on the Euro Indy Artist radio charts, show Barlow's ability to turn life observations into solid stories. Album sequencing, it seems, is intentional, as each track smoothly links to the next, creating a continuity of humor, sarcasm, and emotional honesty. Listeners who appreciate Barlow's music will recognize his characteristic observational style, but the album also presents new textures and dynamics that support the richness of his songwriting as well as empathy for human emotion.<br><br>By Special Request sits well alongside other fan-favorite or thematically sequential albums that encourage listener involvement, evoking efforts like Taylor Swift's Folklore and Evermore, which marry confessional storytelling with a unifying, cinematic atmosphere. By the same token, the pairing of witty, readable lyrics and musical variety places Barlow in league with artists such as Leon Bridges or Allen Stone, whose music is equal parts soulful rhythm and openness. For anyone looking to hear music that's both intelligent and emotional, Barlow's new album is full of both.<br><br>Outside the studio, Barlow has fostered an active online presence, communicating directly with fans on media platforms such as TikTok and YouTube. His on-line work, usually presented in the guise of behind-the-scenes looks at his songwriting, serves to reinforce the intimacy and immediacy that characterize By Special Request. This artist-fan relationship carries over from the music into the act of listening, encouraging listeners to feel personally responsible for every note and line.<br><br>In the end, By Special Request is more than a favorites album. It's an offer to listen for a dialogue between artist and listener, to locate the humor, openness, and observational acuity that have characterized Bill Barlow's life's work. With its mix of blues, R&amp;B, and hard-telling songcraft, the album is a testament to the emotional strength of music that listens as much as it talks.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Qymira Steps Into The &quot;Labyrinth Of Life&quot; With Earth-Shattering Remix And Prescient Sound</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/qymira-steps-into-the-labyrinth-of-life-with-earth-shattering-remix-and-prescient-sound/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/qymira-steps-into-the-labyrinth-of-life-with-earth-shattering-remix-and-prescient-sound/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:15:58+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/70/volecho-music-magazine-14.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/70/volecho-music-magazine-14.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>There's always been something greater-than-life about Qymira. Born in Hong Kong, raised in San Francisco, educated in Britain, the artist has never regarded music as mere sound—it's world-building. Her songs sit in the crossroads of a movie soundtrack and dance floor, where global beats and classical orchestration mingle with narrative emotion. Now, with her latest release Labyrinth Of Life (Eddie Craig Remix) releasing October 25 on On QiiA Media, Qymira reimagines power, vulnerability, and cinematic scale for the fourth time.<br><br>The song is one of a string of chart-topping hits from the artist, such as Wait For No One, Give It To Me, and Brazilian hit radio favorites Perdão, Sun &amp; Sea, and Vem Comigo. But Labyrinth Of Life is different. It's heavier, darker, and more introspective—less about escaping, more about confronting what's beneath the surface. The track joins Qymira's authoritative vocals with snappy production from Eddie Craig—he's half of UK electronic duo The Wideboys, who've produced for Rihanna, Kylie Minogue, and Girls Aloud. Add in a verse by ItzDvn, whose delivery brings the grit to this song, and you've got something that is simultaneously spiritual and physical, mental and club-danceable.<br><br>Labyrinth Of Life is a thematically deconstructionist song. It's an invitation to wake up—to draw back the curtain on all that is artificial, surface-level, performative. Qymira describes it as "a search for truth and clarity through a labyrinth of distractions." But this is not sanctimonious cogitating; this is an anthem that succeeds. The orchestral arrangement, composed and arranged by Qymira herself with the assistance of the Philippine Philharmonic Orchestra, raises a dance track to something exalted. It's Inception and The Matrix in their heads if they were being sound-tracked for an electronic opera. You can picture this track ending an episode of Euphoria or thumping through a late-night Drive montage—neon glows on wet pavement, all a little dreamlike but very real.<br><br>This drop follows hard on the heels of Melodrama (RainForest Edit), another with Eddie Craig that took her first orchestral single and remixed it as an ecstasy dance edit. It pared the sound back to staccato synths and rhythmic chunk but retained Qymira's magnetic vocals at the forefront. That track was one about illusion and manipulation—dynamics of power that distort relationships. Labyrinth Of Life blows open that world, takes individualized chaos and universalizes it. It's not one relationship now; it's systems we inhabit and the identities we construct within them.<br><br>Qymira's ascent has been anything but conventional. Classically trained on violin, piano, and voice since childhood, she was already leading orchestras as a teenager. Her debut single Satisfied made No. 1 in the UK Music Week Breakers Chart and propelled her onto a UK tour that saw her performing in front of tens of thousands. She has since conducted members of premier orchestras throughout Asia and had her music performed on the world's stages. The music she is making today—this union of classical grandeur, global beat, and electronic bite—sounds like the natural extension of that tradition.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Benjamin Quartz Lights the Fire with &#x27;Pyromane&#x27;</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/benjamin-quartz-lights-the-fire-with-pyromane/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/benjamin-quartz-lights-the-fire-with-pyromane/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:16:06+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/69/volecho-music-magazine-13.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/69/volecho-music-magazine-13.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>Benjamin Quartz is back with his latest single, Pyromane, a song that commands attention from the opening notes with its blend of samba beats, Brazilian percussion, and very rich strings. The song dropped on September 26, 2025, and it marks a positive step in Benjamin's musical growth, with a demonstration of his capacity to balance sophisticated instrumentation with lyrical storytelling.<br><br>From the first few seconds, Pyromane crafts a rich setting, one of heat, urgency, and closeness mingling together. The drums are alive with the feel of a festival, while the strings introduce an almost motion picture elegance, surrounding Benjamin's voice in a manner that is rough and yet otherworldly. It's a sonic tapestry that evokes visions of a gypsy entertainer near a roaring fire, hot and inescapable but cultured and controlled. The skillful weaving of language and rhythm in the song illustrate Benjamin's aptitude both as storyteller and musician, mediating tale and tone. <br><br>Pyromane, musically, probe the constants of humanity, desire, and longing. Benjamin portrays love not as romance itself, but as something natural, unpredictable, devouring, and intensely beautiful. The understated dance of percussion, clapping, and castanets at the end of the song leaves the listener suspended in that place between fantasy and reality, where the music is the vehicle for feeling. The song structure, although based on the traditional samba beats, is completely modern, so it is perfectly suited to fit any level of intimacy listening, as well as larger playlists of world, inflected pop or indie songs.<br><br>Benjamin Quartz' innovation in this case is reminiscent of lush experimentation in the style of Devendra Banhart or Rodrigo Amarante but infused with his own unique French sensibility. There's an eternal quality to his work: you're in a Parisian café at night, in a Brazilian square during sunset, and in a candlelit, intimate setting simultaneously. It's this cross, cultural sensitivity and emotional intelligence that makes Pyromane so fascinating.<br><br>For those who listen to rich-textured, world-infused music, Pyromane sits comfortably alongside new music by cutting-edge world, pop acts such as Ibeyi, Aurora, or even more rhythmically adventurous songs by Carla Morrison. Its film and dance suitability would not only go well with sensual or narrative-heavy films but could equally be likened to the soundtracks of Call Me by Your Name or The Secret Life of Walter Mitty.<br><br>In an oft-too-formula-filled musical landscape, Benjamin Quartz reminds us that passion and grace can be balanced, that poetry and rhythm can collide without sacrificing their finesse. Pyromane is a song; it's a brief, transporting excursion to a world where music writes in a way words cannot. By the time the last castanet fades, you’re left not just with a melody, but with a sense of place, mood, and longing, a testament to Benjamin Quartz’s growing mastery of his craft.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Amara Fe&#x27;s Reborn Is a 24-Track Testament to Legacy, Labor, and Living Loud</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/amara-fes-reborn-is-a-24-track-testament-to-legacy-labor-and-living-loud/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/amara-fes-reborn-is-a-24-track-testament-to-legacy-labor-and-living-loud/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:16:12+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/68/volecho-music-magazine-12.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/68/volecho-music-magazine-12.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>Some records seem to have been produced overnight, a burst of one-off inspiration. Reborn isn't. It's the product of years of acquiring knowledge, listening, and suffering. On twenty-four tracks, Amara Fe digs deep into a reservoir of family myth, musical heritage, and plain determination. It's not an album — it's an assembly of soul, rhythm, and resolve.<br><br>Out on September 9, 2025, Reborn is ambitiously expansive for a debut from an artist not willing to play it small. Most debuts are tentative-sounding six-songs-and-a-hopeful-prayer-for-playlist-ness exercises, but Amara bursts in with an album twice the size, just as varied, and utterly unique. It's the sound of an artist determined not to hold back, and you can hear that dedication in every lyric, every hook, every hit of every beat.<br><br>Raised in Mission, USA, Amara Fe has more than love for music — she has roots. Her roots started long before a studio mic ever recorded her voice. There's her uncle Eugene and Rene, whose day-long-long Tulsa, Oklahoma, jam sessions of yesteryear used to keep her up, and her grandmother, who had written for the great Minnie Riperton. All of them are embedded in Reborn. You hear them in the heat of the chords and the authenticity of her lyrics, as if specters of vintage tunes cooed along with her.<br><br>The heartbeat of the album is its eclecticism. "It's made for every ear," Amara assures, and she is on the money. Reborn glides from genre to genre effortlessly — soul ballads sounding like pre-dawn after heartbreak, pop songs romping together with funk, R&amp;B grooves sprinkled with introspection. It's not often that an artist manages variety work at the expense of cohesion, but Amara weaves it all together in her voice, shifting from smooth restraint to raw intensity with seamless ease. She's whispering in your ear one second, soaring over piled harmonies that sound like gospel translated in today's pop the next.<br><br>There is something movie-like to Reborn. It might take a season of your life — all-night rides, wake-up calls, the silence following big choices. You can envision it alongside albums like Alicia Keys' The Diary of Alicia Keys, H.E.R.'s eponymous release, or even Lana Del Rey's Norman Fing Rockwell!*** in its balance of soul and narrative. All the tracks are inhabited, not written for trends or for hits but born of somewhere true.<br><br>The album title aptly reflects this. Reborn is what it's like when an artist becomes overwhelmed in the moment —recycling scraps of her former self and remaking them over again. That taking back is only half of what makes it so strong. Whatever she sings about self-esteem, love, or believing, there's always some undertow of persistence that keeps everything glued together. You can tell these songs were constructed laboriously, brick by brick on a canvas.<br><br>Amara's voice has the kind of emotional gravity that doesn't require amplifying. She isn't over-singing or relying on studio gimmicks. Her tone is carrying the load — the kind of voice that'll sound best via a good pair of headphones or in a dark room with the volume cranked just past comfortable. Imagine the intimacy of Sade or the subtle strength of Solange, but channeled through Amara's own light.<br><br>What Reborn has that is great is also its restraint. Amidst the culture of music so fixated on singles, Amara's twenty-four-track first album comes close to being inflammatory. It encourages you to let it live with you, allow the songs to unspool. It's an album that believes in albums — a complete thing, not a scroll. And that belief makes it even more rewarding.<br><br>Her production decisions mirror that same faith. The productions strike a balance between new-school texture and old-school soul components — live bass lines, fiery keys, and vocal stacks that reference Motown but feel now. It's something that would reside comfortably on a playlist with Jazmine Sullivan, Anderson .Paak, and Erykah Badu, but one distinguished by Amara's unmistakable world — intimate, sensual, and heavy with nostalgia.<br><br>If Reborn were a film, it would be Selma encountering A Star Is Born: one historically, the other unapologetically in self-exploration. It is that artful blend of respect and disobedience.<br><br>You sense this album was labored slow — not merely to write, but to breathe. It's from a person with enough life to know music isn't flawless, it's conversational. Each song sounds like a letter to somebody, or perhaps to herself. And among the two dozen tracks, you get the impression that Amara Fe isn't in town to make a statement. She's just letting us know what she knows — and there's a lot of that.</p>
<p> </p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Veronica Fusaro Hits Gold With Her Uplifting Single &quot;Gold Rush&quot;</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/veronica-fusaro-hits-gold-with-her-uplifting-single-gold-rush/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/veronica-fusaro-hits-gold-with-her-uplifting-single-gold-rush/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:16:18+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/67/volecho-music-magazine-11.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/67/volecho-music-magazine-11.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>In a speed-driven world, Swiss-Italian artist and composer Veronica Fusaro doesn't leave much of a footprint behind. Her latest single Gold Rush (released September 26) is off to a flying start with infectious energy, rich storytelling, and hooky combinations of indie pop, rock, and cinematic-like sophistication. Recording and produced by Kim Wennerström, the track is the last teaser before Fusaro's long-awaited sophomore album Looking for Connection releases on October 24 — and by all accounts, including Gold Rush, one of the most urgent pop records of the year.<br><br>Gold Rush strikes us immediately upon first listen like a runaway anthem. Its beat pounds hard, the type that makes you go before your head catches on. But under the gloss, it is all about the anxiety — the desiring, the seeking, the contemporary hunger for more. Fusaro digs into the legend of California's Gold Rush in converting a 19th-century tale of greed and aspiration into a commentary on our time. She gazes upon fevered quest for validation, sleepless desire to "win big," and the quiet loneliness that usually follows. "Everybody wants to be successful, rich, have it all — and in a hurry," Fusaro states. "Gold Rush is about that high and the price of wanting more."<br><br>That cost goes deep. It begins with the Italian words "Dai tira il dado dai" ("Roll the dice, come on"), a brazen invitation to take the risk. Then all the machinery is engaged — glinting synths, pounding bassline, and a screaming vocal that builds up until it is almost explosive. When Fusaro sings “Fast life, I’m living the fast life”, she captures both the thrill and unraveling of ambition, a feeling that hits somewhere between euphoria and exhaustion. It’s the same emotional territory that artists like HAIM, Maggie Rogers, and The Killers often explore: the intoxicating side of ambition, and what happens when the high fades.<br><br>The track precedes Jealousy and No Rain No Tears, the highlight tracks which provided an appetizer of the sonic range of Looking for Connection. While those initial releases tipped the nod towards rhythm and love introspection, Gold Rush is the spark — forceful, insistent, and cinematic. It's an open-road-at-night-city-lights song, the sort that makes you recall the mind-blinkingly false promise of success that characterizes so much of contemporary life. You can easily envision it over a shot in Babylon or Euphoria, where burnout and beauty coincide in the same shot.<br><br>Fusaro's voice has always functioned by balancing precariously on that tightrope between light and darkness. Her 2023 release All the Colors of the Sky led No. 5 on the Swiss charts, an ethereal collection of tunes that established her as both delicate and bold. She's gone on to perform more than 500 concerts in Europe, the UK, and elsewhere — including at Glastonbury, Montreux Jazz Festival, and a sold-out headlining performance at Kaufleuten in Zurich. Being on stage with Mark Knopfler at the Amphitheater in Nîmes only demonstrated her capability to stand shoulder-to-shoulder with the legends.<br><br>It's not so much her singing voice — which slides from sultry stillness to full-throated emotion — but the way she crafts sentences. Fusaro's lyrics cut without irony, with unvarnished candor and melody. To that degree, she reminds us of Taylor Swift's 1989-period confessional directness, the movie-studio gloss of Lana Del Rey, and the earthy confessionalism of Clairo. But the actual songs she writes are unique: light but textured, intimate but scratchy.<br><br>Searching for Connection is her most intimate work yet, an album that arose from a paradox — more connected than ever before, but lonelier each day. Through its lyrics, she is looking at ambition (Gold Rush), rivalry (Jealousy), and heartbreak (No Rain No Tears) and the incessant din of contemporary living (Slot Machine). It’s a record about the distance between who we are and who we pretend to be — and the fragile hope that maybe, somewhere in between, real connection still exists.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Vanessa Marie King Finds Forever in Her Debut Album Eterna</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/vanessa-marie-king-finds-forever-in-her-debut-album-eterna/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/vanessa-marie-king-finds-forever-in-her-debut-album-eterna/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:16:25+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/66/volecho-music-magazine-10.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/66/volecho-music-magazine-10.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>There’s a moment, about two minutes into the title track of Eterna, when Vanessa Marie King’s voice cracks ever so slightly, not from strain, but from truth. It’s the kind of moment that stops you mid, thought. You can hear that she’s not just performing the song, she’s living it. That’s the essence of Eterna, a debut record that feels both intimate and cinematic, a confession wrapped in melody.<br><br>Released on September 30, 2025, under her family label KINGBYDESIGN, Eterna isn’t just an introduction, it’s a declaration. Across its ten tracks, King delivers a deeply personal portrait of love, loss, and endurance. Each song feels like a diary entry, written not in ink but in rhythm and resonance.<br><br>Vanessa hails from Mission, United States, but her music feels borderless. There’s a universality to the emotions she captures, and her bilingual songwriting adds an even richer layer to the storytelling. Tracks like Jugaste con fuego (“You played with fire”) and Niña perdida (“Lost girl”) unfold like chapters in a memoir, vivid, vulnerable, and unflinchingly honest. The Spanish lyrics roll off her tongue with warmth and gravity, while her English verses reveal a poet’s sense of space and rhythm.<br><br>In Eterna, Vanessa doesn’t shy away from her scars. She folds them into melodies that ache and glow in equal measure. The album’s production leans into organic textures, acoustic guitars, soft percussion, and layered harmonies that breathe rather than shout. It’s reminiscent of the emotional clarity found in the works of Rosalía’s early Flamenco, inspired recordings or the introspective glow of Billie Eilish’s Happier Than Ever, but Vanessa’s tone is entirely her own. Her voice carries the grit of lived experience, paired with the elegance of someone who’s learned to stand still in the storm.<br><br>“Every song on Eterna comes from a real place,” Vanessa shared in a recent interview. “I wrote about people who changed me, moments that hurt, and lessons that kept finding me. Music helped me turn pain into peace.” That spirit runs through the entire record. Eterna doesn’t try to impress, it connects.<br><br>The album’s title track is its heartbeat. Eterna swells slowly, its melody circling around the idea of love that lingers beyond endings, love that lives in memory, in forgiveness, in letting go. It’s the kind of song that would fit perfectly at the end of a film like Blue Valentine or Before Sunset, a closing montage of quiet revelation.<br><br>Elsewhere, Jugaste con fuego burns brighter. It’s sharp, rhythmic, and unapologetic, a track that channels betrayal into strength, with Vanessa’s voice rising over a simmering groove. Niña perdida, on the other hand, pulls inward. It’s hauntingly simple, just piano, soft reverb, and the weight of introspection. The restraint makes it devastating.<br><br>Fans of Lana Del Rey, Natalia Lafourcade, or Adele’s 21, era ballads will find something familiar in Eterna, that mix of heartbreak and hope, vulnerability and defiance. Yet Vanessa’s storytelling feels distinctly modern. Her lyrics don’t wallow; they evolve. Even in her saddest moments, there’s movement, a sense that healing is already on its way.<br><br>It’s worth noting that Eterna arrives at a time when many debut records are overproduced or algorithm, friendly, designed for attention spans, not hearts. King goes the other way. She gives her songs time to breathe, letting emotion take the lead. The result feels timeless.<br><br>What also stands out is her independence. Releasing under KINGBYDESIGN, a family label, adds a layer of authenticity. You can feel that this wasn’t filtered through marketing departments or committee edits. It’s handcrafted, personal in every sense. That independence mirrors artists like Sabrina Claudio, Laufey, or Hozier, who build worlds that listeners enter willingly because they feel real.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Makanduk&#x27;s &quot;Ruined&quot; Translates Club Sound into Cinematic Fantasy</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/makanduks-ruined-translates-club-sound-into-cinematic-fantasy/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/makanduks-ruined-translates-club-sound-into-cinematic-fantasy/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:16:31+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/65/volecho-music-magazine-9.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/65/volecho-music-magazine-9.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>Makanduk, the Sydney-born self-taught producer, is a standout talent who makes a laptop and bits of gear bigger than the room it sprang from. His new EP, Ruined, released October 10, 2025, is a trim, driving declaration that weaves club sound with sci-fi texture and the desolate feeling of a middle-of-the-night drive along a city that doesn't even exist.<br><br>Makanduk's sound exists in just the right spot between beat and atmosphere. He's plainly borrowed from producers like Chris Lake and Chris Stussy, but where his sound succeeds is in its sense of film. There's groove, there's sweat, but there's story too. The three songs that constitute Ruined—specifically the trance-nation Crazy and low-slung bruiser Reason—sound like scenes in a hitech-colored film, half action and half suspense. You can almost envision the strobe light and fog machines, that sort of fog where time crawls just so the drop strikes all the more forcefully.<br><br>Where the production is sleek and about to drop at the club, there is something beating like nostalgia coursing through it. Makanduk resides in between Sydney and Germany, and that bite of cultural duality creeps in big and small ways. There's the precision and order of Berlin electronic music and the open-road, sun-kissed sound of Sydney. It pops up in transitions, where minimalist cool clashes with warm melody, or how he allows basslines to wander like characters and not rhythms.<br><br>What's admirable about Ruined is how well it works considering that it was born in a home studio. There's no feeling of being restrained here. Rather, the lo-fi equipment lends the EP its edge, a raw intensity that sheen production compromises. Each hi-hat crack is sharp, each build measured. It's the sound of an artist who learned that emotion is greater than gear.<br><br>Tracks like Crazy are set for underground club dance floors but also sustain themselves during a night-walk listened to through the headphones. It's a balancing act difficult to achieve—club music that can also be a solo activity. You hear it on albums like Fred again.'s Actual Life, or in the dramatic tension of Trentemøller's The Last Resort. There's intensity, but there's also considered thought. A physical and affective groove.<br><br>Reason, another jewel, is heavier with a gritty bass line that pretty much demands a bass face. It's a testament to Makanduk being no mere coloring with atmosphere but building tension and release in good faith. There's a hint of that early 2010s vibe—think Deadmau5 or Eric Prydz—refracted through a contemporary lens, cut to the bone and fueled by feel.<br><br>You can tell that Ruined is more than a name—it's a theme. The songs sound like the soundtrack to burning to the ground in progress, to elegance in things deteriorating over time. It's dance music that seeks to capture the ridiculousness of seeing a city burn in the club. Destructive, but cleansing. Like sweating out tears of sorrow in strobing lights.<br><br>It's refreshing to see a producer getting enthusiastic about fantasy in a scene which often fetishizes over templates and trends. Makanduk talks about writing his music as he would write "sci-fi and action movie scenarios," and that's precisely how it sounds. You can put these tracks into something like Blade Runner 2049 or Drive and they'd fit right in. They have that mix of pulse and emotion, the feeling that something’s about to happen.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bright Shining Lights Take Fans On An Orbit With &quot;The Sun Is A Star&quot;</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/bright-shining-lights-take-fans-on-an-orbit-with-the-sun-is-a-star/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/bright-shining-lights-take-fans-on-an-orbit-with-the-sun-is-a-star/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-15T00:16:37+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/64/volecho-music-magazine-8.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/64/volecho-music-magazine-8.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #4</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/tstt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-4/paperback/product-84y724j.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p class="align-left">While playlists reign and albums increasingly are heard these days in snippets, Bright Shining Lights have done the opposite. Their sophomore full-length album, The Sun Is A Star, is not an assembly of songs. It's an aural-image trip of music and narrative, a concept album that is like listening to a movie. Dropped solo on DistroKid this September, the record is an ode to a time when listeners stayed put, let the lights grow low, and let the music take hold.<br><br>Art C. Gusmano and Rob Maru, the two men behind the project, have a background. Both were members of 90s New Jersey group Wellcurbs, a local legend for their misty mix of guitar-scorched despair and melodic sensibility. Having spent years writing in solitude, the duo came together as Bright Shining Lights and dropped their own debut, This Is Where We Start, in 2020 on Deko Entertainment. That drop foreshadowed the widescreen scope that will characterize The Sun Is A Star—but not this time, they left nothing in their back pocket.<br><br>Listening to The Sun Is A Star is like stepping into a world of its own. The album begins with "Go For Launch," a thudding, ambient song that might soundtrack the beginning of a great science fiction epic. The album then unspools across sixteen tracks that chart both a literal and figurative route: discovery, loneliness, community, purpose. It's music constructed from human queries, in starry terms. Gusmano and Maru do not use space as a place of fantasy, but as a reflection of what it is to be alive and looking.<br><br>"Everything started with a single song, actually," Gusmano said of Go For Launch. "It was the foundation for all the rest of it. Space is a good place to start because it's all about the unknown. From there, we wanted to see if we could take all these ideas of isolation, and purpose, and having to belong to something greater than yourself." <br><br>There's a build-creep sense to the sequencing of the album. Early tracks glow with energy and propulsion, and subsequent tracks lean towards introspection and emotional depth. There is a point at which the guitars sound like they might have emanated from Dark Side of the Moon, then another in which they evoke the ghostly sadness of OK Computer. There are echoes of The Cure's retro design and Arcade Fire's sweep and grandeur, but there isn't anything that feels like copying. The group proudly flaunts their influences but uses them as points of departure of orbit rather than anchors.<br><br>The music is lush and cinematic. Synths ascend like solar gusts, drums drop with carved heat, and vocals drift on a plane of confession and incantation. The songs are easy to envision as part of a film's soundtrack, which is no accident. The inspiration of cinema drives how the duo composes music. They're not creating singles for instant listen—they're composing music for the score of a non-existent film. The listener is the protagonist.<br><br>Maru views the scope of the project with the kind of exhaustion that only occurs after decades of building. "These types of projects take time," he said. "You work on version after version until words and sound finally come together and form something that is meaningful. You can't speed it up. You just have to be in it."<br><br>And that is what distinguishes The Sun Is A Star. They are inviting you to slow down. When musicians today struggle to compromise 15 seconds of someone's attention, Gusmano and Maru struggle for an hour and half—and and they're worth every moment of it. The album is like an artifact from the past, when listeners wore out CD booklets and stayed up nights deciphering lyrics.<br><br>Fans of M83’s Hurry Up, We’re Dreaming, The War on Drugs’ Lost in the Dream, or even Interstellar’s score by Hans Zimmer will find plenty to love here. It’s a record that rewards immersion, best played from start to finish with the lights down and maybe a little stargazing out the window.<br><br>There's also a thematic affinity between films such as Solaris or Ad Astra—films which take the chill of space to stretch towards human feeling. As with those films, The Sun Is A Star isn't concerned with flight; it's concerned with looking in. Each synth wave, each reverb-drenched chord, sounds like a hushed conversation between what's out there and what's in here.<br><br>The chemistry of Gusmano and Maru is what holds the album together. They share the history that reflects how the songs breathe. They play like old friends finishing each other's sentences, or movie directors knowing precisely when to hold the camera and when to cut.<br><br>The Sun Is A Star isn't easily slotted into the stream culture of today, but that's exactly the point. It's in the same tradition as Pink Floyd's The Wall or Radiohead's Kid A—albuns that demand work and faith, that reward those who persevere. It's a work of some kind of modest bravery, the sort that doesn't seek permission and pursue a trend.</p>
<p> </p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
