<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>volecho.com</title>
    <link href="https://volecho.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://volecho.com" />
    <updated>2025-11-25T13:15:08+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Volecho.com</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://volecho.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Pointe Step Through the Fog With Guard Rails, A Debut That Waits, Tightens, and Finally Sparks</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/pointe-step-through-the-fog-with-guard-rails-a-debut-that-waits-tightens-and-finally-sparks/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/pointe-step-through-the-fog-with-guard-rails-a-debut-that-waits-tightens-and-finally-sparks/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-25T13:14:03+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/96/volecho-music-magazine.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/96/volecho-music-magazine.jpg" alt="" />
                <p> </p>
<p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #7</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/smkf/">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-7/paperback/product-v8qw95p.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p>Pointe's single Guard Rails arrives with the kind of quiet tension that holds your attention before you've even registered why. The Brisbane group are still only twenty, yet carry themselves with a depth that speaks to long nights in tiny rehearsal rooms and more than a few conversations about the songs that changed their lives. Guard Rails sits in that uneasy space before a major life shift, where dread lingers longer than the leap itself. Rose Fogarty puts that weight into her voice, soft but firm, as though sorting through the fear in real time.<br><br>What the band builds under her feels both angular and tender. Evander Adams Post shapes the pulse with a steady hand, Jude Spann's bass moves with intent, and Jake Park's guitar lines thread themselves in like a series of quiet questions. The track opens up slowly, then pulls tight again, recalling the cold edge of Interpol and the emotional clarity of The Cranberries. Paul Blakey's mastering gives the song clean space, the kind that lets small details hit with extra force.<br><br>Rooms at The Cave Inn have already been filled with Pointe, and the run of local dates would suggest their following will only grow. This debut hints at a full EP that could live comfortably next to early Daughter, the moodier moments of Wolf Alice, or even the dim neon glow of a Gregg Araki soundtrack. Guard Rails feels like the start of a band learning how to turn fear into something melodic, something honest, and something that sticks around long after the final note fades.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Emerging Voices and Bold Sounds Shaping the Year</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/emerging-voices-and-bold-sounds-shaping-the-year/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/emerging-voices-and-bold-sounds-shaping-the-year/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-25T12:11:12+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/95/volecho-music-magazine-33.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/95/volecho-music-magazine-33.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #7</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/smkf/">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-7/paperback/product-v8qw95p.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<h2 class="align-left" data-start="13216" data-end="13264"><strong data-start="13219" data-end="13262">Wotts — Soft Lies in a Psychedelic Glow</strong></h2>
<p class="align-left" data-start="13279" data-end="13700">Ottawa’s indie-pop duo Wotts return with <em data-start="13320" data-end="13346">He Spoke With Conviction</em>, a track that drifts through the speakers like a half-remembered dream. Jayem and Ricky 100 lean into their earlier psychedelic instincts here, letting lo-fi warmth and soft, analog shimmer carry a story that unfolds gently but cuts deeply. The result feels like waking up mid-daydream—colors blurred, details softened, emotions sharper than expected.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="13702" data-end="14256">At its core, the song explores the lies we tell ourselves—the small, comforting untruths that help us make it through stretches where life feels heavier than usual. It’s introspective without being bleak, reflective without sinking. Jayem’s production builds a world of drifting synths, warm guitars, and textures that sound dusted in sunlight. Meanwhile, Ricky 100 keeps the track grounded with a bassline that refuses to overcrowd the mood. Together, they create a sense of hazy forward motion, like navigating a familiar street through shifting fog.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="14258" data-end="14602">Fans of early Tame Impala, Pond, Homeshake, or Mild High Club will immediately recognize the psychedelic contouring: the VHS-tinted synths, the softened edges, the dreamy pacing that feels almost weightless. It’s the kind of track that would sit easily in the more reflective scenes of <em data-start="14544" data-end="14554">Euphoria</em>, where the world tilts but never fully slips.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="14604" data-end="15021"><em data-start="14604" data-end="14630">He Spoke With Conviction</em> serves as a gateway to Wotts’ upcoming EP <em data-start="14673" data-end="14679">COPE</em>, which follows their emotionally heavier previous effort, <em data-start="14738" data-end="14746">FLANK!</em> If that record dealt with what breaks you, <em data-start="14790" data-end="14796">COPE</em> lingers in the space after the dust settles—when you try to move forward but aren’t sure your feet are steady yet. Wotts don’t offer fixes; they offer reflection, and it’s that honesty that makes this new chapter resonate.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="15023" data-end="15340">The single releases November 21, with a video arriving a week later, and if the EP carries this balance of warmth and unease, Wotts may land one of their most affecting projects yet. This is music for late-night thinkers, quiet mornings, and anyone learning the difference between letting go and simply continuing on.</p>
<h2 class="align-left" data-start="15347" data-end="15423"><strong data-start="15350" data-end="15421">Luka &amp; the Nightbirds — Last Resort and the Weight of Starting Over</strong></h2>
<p class="align-left" data-start="15438" data-end="16004">From Metz comes Luka &amp; the Nightbirds, a project built from a lifetime of musical immersion and a recent shift toward rawer, more human storytelling. Luka grew up listening to Chopin, Debussy, Duke Ellington, and The Beatles—absorbing classical clarity and jazz looseness before falling fully in love with <em data-start="15744" data-end="15756">Abbey Road</em> at six years old. His early solo career with Mercury and Universal brought chart success with tracks like “Rêves polyesters” and “Je ne pars pas sans toi,” but his newest phase with the Nightbirds feels more lived-in, more vulnerable, more real.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="16006" data-end="16569">Their lead single <em data-start="16024" data-end="16033">Vertigo</em>, from the forthcoming album <em data-start="16062" data-end="16075">Last Resort</em>, is a gentle emotional exhale. It’s a song about loss—acknowledged but not indulged—carried by Luka’s grounded, unforced vocal delivery and a band that understands the power of letting a moment breathe. Recorded live at Angie Studio in rural Cantal, <em data-start="16326" data-end="16335">Vertigo</em> holds the warmth and small imperfections of real rooms, real breaths, real people. That openness recalls the stark honesty of Bruce Springsteen’s <em data-start="16482" data-end="16492">Nebraska</em> or the quiet emotional cracks that make Big Thief’s recordings feel alive.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="16571" data-end="17016">There’s a cinematic quality to the track too, though not one painted in widescreen drama. Instead, it evokes those late-night scenes in films like <em data-start="16718" data-end="16739">Lost in Translation</em>, where the world softens and meaning slips in sideways. Luka writes like someone who has weathered storms and no longer tries to polish the rough edges away. The Nightbirds follow suit, shaping an atmosphere that holds emotional weight without squeezing it into neat shapes.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="17018" data-end="17453">Fans of The National, Ben Howard, or the softer corners of Wilco will recognize the blend of melancholy and gentle propulsion. <em data-start="17145" data-end="17158">Last Resort</em> arrives November 14, 2025, and if <em data-start="17193" data-end="17202">Vertigo</em> is a clue, the album will carry the bruises of a hard year while still letting small sparks shine through. This is music built from experience rather than performance—a reminder that beginning again rarely looks clean but can sound profoundly honest.</p>
<h2 class="align-left" data-start="17460" data-end="17524"><strong data-start="17463" data-end="17522">Mad Morning — The Circle and the Sound of Breaking Free</strong></h2>
<p class="align-left" data-start="17539" data-end="17992">Essex trio Mad Morning are done easing into anything. After the explosive impact of their debut <em data-start="17635" data-end="17647">Painkiller</em>, they return with <em data-start="17666" data-end="17678">The Circle</em>, a track that kicks its way into the room with sharp edges, louder instincts, and a restless energy that feels ripped straight from modern life’s accelerating churn. Their blend of post-grunge abrasion and indie hard-rock bite evokes the punch of early Alice in Chains meeting the tight ferocity of Royal Blood.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="17994" data-end="18542">The song digs into the cycles that trap us—financial grind, control, pressure, the endless race to keep pace while losing what matters. Rob Jarvis delivers lines like “take the money, I’ll keep my pride” with the dry grin of someone calling out the rat race while running through it. Kevin Hein’s drumming hits like a steel beam dropped from height, and the guitars slice with a jagged precision reminiscent of Velvet Revolver or the darker corners of Soundgarden. It’s a track built for Friday nights, sweat, and rooms that vibrate at the edges.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="18544" data-end="19129">What makes Mad Morning’s momentum so striking is how quickly their live presence caught fire. Before releasing a single piece of recorded music, they were already selling out venues like The Black Heart in Camden and The Waiting Room in Stoke Newington, with fans shouting lyrics that didn’t technically exist yet. Jarvis, seasoned from his years in the U.S., sings with the urgency of someone on his third or fourth reinvention. Hein, with his German metal-scene roots, plays with force and surgical consistency. Together, they compress stadium-scale energy into a three-piece roar.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="19131" data-end="19433">If <em data-start="19134" data-end="19146">Painkiller</em> was the spark, <em data-start="19162" data-end="19174">The Circle</em> is the ignition. Fans of Foo Fighters, Royal Blood, or the heavier edge of Queens of the Stone Age will latch on instantly. The track feels built for needle-drop moments in gritty films—the neon rush of <em data-start="19378" data-end="19385">Drive</em> or the explosive tension of <em data-start="19414" data-end="19430">Peaky Blinders</em>.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="19435" data-end="19644">With <em data-start="19440" data-end="19452">The Circle</em> out October 31 via Saviour Music, Mad Morning establish themselves as one of the UK’s most dangerous new rock prospects. Loud, sharp, and unwilling to compromise—they’re just getting started.</p>
<article class="text-token-text-primary w-full focus:outline-none [--shadow-height:45px] has-data-writing-block:pointer-events-none has-data-writing-block:-mt-(--shadow-height) has-data-writing-block:pt-(--shadow-height) [&amp;:has([data-writing-block])&gt;*]:pointer-events-auto [content-visibility:auto] supports-[content-visibility:auto]:[contain-intrinsic-size:auto_100lvh] scroll-mt-[calc(var(--header-height)+min(200px,max(70px,20svh)))]" dir="auto" tabindex="-1" data-turn-id="request-68e0f597-2f90-832f-88b4-28c59798b36f-16" data-testid="conversation-turn-64" data-scroll-anchor="true" data-turn="assistant">
<div class="text-base my-auto mx-auto pb-10 [--thread-content-margin:--spacing(4)] thread-sm:[--thread-content-margin:--spacing(6)] thread-lg:[--thread-content-margin:--spacing(16)] px-(--thread-content-margin)">
<div class="[--thread-content-max-width:40rem] thread-lg:[--thread-content-max-width:48rem] mx-auto max-w-(--thread-content-max-width) flex-1 group/turn-messages focus-visible:outline-hidden relative flex w-full min-w-0 flex-col agent-turn" tabindex="-1">
<div class="flex max-w-full flex-col grow">
<div class="min-h-8 text-message relative flex w-full flex-col items-end gap-2 text-start break-words whitespace-normal [.text-message+&amp;]:mt-1" dir="auto" data-message-author-role="assistant" data-message-id="494fc3bd-28d1-4d62-8081-a2415d274b3e" data-message-model-slug="gpt-5-1">
<div class="flex w-full flex-col gap-1 empty:hidden first:pt-[1px]">
<div class="markdown prose dark:prose-invert w-full break-words dark markdown-new-styling">
<h2 data-start="19651" data-end="19707"><strong data-start="19654" data-end="19705">Allegra — Red and the Birth of an Adult-Pop Era</strong></h2>
<p data-start="19708" data-end="19720">London’s Allegra steps into a new chapter with <em data-start="19769" data-end="19774">Red</em>, a track that signals a clear shift from youthful dance-pop toward a deeper, darker, more self-possessed sound. Fresh off a #1 on the <em data-start="19909" data-end="19921">Music Week</em> Commercial Pop Chart with <em data-start="19948" data-end="19958">Wildfire</em>, she arrives here with unmistakable confidence—no longer leaning on momentum, but defining her path. <em data-start="20060" data-end="20065">Red</em>, the first glimpse of her upcoming second EP, moves on a deep, slow-burning bassline, airy synths, and vocals that hover between a whisper and a challenge. It’s intimate, late-night, and tinged with emotional weight beneath the sheen.</p>
<p data-start="20304" data-end="20702">The visualiser doubles down on that new identity. Allegra alternates between stark white and pulsing red, her performance measured and magnetic. The choreography is crisp enough for TikTok loops, yet the overall atmosphere feels more like the smoldering minimalism of a Dua Lipa cut or the mood-drenched glow of early <em data-start="20622" data-end="20632">Euphoria</em> sequences. It’s a reinvention—one shaped carefully but confidently.</p>
<p data-start="20704" data-end="21221">The full EP outlines the arc of someone stepping into adulthood in real time. <em data-start="20782" data-end="20787">Ash</em> lingers in a reflective haze, <em data-start="20818" data-end="20830">Slow Dance</em> blends warmth with club-friendly clarity, <em data-start="20873" data-end="20884">Waterfall</em> drifts breezily, and <em data-start="20906" data-end="20924">Love Me A Little</em> stands as the emotional centerpiece: tender, stripped-back, honest. Alongside them, <em data-start="21009" data-end="21019">Upgraded</em> balances sadness with lift, while <em data-start="21054" data-end="21062">Refund</em> channels the bite of a breakup anthem meant to be shouted with friends. Together, the tracklist forms a narrative of transition—messy, thrilling, and human.</p>
<p data-start="21223" data-end="21656">Allegra’s rise has been steady but substantial. Collaborations with Tiësto, Alok, Tobtok, Full Intention, Majestic, and R3HAB have pushed her into international territory, while millions of streams and support from major UK media have built a solid foundation. Magazines from <em data-start="21499" data-end="21513">Rollacoaster</em> to <em data-start="21517" data-end="21529">Wonderland</em> have spotlighted her trajectory, and her singles consistently climb global charts from the UAE to the Billboard Dance Chart.</p>
<p data-start="21658" data-end="21948">Now, <em data-start="21663" data-end="21668">Red</em> marks the moment her sound matures into something more textured. Fans of Tate McRae, Rita Ora, Mabel, Olivia Rodrigo, and Gracie Abrams will find easy entry. But this era feels distinctly Allegra—cooler, richer, and poised for the shift from rising talent to undeniable presence.</p>
<h2 data-start="21955" data-end="22016"><strong data-start="21958" data-end="22014">Janet Devlin — Not My First Emotional Rodeo (Deluxe)</strong></h2>
<p data-start="22031" data-end="22457">Janet Devlin has always written like someone handing over pages torn straight from her journal, but the deluxe edition of <em data-start="22153" data-end="22183">Not My First Emotional Rodeo</em> opens that door even further. The original album already topped the iTunes Country Chart, yet this expanded version reveals new corners and tensions, stretching her sound from twang-edged swagger to quiet, cinematic introspection. It’s not a reinvention—it’s a deepening.</p>
<p data-start="22459" data-end="23054">From the fiery punch of <em data-start="22483" data-end="22490">Candy</em> to the wounded honesty of <em data-start="22517" data-end="22543">If He Wanted To He Would</em>, Devlin navigates emotional extremes with steady control. <em data-start="22602" data-end="22618">Plastic Pistol</em> sharpens the mood with a darker undercurrent, while <em data-start="22671" data-end="22682">Psycho Ex</em> carries a smirk that conceals its sting. But it’s her stripped-down take on <em data-start="22759" data-end="22772">The Gambler</em> that anchors the deluxe. Recorded live with little more than a guitar, she sings with the weight of someone who understands how silence can hold a story. The performance carries the kind of late-night stillness found in <em data-start="22993" data-end="23009">A Star Is Born</em> or the roadside tenderness of <em data-start="23040" data-end="23051">Nomadland</em>.</p>
<p data-start="23056" data-end="23514">Part of Devlin’s appeal has always been her ability to blend vulnerability with grit. Fans of Kacey Musgraves, Orville Peck, or Noah Kahan will feel immediately at home here, yet Devlin maintains a tonal identity distinct from all three: sharper than Musgraves, more melodic than Peck, and less confessional-pop than Kahan. She writes like someone who has been collecting emotional weather patterns for years and finally decided to map them with precision.</p>
<p data-start="23516" data-end="23849">The deluxe edition isn’t just an expansion—it’s a recalibration of the album’s heartbeat. If <em data-start="23609" data-end="23626">Emotional Rodeo</em> was the forward sprint through heartbreak, confusion, and defiance, this new version is the reflective walk afterward, when adrenaline fades and clarity settles in. It feels more lived-in, more human, and more unguarded.</p>
<p data-start="23851" data-end="24094">For listeners seeking modern country that doesn’t lean into clichés or over-polish, <em data-start="23935" data-end="23974">Not My First Emotional Rodeo (Deluxe)</em> is a full-evening experience—one best consumed in low light, with plenty of room to feel whatever rises to the surface.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="z-0 flex min-h-[46px] justify-start"> </div>
</div>
</div>
</article>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>New Artists Redefining 2025</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/new-artists-redefining-2025/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/new-artists-redefining-2025/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-25T13:15:08+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/94/volecho-music-magazine-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/94/volecho-music-magazine-1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #7</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/smkf/">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-7/paperback/product-v8qw95p.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p> </p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="text-align: left; font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Jasmith Finds the Bright Side on Festive Night</strong></p>
<p class="align-left"><br><br>Festive Night lands with that kind of spark that makes you forget how heavy the world can feel. Singapore's Jasmith keeps things simple on the surface, but there is a quiet intention behind the song's bright pulse. Built on clean production and a hook which nudges you into a good mood before you even notice, the track works the way a scene in a feel-good film does: like that moment in Crazy Rich Asians when the lights warm up, and everything turns soft for a second. It is pop built for actual human joy, not the forced kind.<br><br>He takes care of literally every part of the project himself, and for that, the song has a warm clarity, with an early Lauv or Conan Gray's sweet side to it. The beat has that gentle lift, the vocals sit well in the pocket, and nothing is trying too hard. It's that kind of song where you could slide next to Troye Sivan's lighter singles or any playlist built around nights that go a little later than planned. There's also a hint of that K-pop glow-something you'd hear tucked into the soundtrack of a drama right before the two lead characters pretend they're not falling for each other.<br><br>What makes Festive Night work is how honest it feels about its own job: it wants to give you a few minutes of relief, and it succeeds without leaning on big statements. Jasmith seems aware that cheerful songs can hit just as deep as sad ones when they come from the right place. If this is the first step in a longer path, it's a promising one. The song feels ready for any playlist that needs a lift, and that alone is a solid start for someone carving out their own lane with patience and care.<br><br><strong>Anke Richards — Quiet Fire in Another Realm</strong><br><br>Anke Richards has long occupied that subtle space between whisper and atmosphere, but Another Realm feels like the moment her sound crystallizes into something unmistakably her own. Built in collaboration with Grammy-nominated writer Dante Lattanzi, the single stretches a soft, nocturnal glow across its entire runtime. Richards sings as though the room is dark and you're the only one awake with her-every breath is purposeful, every pause carries its own weight. Her voice hovers just above glassy synths that widen slowly, like light settling across still water at midnight.<br><br>Her rise has been quiet but sure-more than 17 million streams without the flashier trappings of a viral breakout-and this track shows exactly why she's found an audience. She holds the same shadowy spark that fans of Billie Eilish or Tate McRae gravitate towards, except she occupies a gentler emotional register, closer to AURORA's soft luminescence or Daughter's early hushed confessions. Cinematic touches slip into the production almost without notice, giving the track the widescreen stillness of a late-night sci-fi sequence or the eerie calm of a series like Dark.<br><br>It further deepens Another Realm for its connection to Artists for Sea Shepherd-a partnership that makes streams and shares real support for marine conservation, a purpose folded discreetly into the song's atmosphere rather than stamped across it. Richards achieves something rare here: a sound both grounded and weightless, personal and expansive, the kind of track built for late-night drives, headphone nights, and quiet apartments where thoughts are allowed to settle slowly. If this is the energy Richards is carrying into 2025, it marks the beginning of a powerful stretch. Another Realm doesn't shout; it settles, it glows, and it lingers. In a year already crowded with maximalist pop, her ability to pull listeners inward might be the exact calm listeners return to again and again.<br><br><strong>Hellkern Warriors — The Pulse of the Void </strong></p>
<p>Hellkern Warriors arrived in 2025 not so much with a launch as with a rupture-a darkwave signal slicing through static from three continents at once. Formed around early sketches from Tom Radar, the group expanded quickly into a full-scale electronic-gothic hybrid when Kabal, Mauricio, and Fabian added their own weight and atmosphere. What began as a handful of shadowy demos-Hellkern Warriors, Petrol &amp; Water, Endless Road-grew into a conceptual world they now call The Pulse of the Void, a sonic space defined by analog synth grit, cold guitar lines, and a heartbeat that moves like machinery learning to feel. Their name references a computer worm, fitting for a band that moves quietly through the dark but cuts unmistakable tracks in their wake. Their debut video, released September 2025, set the tone with stark, minimal visuals and a sound that feels equally suited for late-night playlists, underground basements, or the neon-tinged melancholy of films like The Crow or Underworld. The follow-up single, Petrol &amp; Water, pushed deeper into their signature cold glow.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="3442" data-end="3968">Each member arrives with a history that shapes the project’s depth. Tom Radar’s previous work in RADARFIELD built an international following with its careful balance of emotion and electronic precision. Kabal—also known as Dylan Phoenix—has decades behind him across metal, goth, and EBM scenes, giving Hellkern its poetic tension and sharpened edges. Meanwhile, Colombian musicians Fabian and Mauricio bring a heavy discipline from their metal roots, grounding the project’s electronic pulse with a sense of physical force.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="3970" data-end="4373">The result is a sound that lands somewhere between the chill of Boy Harsher, the brooding minimalism of She Past Away, and the slow-burn tension found in retro-leaning shows like <em data-start="4149" data-end="4166">Stranger Things</em>. It’s early days for Hellkern Warriors, but they already carry the clarity of a band that knows its terrain. These tracks hit like headlights on an empty highway—steady, ghostly, and impossible to ignore.</p>
<p class="align-left" data-start="4375" data-end="4519">If <em data-start="4378" data-end="4401">The Pulse of the Void</em> is only the beginning, then Hellkern Warriors are carving out a realm listeners will want to inhabit for a long time.</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-left" data-start="4526" data-end="4580"><strong>Chris Oledude — Turning Tables, Turning Heads</strong><br><br>Chris Oledude has long been a sharp, steady voice for when conversations get complicated, but Turning Tables feels like a moment where message and groove meet in perfect balance. The third single from his debut album Preacher Man Vol. 1, the track hits with a confident, unhurried funk that moves with the bounce of early Curtis Mayfield while carrying the warmth of New York street-corner soul. Featuring a vibrant duet with Lindsey Wilson, the song plays like two friends trading truths at a block party—fiery, playful, and urgent.<br><br>What really makes Turning Tables hit even harder, though, is the path it traveled to get here. Sparked originally by writer Dr. Lora Ellen McKinney, the track moved through Oledude's live shows, rewrites, and long, careful studio sessions across Woodstock and lower Manhattan before settling into its final form. You can hear that lived-in quality throughout: backing vocals filled by friends and longtime collaborators, instrumentation that feels played rather than arranged, and a rhythm section that carries the easy authority of musicians who have spent decades honing their craft.<br><br>The roots of Oledude run deep. Raised in a home where protest songs lived beside folk and pop, he developed early on an instinct for music that speaks plainly while still moving with joy. His 1984 cassette Anyone's Revolution already hinted at the voice he would eventually grow into, and his years of civic engagement only sharpened the urgency and compassion layered into his new work. Now, returning fully to art after loss and reflection, he sounds clearer and more grounded than ever.<br><br>Turning Tables also serves as an entrance into the greater universe of Preacher Man Vol. 1, an album that represents forty years of writing, yet feels strikingly present. It fits seamlessly beside Brittany Howard's "Stay High," The Roots' "You Got Me," or the soulful narrative style that carries through Spike Lee's Do the Right Thing.<br><br>Oledude isn't chasing trends; he's building a lane rooted in rhythm, truth, and community. On Turning Tables, that lane feels wide open.<br><br><strong>Agent of Kaos (AOK) — Voltage Rising</strong><br><br>Agent of Kaos, better known across the EDM circuit as AOK, has reached 2025 with a fire he's no longer interested in containing. A familiar name within the Musosoup community, he has always made solid, high-energy tracks, but he's also the first to say they were warm-ups. Now, he's pivoting into a months-long blitz of releases aimed squarely at the dance floor: heavier, sharper, more chaotic, and more precise. Coming out of Denver-a city where bass culture runs through venues like an underground current-AOK is stepping into this new phase with unmistakable purpose.<br><br>His foundations lie in bass-driven production, but he refuses to stay caged by genre. Instead, he treats bass as a launchpad, pushing into festival-scale drops, left-turn structures, and atmospheric builds that echo industry giants like RL Grime, Kayzo, and early Skrillex without ever falling into mimicry. There's a rawness embedded in his sound-a willingness to distort, break, and rebuild patterns-that places him in the rising crowd alongside Rezz, Subtronics, and ISOxo.<br><br>Beyond his own output, AOK leads Church Of Us Records, a label built to amplify new producers navigating an industry that often buries fresh voices under algorithms and noise. His commitment to creating community over clout hints at the long game he's playing: not just momentary impact, but sustained movement.<br><br>AOK's new run leans into the cinematic too, music that mirrors the neon fever of Blade Runner 2049 or the pulsing energy of the Arcane soundtrack. He builds tension with the confidence of someone who knows exactly when the floor will fall out and precisely how the crowd will respond. If you're preparing for what's next, cue him up beside Rezz's darker cuts or ISOxo's explosive drops. This new era is built for late nights, sweat-soaked rooms, and that communal electricity that hits the moment the beat snaps into place. Whatever AOK delivers next, one thing is clear: it's going to be loud.</p>
<article class="text-token-text-primary w-full focus:outline-none [--shadow-height:45px] has-data-writing-block:pointer-events-none has-data-writing-block:-mt-(--shadow-height) has-data-writing-block:pt-(--shadow-height) [&amp;:has([data-writing-block])&gt;*]:pointer-events-auto [content-visibility:auto] supports-[content-visibility:auto]:[contain-intrinsic-size:auto_100lvh] scroll-mt-[calc(var(--header-height)+min(200px,max(70px,20svh)))]" dir="auto" tabindex="-1" data-turn-id="request-68e0f597-2f90-832f-88b4-28c59798b36f-6" data-testid="conversation-turn-44" data-scroll-anchor="false" data-turn="assistant">
<div class="text-base my-auto mx-auto [--thread-content-margin:--spacing(4)] thread-sm:[--thread-content-margin:--spacing(6)] thread-lg:[--thread-content-margin:--spacing(16)] px-(--thread-content-margin)">
<div class="[--thread-content-max-width:40rem] thread-lg:[--thread-content-max-width:48rem] mx-auto max-w-(--thread-content-max-width) flex-1 group/turn-messages focus-visible:outline-hidden relative flex w-full min-w-0 flex-col agent-turn" tabindex="-1">
<div class="z-0 flex min-h-[46px] justify-start"> </div>
</div>
</div>
</article>
<article class="text-token-text-primary w-full focus:outline-none [--shadow-height:45px] has-data-writing-block:pointer-events-none has-data-writing-block:-mt-(--shadow-height) has-data-writing-block:pt-(--shadow-height) [&amp;:has([data-writing-block])&gt;*]:pointer-events-auto scroll-mt-(--header-height)" dir="auto" tabindex="-1" data-turn-id="655b5599-1137-482c-9ea1-d9312a7032af" data-testid="conversation-turn-45" data-scroll-anchor="false" data-turn="user"><hr><strong>Simonne Draper — Strings in Motion, Light in the Quiet</strong><br><br>Simonne Draper moves with a composer's precision and an explorer's restlessness, fashioning a sonic world in which classical guitar meets modern atmosphere but never loses its emotional center. Based between Prague and Kent, Draper forged her artistry through discipline and reinvention-starting in law before throwing herself full-time into composition under Milan Tesar. Early acclaim arrived with Portraits in Guitar, a record that captured both radio and print across Europe, consolidating her as a guitarist capable of striking clarity. But Draper would never stay there. Her next project, Silence of Eclipse, pushed deeper into mood and narrative: a mix of the intimacy of acoustic lines with discreet modern touches redolent of the quiet tension of Gustavo Santaolalla or the spacious, emotional landscapes of Ryuichi Sakamoto. To listen to Draper is to watch light shift across a room-slow, precise, deeply evocative. Her music could sit inside a Denis Villeneuve film or in the shadowy emotional framework of a series like Dark, where sound becomes an invisible storyteller. Draper's recent collaborations show just how fluidly she moves between worlds. Working with GRAMMY-winner Alexx Antaeus and producer Jon Kennedy, she brings her guitar into clean electronic and downtempo spaces to create a blend that feels organic rather than forced. It's the same balance that artists such as Nils Frahm or Bonobo achieve-acoustic warmth acting as the anchor that holds electronic layers steady. Her award-winning pieces, Espanola and Canzonetta dell’Acqua, are markers of creative clarity rather than arrival. Draper writes with intent but never with a straitjacket; she lets silence, breath, and restraint become part of the composition. Whether crafting meditative solo work or stepping into projects with an electronic lean, she maintains an unmistakable voice: grounded, emotional, and quietly luminous. Those for whom solace has been found in Max Richter's Sleep, Sakamoto's async, or the softer outlines of Tycho will feel instantly at home in Draper's catalog. Her music isn't built for quick thrills-it rewards slow listening, attentive moments, and rooms where quiet feels like its own instrument. Draper stands firmly in the middle of a new movement: artists who understand that calm carries power.<br><br>Pointe — Guard Rails and the Art of Tension Brisbane's rising alt-indie outfit Pointe arrive with Guard Rails, a debut single that already carries the grip of a band well beyond their years. Formed in high school and now stepping into a wider spotlight, the quartet-Rose Fogarty, Evander Adams Post, Jude Spann, and Jake Park-craft a sound built on soft tension, emotional clarity, and the kind of raw intuition that young bands rarely capture this early. Guard Rails centers on a moment suspended between dread and change-the uneasy stretch before life shifts direction. Fogarty's voice pulls that feeling forward with a mix of fragility and insistence. She doesn't belt; she bears weight quietly, the way Dolores O'Riordan once could, or the way Interpol's Paul Banks let cold, steady cadence carry whole scenes. The band wraps her in atmospheric restraint: patient drums, a close-mic'd piano, bass that moves with intention, and guitar lines that slip in like unanswered questions. Listeners might hear echoes of Daughter's early work or the moodier corners of Wolf Alice, but Pointe carve their own shape in the quiet. Paul Blakey's mastering adds a spacious minimalism that lets tiny details land with force-a breath, a tremble, a shift in tone. Despite their youth, Pointe have already packed out rooms at The Cave Inn, a testament to the immediacy of their live presence. Their shows carry that same balance of vulnerability and precision, a push-pull of softness and pressure. It's not flashy; it's intimate. And intimacy tends to travel far. If you're building a playlist around Guard Rails, pair it with The National's Trouble Will Find Me, Wet Leg's gentler cuts, or the drifting neon melancholy of a Gregg Araki soundtrack. Pointe occupy that hazy territory where fear turns into motion and where hesitation becomes the spark for something new. As their debut EP approaches, Guard Rails stands as both a beginning and a promise. Pointe are learning how to turn tension into melody-and they're doing it with startling control.<br>
<article class="text-token-text-primary w-full focus:outline-none [--shadow-height:45px] has-data-writing-block:pointer-events-none has-data-writing-block:-mt-(--shadow-height) has-data-writing-block:pt-(--shadow-height) [&amp;:has([data-writing-block])&gt;*]:pointer-events-auto [content-visibility:auto] supports-[content-visibility:auto]:[contain-intrinsic-size:auto_100lvh] scroll-mt-[calc(var(--header-height)+min(200px,max(70px,20svh)))]" dir="auto" tabindex="-1" data-turn-id="request-68e0f597-2f90-832f-88b4-28c59798b36f-16" data-testid="conversation-turn-64" data-scroll-anchor="true" data-turn="assistant">
<div class="text-base my-auto mx-auto pb-10 [--thread-content-margin:--spacing(4)] thread-sm:[--thread-content-margin:--spacing(6)] thread-lg:[--thread-content-margin:--spacing(16)] px-(--thread-content-margin)">
<div class="[--thread-content-max-width:40rem] thread-lg:[--thread-content-max-width:48rem] mx-auto max-w-(--thread-content-max-width) flex-1 group/turn-messages focus-visible:outline-hidden relative flex w-full min-w-0 flex-col agent-turn" tabindex="-1">
<div class="z-0 flex min-h-[46px] justify-start">
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
</div>
<div class="mt-3 w-full empty:hidden">
<div class="text-center"> </div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</article>
<div class="pointer-events-none h-px w-px align-left" aria-hidden="true" data-edge="true"> </div>
</article>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Definitely Maybe Unveil Beginning to End, a Fearless Six-Track Dive Into Heartbreak, Recovery, and Rebirth</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/definitely-maybe-unveil-beginning-to-end-a-fearless-six-track-dive-into-heartbreak-recovery-and-rebirth/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/definitely-maybe-unveil-beginning-to-end-a-fearless-six-track-dive-into-heartbreak-recovery-and-rebirth/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-25T12:11:29+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/93/volecho-music-magazine-31.jpg" alt="" />
                    Chicago’s rising alt-rock duo Definitely Maybe return with Beginning to End, a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/93/volecho-music-magazine-31.jpg" alt="" />
                <p data-start="116" data-end="548">Chicago’s rising alt-rock duo Definitely Maybe return with <em data-start="175" data-end="193">Beginning to End</em>, a striking six-song EP that traces the emotional arc of losing love and slowly learning to live again. Produced by hitmaker Kevin McCombs (Sueco, Papa Roach, Story of the Year), the project blends alt-rock grit, emo-pop vulnerability, and a sharp pop-punk bite — a fusion that turns each track into its own cinematic chapter of heartbreak and healing.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="116" data-end="548"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/7oO9fBEnIUGRWdMkUwKArb?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p data-start="550" data-end="961">On <em data-start="553" data-end="571">Beginning to End</em>, the band leans fully into honesty. Each song captures a different facet of emotional fallout: the initial sting, the spiraling questions, the moments of denial, and finally, the fragile but powerful return to hope. Towering choruses, explosive guitars, and raw, expressive vocals form the backbone of the EP, weaving a narrative that feels both deeply personal and universally familiar.</p>
<p data-start="963" data-end="1171">“<em data-start="964" data-end="1103">Beginning to End is about processing everything — the pain, the denial, the acceptance — and finding some kind of hope at the other side,</em>” the duo explains. “<em data-start="1124" data-end="1168">It’s the most honest thing we’ve made yet.</em>”</p>
<p data-start="1173" data-end="1486" data-is-last-node="" data-is-only-node="">With its blend of visceral storytelling and modern, arena-ready production, <em data-start="1249" data-end="1267">Beginning to End</em> positions Definitely Maybe as one of 2026’s essential new rock-pop acts. The EP lands November 14, 2025 via DMG Recordings, marking a defining moment for a band stepping boldly into their sound — and into their future.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Songs Built From Scrapes and Sparks: Five Artists Rewriting Their Own Stories</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/songs-built-from-scrapes-and-sparks-five-artists-rewriting-their-own-stories/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/songs-built-from-scrapes-and-sparks-five-artists-rewriting-their-own-stories/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-25T12:25:50+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/92/volecho-music-magazine-30.jpg" alt="" />
                    he following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/92/volecho-music-magazine-30.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">he following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #7</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/smkf/">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-7/paperback/product-v8qw95p.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong></address>
<p class="align-center" data-start="339" data-end="381"><strong>Podge Lane Finds His Voice On The Road</strong><br><br>Podge Lane has always written like someone who listens with both ears open. His new album, Less Of Me, feels like the direct result of a year spent letting life talk back. When he left Ireland for the US in March, the plan was simple enough: travel, play shows, write what comes. What he did not expect was the rhythm that took over. More than one hundred gigs in seven months-from tiny rooms to New York staples like Pete's Candy Store and the Bitter End-shaped the songs in real time. Less Of Me sounds like a notebook that kept filling as crowds pushed him toward sharper lines and looser instincts.<br><br>Lane's alt-country touch has always tended toward the intimate, but here his voice comes through clearer. You can hear echoes of early Jason Isbell, the soft sting of Gillian Welch, even hints of Noah Gundersen's early acoustic grit. It tracks his route from the American South to New York without forcing any grand arc. Instead, the tone falls somewhere between quiet humor and bare honesty, two things he's always carried well.<br><br>This is an album that lands like a natural step for listeners who fell for the raw edge of Outer Monologues or the restless spirit of Common Country Misconceptions. It retains his fondness for concept records but trades in tighter framing for something looser and more lived-in. You'll find a familiar pulse here if you're a fan of Boygenius, Buck Meek, or Big Thief's acoustic tracks' sad fun.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="339" data-end="381"><br><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/23HMN3bFOMVYo5Is4C7sxi?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div><br><br><br><br>Lane spent 2024 wrapping a run of shows he jokingly called Sad But Tourable, which suits him. He writes the kind of songs that hit harder when he is laughing at himself, like the scene in an A24 film where the main character admits the truth they have been dodging for an hour. Less Of Me leans into that tone without losing the tender weight of his lyrics. His third LP, Multiple Dead Ends, hinted at a shift. This one confirms it. Podge Lane is still working in country, folk, and the sort of indie that feels built for late-night car speakers, but he sounds freer than ever. Less Of Me is not loud and is not flashy. It's just a record made by someone who paid attention long enough to notice what actually matters. And sometimes that is all a good album needs.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="1425" data-end="1801"> </p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center" data-start="173" data-end="235"><strong>A.D.A.M. Music Project Turns Alien Panic Into Rock Theater</strong><br><br>A.D.A.M. Music Project has never made music for the background, and their new single They Are Here plays like that moment in a sci-fi film when the sky cracks open and no one's ready. The track pulls from classic alien-heavy games like Halo and Half Life, but the point isn't nostalgia. This is rock built for impact, driven by Lacy Saunders and her sharp, soaring voice that cuts into the mix with the kind of lift usually heard in heavy metal epics. The guitars shred without slipping into excess, and the synths widen the track until it feels like a chase scene with no clean exit.<br><br>Fans of bands like Starset, Puscifer, or the heavier side of Muse are in their element. There is this tension running through the song reminiscent of the cold dread of films like Arrival or the frantic energy in Doom Eternal's soundtrack. It hits fast and stays urgent, yet still leaves space for a few theatrical edges to keep the song's world intact.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="173" data-end="235"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/19NbQWCfWWDi4gNidk4ooe?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center" data-start="173" data-end="235"><br><br>AMP's built a catalog that speaks to listeners wanting intensity without noise for the sake of noise. Members hailing from different corners of rock and pop give each track a messy charm, the good kind. It sounds like a team pushing the volume up until something shakes loose. It is the closest thing rock has right now to gaming lore turned into sound, and it works because the band leans into the absurd fun of the concept without losing the weight behind it.</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center" data-start="1673" data-end="1712"><strong>Korda Korder Finds Clarity In Grief</strong><br><br>Goodbye My Friend is that kind of song that, at least for a moment, slows down everything. Korda Korder took the spark from a Sam Fender interview in which he talked about losing someone close and made a track that sounds like a confession passed between friends at 2 am. There is not a big statement in the writing. Instead, his vocals float atop dream pop textures, aglow at the edges, à la Cocteau Twins or early Cigarettes After Sex, where the voice almost folds itself into the synth haze.<br><br>The band has already earned the trust of people like Steve Lamacq and John Kennedy, and it makes sense. Their songs hit with a softness that lingers, the way a Phoebe Bridgers ballad lingers long after the last chord. Goodbye My Friend builds on the pull of What Have You Done and You Still Turn Me Inside Out, but it has a calmer weight to it, as if they let silence work as part of the arrangement.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="1673" data-end="1712"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/1SP4UeWJaEOaCJgFi08lyz?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div><br><br>Korda Korder formed only a short time ago, and yet their tone feels lived in. They write with the grounded ease of acts like London Grammar or Still Corners, artists who know that slow can be powerful, provided one handles it with care. This track would fit next to films like Aftersun or The Florida Project, quiet stories about love and loss told without rushing the emotion. For a band still defining their place, they already sound like they understand exactly what frequency they want to hold.</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center" data-start="3095" data-end="3131"><strong>TRALALAS Turns Shadows Into Song</strong><br><br>Morten Alsinger's new project TRALALAS arrives with a calm certainty that can only come from someone who lived a full life before stepping back into the room. Ornament, his debut under the name, pulls from decades of sound: You can hear bits of Danish electro-punk roots, slow-burning pop, and the kind of deep tone heard in Leonard Cohen's later work. The album feels patient, shaped by someone who trusts small choices. It sits in the space between dark pop and stripped-back indie, balanced by Heidi Lindahl's voice, which moves through the songs with a steady warmth.<br><br>There is a reflective feeling to the writing. Alsinger had been away from the music world for years, returning through new tools and new company, giving these nine tracks the feel of rebuilding his creative voice with intent and without hurry. Those who love Nick Cave's quieter releases or the dreamlike pull of early Beach House records will find common ground here. Ornament leans into echo and tone, slow tension aplenty, more film noir than bright pop release.<br><br><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/6pJyrbbgWrZGIIM7NFk2bP?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div><br><br><br>The project grew with the help of producer Thomas Li and a small circle of players, which keeps everything tight but never stiff. Winter on the Vine, the first single, sets the tone with a calm undercurrent that would fit neatly beside the closing credits of a moody indie film. Ornament feels like a reminder that music can be heavy without being loud, and that age can add focus rather than limit it.</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center" data-start="4590" data-end="4639"><strong>Grim Logick and iLLLogick Build A World Out Of Scar Tissue</strong><br><br>Cipher Chronicles: The Network Archives is the kind of record you feel before you understand it. Grim Logick and iLLLogick turn their own history into a 10-track blast of Dark Orchestral Trap that pulls from pain, survival, and the sharp grind of years spent outside the industry’s clean paths. Recorded in Baton Rouge and shaped in a space they built piece by piece, the album carries the raw tone of early Tech N9ne mixed with the cinematic pull of Run The Jewels at their most focused. Every track seems to push back against a world that tried to shut them out.<br><br>A digital narrator and the sense these artists are writing their past and future in tandem are what bring the concept together. Fans of the grit of City Morgue, cold weight of Clipping., or the punch of Denzel Curry's slower tracks will lock in quickly. The production, reaching back for strings, choir hits, and drums that sound like they were recorded in a room too small for their volume, compounds the feeling of pressure.</p>
<p class="align-center" data-start="4590" data-end="4639"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/1JrvTvesMYmlbSx1X1ildu?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div><br><br>But what makes the project land is the honesty: this is music built from illness, family strain, and the grind of starting with nothing, yet it avoids pity and finds a strange energy in the fight itself. The album plays like a graphic novel soundtrack, one that you'd hear under the scene from Into the Spider-Verse or some high-intensity moment in a Dark Souls cutscene. Grim Logick raps with a tone that feels less like performance and more like he's giving you the truth without softening the edges.<br><br>Cipher Chronicles is loud, tense, and human. You can tell it was made by people with something real to protect. That's what gives it weight.</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Follow Our Playlist For More Music!</strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/playlist/7nCQfSSikvEPorn78ARusH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top Releases 11/17/25</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/top-releases-111725/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/top-releases-111725/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-17T00:28:38+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/91/Top-Tracks-2xl.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1zcQIwpaxhHlEStbKeE36d?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/3lWo4zdHXg2G3cVPXypghf?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/3LX0KsjaK8Qtkc2eMHZUKd?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1Tis3dJsOeKNGDcdf0E9CH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1Gdda2svzKz43K21QwDxWu?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top Releases 10/10/2025</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/top-releases-10102025/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/top-releases-10102025/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-10T23:36:49+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/90/volecho-music-magazine-29.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/90/volecho-music-magazine-29.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #6</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://online.pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/lojb/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-6/paperback/product-w4qrn7p.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong><hr></address>
<p class="align-center"><strong>The Raven's Ghost: Sailing Through the Haunted Waters</strong><br><br>The Raven's Ghost sound like they've been raised on stormlight and distortion. Their music is dripping with the atmosphere of a midnight sea: heavy guitars, spectral melodies, and a rhythm section that moves like waves hitting the hull. On first listen, it's pure rock-and-metal grit. But the longer you stay, the more it comes across as something cinematic: a ghost story told through the amplifiers.<br><br>There's a pirate streak running through their songs, not in costume but in the restless defiance of people who live by their own tide. The themes of resilience and redemption are all the more impactful because of this. Tracks twist between shadow and revelation, the haunted and the human. Their shows have that rare balance of precision and abandon, like old Iron Maiden colliding with the storytelling punch of Alkaline Trio or Ghost.<br><br>Listening to The Raven's Ghost is like boarding a ship crewed by the outcast and the brave: theatre and thunder, wrapped in the kind of rock that remembers why it mattered in the first place. You hear shades of early Metallica, flashes of Danzig, even a touch of Nick Cave's dark romance. Haunted waters, yes-but these ghosts know how to wail.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/0QSYDsgEALIBUkTEr3JpGc?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><br><br><strong>Great Adamz &amp; Maddox Jones: The Sound of Two Worlds Meeting</strong><br><br>Body and Soul is what happens when rhythm meets reflection. Great Adamz and Maddox Jones bridge Afrobeats and soul-pop so naturally, it feels like a conversation that was always meant to happen. Adamz brings the sunlight: the pulse of Lagos, the swagger of his Delta State roots. Jones brings the heart: the ache of the English skies and late-night writing sessions. Together, they create something radiant.<br><br>The track unfolds with warmth, its melody carrying both dance and devotion. There's an ease to it, as if both singers understand that connection is stronger than genre. The production gleams but never feels polished for its own sake. Smooth-phrased Adamz finds a foil in the emotional grit of Jones, evoking classic duets like Paul Simon and Ladysmith Black Mambazo or even George Michael and Aretha Franklin.<br><br>This is a point both artists arrive at via rich paths. Adamz has just come off major festival stages and award wins, continuing to push Afrobeat onward; turning global success into something local and alive. A songwriter steeped in indie pop, Jones continues his streak of heartfelt releases that stare life right in the eye. Body and Soul feels built for more than playlists-it's a song for summer nights that turn into memories.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/4RLWCDWYJxU88nMjZc0Ev8?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><br><br><strong>AC Scott: Writing Through the Fire</strong><br><br>Some voices arrive with a story you can't fake. AC Scott's 15 Minutes of Fame sounds like someone telling the truth with nothing left to lose. It's a slow-building piano ballad that starts in reflection and rises to something cinematic — not in scale, but in sincerity. The song looks at fame's temporary glitter with the weary clarity of someone who's seen both sides of the glass.<br><br>Scott's background reads like a novel: broadcaster, novelist, survivor. After years in front of cameras and microphones, a serious lung condition forced her to step away from the career that defined her. Instead of silence, she found melody. The result is music that feels both fragile and fierce.<br><br>15 Minutes of Fame follows her debut Sometimes, a track that drew comparisons to Judie Tzuke and Julia Fordham, with hints of Kate Bush's emotional reach. The new single digs deeper. You can almost imagine it underscoring the last scene of a lost Richard Curtis film - the credits roll on a bittersweet triumph. Scott writes like someone who's made peace with impermanence, finding power in the act of creation itself. Every note feels earned. This isn't reinvention; it's resurrection.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/3sGVqsv06o5f9L4yyxMMz1?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>The Bare Minimum: Holding It Together in a Broken City</strong><br><br>Doomed City doesn't pretend to save anyone. It just screams the truth loud enough that you might remember why punk still matters. The Bare Minimum tear through four tracks of burnout, fines, and late-night chaos — all the mundane pressures that make modern city life feel like a trap, flipped into cathartic noise.<br><br>Somewhere between early Against Me! and Dead Kennedys, their sound retains a certain Canadian grit that makes them more grounded. The guitars snarl without overplaying, while the drums are all urgency and no polish. It's how joy leaks through frustration that amazes: community, even in collapse, is so worth hollering about.<br><br>The Bare Minimum live what they sing. Between DIY documentaries, local playlists, and work with non-profits, they keep their scene alive by sheer force of participation. That's rare. You can hear that very same spirit in the EP - part exhaustion, part revival.<br><br>If Doomed City were a movie, it'd sit next to Trainspotting and Suburbia, soundtracked by chaos and heart. It's not tidy, but it's real. Punk, as it turns out, is still the most honest way to say you care.</p>
<p class="align-center"><br><br><strong><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/4vT6leutcmMaquuOxBQ4md?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div></strong></p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Trueclaw: Machines with Heart</strong><br><br>Trueclaw's music sounds like solitude turned into signal. The Swedish artist's songs balance human emotion with the shimmer of digital creation-a lone voice working alongside code to build something strangely intimate. It's electronic, but not cold. Similarly, The Ones Remembered and One Road pulse with feeling, each track tracing a quiet arc from reflection to release.<br><br>Working completely solo, Trueclaw writes, records, and produces with the obsessiveness of a person who shapes every sound into exactly what it needs to be to reflect the emotion behind it. The use of AI tools such as Suno and ChatGPT isn't some sort of gimmick here-it's collaboration in the truest sense. The machines act like mirrors, amplifying human depth instead of replacing it.<br><br>There's a calm intensity to the work, calling back to Bon Iver's digital isolation, Burial's shadowed beats, and the cinematic quiet of Cliff Martinez's Drive soundtrack. Yet Trueclaw's voice remains distinct: personal, unguarded, and weirdly comforting. These songs feel like letters to the future in a world of noise. You don't just hear the technology, but you hear the soul behind it, tracing what it means to be both maker and machine.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/7mwgu2FnmzVPFTuGzsQtLR?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><strong>KAYTIE: When Friendship Sounds Like Heartbreak</strong><br><br>Some songs arrive when you've had enough. KAYTIE's Evil Person isn't about romance, but it carries the same ache-the kind that comes when someone you love becomes a stranger. Written in the fallout of a broken friendship, the song channels that quiet fury that follows disappointment. What begins in D minor shifts to E minor, a small but striking move that mirrors the mounting tension in her story.<br><br>KAYTIE is a singer-songwriter from Cincinnati, age 20, who has been writing songs since she was twelve — more than 350 of them, she estimates. But Evil Person feels like a turning point, the one where craft and confession finally lock in step. She's part of a growing wave of young artists who take everyday heartbreak and hone it into sharp, relatable pop, a la early Olivia Rodrigo or Gracie Abrams, with a pianist's sense of intimacy.<br><br>What makes her writing stand out is restraint — a willingness to sit with discomfort instead of dressing it up. She's not chasing chart perfection; she's chasing connection. It's easy to imagine Evil Person soundtracking a key scene in some coming-of-age film: that moment when the friendship ends but the growth begins.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/6TyXblA7968QBU9yCCZmYc?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div><br><br><strong>TRÄLALALÄ: Morten Alsinger's Quiet Return to the Storm</strong><br><br>Morten Alsinger has lived several musical lives. In the 80's and 90's, his sound echoed through Denmark's electro-punk and underground electronic circles. Then came silence - years spent raising a family, working behind the scenes, watching from the wings. Now with his new project TRALALAS and the debut album Ornament, Alsinger steps back into the light with something patient, deliberate, and quietly cinematic.<br><br>TRALALAS bridges digital and analog, electronic pulse meeting fragile melody. The ghosts of Leonard Cohen's baritone reflections, the texture of Joy Division's industrial melancholy, and the spatial melancholy of Beach Boys balladry can all be heard. But dark pop doesn't wallow; it reflects. Each song feels like an artifact - imperfect, lived-in, full of grace.<br><br>When he rediscovered his love for music through the electronica duo VERTICAL, it was through collaboration with singer-songwriter Heidi Lindahl that Alsinger found a new source of creative energy. The project's debut single, Winter on the Vine, shimmers with the cool glow of Scandinavian twilight, equal parts romance and reckoning.<br><br>Ornament isn't just a return; it's a statement from someone who has seen enough to realize the noise fades, but the tone endures. Fans of Nick Cave, Scott Walker, or early Depeche Mode will be offered a world in which they will want to linger courtesy of TRALALAS.<br><br></p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/6pJyrbbgWrZGIIM7NFk2bP?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Jaan: Soundtracks for the Edges of the Map</strong><br><br>There's mystery in Jaan's music: not the marketing kind, but the old-school, analog kind. Their hallucinatory and unclassifiable debut album feels like it could have been unearthed from some forgotten archive: dusty reel tapes, faded labels, stories half-erased. The sound drifts between jazz chaos, ambient haze, and grainy field recordings-a lattice of noise that never sits still.<br><br>Jaan isn't a band so much as a presence-a self-described veteran sonic alchemist who works across Greenland, the Middle East, and Europe. The anonymity isn't a gimmick; it's part of the art. Their sound recalls Brian Eno's Discreet Music, Jon Hassell's "fourth world" soundscapes, and the shadowy tones of Cat People. It's cinematic but not polished, exploratory but not indulgent-a kind of organized drift where emotion and geography blur. In an era of over-explanation, Jaan's refusal to self-define feels refreshing. Listening to the album's tracks is like walking into a dream in which you really have no idea what century it is. You can imagine these tracks running under a Tarkovsky film or some late-night documentary about forgotten cities. It's experimental music that feels human: strange, quiet, full of hidden warmth.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://bandcamp.com/EmbeddedPlayer/album=2304804590/size=large/bgcol=ffffff/linkcol=0687f5/tracklist=false/artwork=small/transparent=true/" seamless=""><a href="https://jaanmusic.bandcamp.com/album/baghali">Baghali by Jaan</a></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top Releases 11/9/2025</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/top-releases-1192025/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/top-releases-1192025/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-09T21:51:38+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/88/Top-Tracks-2xl.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/3lWo4zdHXg2G3cVPXypghf?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Kmxi_XHflAM" title="Hot Chocolate and Apple Cider" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/3LX0KsjaK8Qtkc2eMHZUKd?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1Tis3dJsOeKNGDcdf0E9CH?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/1Gdda2svzKz43K21QwDxWu?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top Releases 11/7/2025</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/top-releases-1172025/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/top-releases-1172025/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-10T23:36:56+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/89/Top-Tracks-2xl.jpg" alt="" />
                    The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/89/Top-Tracks-2xl.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="align-center">The following feature is now included in our online magazine which is also available in print.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong style="font-family: var(--editor-font-family); font-size: inherit;">Issue #6</strong></p>
<address class="align-center"><address class="align-center"><strong><a href="https://online.pubhtml5.com/jgwlo/lojb/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Online Magazine</a> | <a href="https://www.lulu.com/shop/oddstone-printed-media-group/volecho-issue-6/paperback/product-w4qrn7p.html?page=1&amp;pageSize=4" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Print Magazine</a></strong></address><strong><br>For more details contact us at: <a href="mailto:volechomag@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">volechomag@gmail.com</a></strong><hr></address>
<p class="align-center"><strong>John Fishell &amp; Deepak Ram: When Rock Finds Its Reflection in Raga</strong><br><br>Some collaborations sound like theory. Others sound like fate. Notorious Partners in Crime is the rare record where both sides—John Fishell’s rough-edged rock sensibility and Deepak Ram’s luminous bansuri mastery—come together like two sides of a record worn in different decades. Fishell, a lifelong rocker with deep jazz roots, and Ram, a disciple of Pandit Hariprasad Chaurasia, might seem an unlikely pair. But on this project, they have together created something that hums with cultural tension and shared joy.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/6boYyFrIg0yMkAtGC8UUCc?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div><br><br>This set dances like a living, breathing conversation between London, Mumbai, and Memphis. Space Time spools out from 2/4 to 12/8 like it's stretching its own dimensions, while Valentine sways like a lost jazz ballad on a smoky night. Their reimagined Rain Song catches Led Zeppelin's mysticism and turns it inside out—Ram's flute tracing John Paul Jones' ghostly Mellotron textures, while Fishell's baritone guitar carries a slow ache.<br><br>Fishell's past life as a college professor and Grammy-nominated engineer sneaks in through the album's meticulous craft, but the heart is pure chemistry. You can hear the friendship, the laughter between takes. Think of it as George Harrison meeting Ry Cooder by way of Ravi Shankar, with a dose of Zeppelin's spiritual grit. Notorious Partners in Crime doesn't so much blend styles as blur the idea of borders altogether, leaving in its wake something honest and strangely familiar-a world record in the truest sense.<br><br><strong>Stevie Hawkins: Full Circle with a Song for You</strong><br><br>There's a certain gravity when an artist returns to a song that shaped his own story. Stevie Hawkins' recording of Leon Russell's A Song for You carries that weight-and the grace to bear it. He isn't just covering a classic. He's revisiting an old friend. Hawkins once sat behind the kit for Russell in the 1970s and again in the mid-'80s, long before he became a Grammy-recognized vocalist and Blues Hall of Fame inductee. Now, decades later, his version feels like a confession whispered to time itself.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/1Sh4GJzkr09HGeP6u9nYuQ?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div><br><br>The production wraps his voice in lush strings and warm jazz phrasing, mastered by Howie Weinberg, with Rusty Holloway anchoring the bassline. Every note feels lived-in, heavy with memory but lifted by gratitude. There's no flash, just soul—the kind that only comes from someone who's been through the full arc of stage lights and shadows.<br><br>In spirit, Hawkins' take sits next to Donny Hathaway's version, but leans toward the cinematic restraint of Ray Charles. It's a reminder that true blues isn't about sadness-it's about endurance. The track bridges eras, connecting the humid sound of Muscle Shoals to the velvet tone of modern Americana. A Song for You has been sung a thousand ways, but Hawkins' rendition stands apart because he's not just singing to Leon Russell. He's singing with him, one last time.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Calling All Astronauts: Noise Against Tyranny</strong><br><br>Calling All Astronauts sound like a protest set to a strobe light. On their latest album, Noise Against Tyranny, this London-based duo makes industrial beats clash with punk snarl. It's frustration wrapped in rhythm until it hits like catharsis. The new single Time to Party might trick you with its title, being less about escape and more about revolt.<br><br>David B's commanding vocals and programming crash against Paul McCrudden's live instrumentation to create something that sits between Nine Inch Nails and The Prodigy. It's sweaty, loud, and curiously uplifting, with lyrics pushing back against both conformity and self-doubt. There's an undercurrent of hope beneath the chaos, like the pulse of a crowd refusing to give up. Since their inception in 2011, the band has consistently blurred the lines between punk, goth, and electronic, drawing fire from the very same political furnace that once fueled the likes of The Clash and Public Enemy. Live, the performances feel like underground sermons, defiant and unfiltered. Noise Against Tyranny captures that urgency in full. For anyone who still believes that music can confront power, this is essential listening. It's not polite, but it's pure. In a time when rebellion often gets repackaged as nostalgia, Calling All Astronauts remind us it still belongs in the present tense.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/0xqglBsPF9COYj64LNl85t?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Sean MacLeod: The Philosopher of Pop</strong><br><br>Sean MacLeod writes like he was raised on vinyl and big thoughts. His new single Beautiful Star glows with the melodic warmth of classic pop, yet beneath the surface lies a quiet search for meaning. The song is built around piano and rich vocal layers, nodding to 70s prog and the meticulous craftsmanship of early Beach Boys or McCartney's Wings years.<br><br>MacLeod, formerly of the Dublin band Cisco, brings a seasoned songwriter's discipline to his solo work, weaving together complex harmonies that still feel effortless. Lyrically, Beautiful Star poses spiritual and philosophical questions but keeps them bound by melody, never letting the message overtake the music. It's the kind of song that lingers, a tune you hum before you realize what it is asking of you.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/0PYoQyfkI47SQecvr8Z4Gz?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div><br><br>His forthcoming album New Start promises more of this thoughtful pop, but a separate, experimental project titled We Don’t See That We Don’t See hints at his restless curiosity. MacLeod often sits between Todd Rundgren and Nick Drake, matching reflection with irresistible hooks. Against the streaming backdrop of half-choruses, Beautiful Star feels refreshingly whole: a reminder that pop can still reach for the heart and the brain in a single breath.</p>
<p class="align-center"><strong>Amelina: A New Year, A New Anthem</strong><br><br>Amelina's A New Year's Wish is not your background playlist for party confetti. It's a pop-rock spark with heart, a track that captures the rush of starting over and the ache that comes with it. The guitars shimmer, the vocals soar, and the chorus hits like a toast to each and every version of you that has made it so far.<br><br>Raised in Russia and now based in Spain, Amelina writes from the perspective of someone who's rebuilt their life in real time. There's a blend of early 2000s pop grit-think Avril Lavigne's Under My Skin era-with the cinematic lift of Kelly Clarkson's biggest choruses. It's nostalgic but alive, holding its own against the new wave of fearless pop voices like Olivia Rodrigo and Sabrina Carpenter. A New Year's Wish finds its place among earlier singles like Step by Step and Roblox Realms, compiling a discography that can only be likened to a coming-of-age soundtrack. Every song sounds like a scene: neon light, open road, defiant grin. Amelina isn't writing for algorithms; she's writing for the brave parts of people trying again. The year might change, but her message stays: resilience can sound electric when you sing it loud enough.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/2KB8CcoEbyUA0hP58619Iu?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>AMELINA: Lighting Up the Sky with “A New Year’s Wish”</title>
        <author>
            <name>Volecho.com</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://volecho.com/amelina-lighting-up-the-sky-with-a-new-years-wish/"/>
        <id>https://volecho.com/amelina-lighting-up-the-sky-with-a-new-years-wish/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-09T13:20:04+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/87/volecho-music-magazine-28.jpg" alt="" />
                    If pop music had a season, it would be this one: the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://volecho.com/media/posts/87/volecho-music-magazine-28.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>If pop music had a season, it would be this one: the in-between stretch when the year exhales and something new begins to take shape. Into that moment steps Amelina, the Russian-born, Spain-based pop-rock newcomer whose new single “A New Year’s Wish” captures the quiet courage of starting over. Out October 30, 2025, the track is a radiant mix of bright guitars, crisp percussion, and vocals that rise like fireworks over the horizon. It’s both cinematic and deeply human, a song about shaking off fear and finding magic in uncertainty.</p>
<p class="align-center"><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.ibb.co/R40cshjn/IMG-4612.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="IMG-4612" border="0"></p>
<p>At first listen, "A New Year's Wish" sounds like it's reaching for the stars, but its power lies in the details: the shimmer of a chord, the lift of a melody that feels like hope in motion. There's a touch of early Avril Lavigne's sparkle in the guitars, a trace of Kelly Clarkson's anthem-sized delivery, and the storytelling clarity of Olivia Rodrigo or Sabrina Carpenter. But Amelina's voice carries something all her own: a kind of bright defiance that comes not from confidence but from survival. The song builds slowly from what's almost a whisper to a chorus that feels like it's been waiting all year to arrive. "It's like fireworks," Amelina says. "It starts quiet, then bursts into color and reminds you how alive you are." That image fits her music perfectly: emotion and adrenaline intertwined, a flare sent into the dark sky just to remind you that light always returns.</p>
<p class="align-center"><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="352" style="max-width: 100%; border-radius: 12px;" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/artist/2KB8CcoEbyUA0hP58619Iu?utm_source=generator" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" allow="autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture" loading="lazy"></iframe></div>
<p><br>Amelina's story is threaded through that same mix of fragility and strength. When she moved from Russia to Spain in 2023, she left behind a familiar language, a music scene she knew, and the sense of safety that comes with routine. What she found instead was a new kind of creative urgency. Alone in a new city, she began writing songs that mirrored her life — not grand statements, but little affirmations, notes to self set to melody. You can hear that growth between her early tracks such as "Step by Step" and "Roblox Realms," blending indie pop with flashes of rock and cinematic sheen.<br>On "A New Year's Wish," she sounds like an artist who has finally found her rhythm. The production sparkles but never feels polished to emptiness; there's breath and texture in every measure. You can sense her background as both dreamer and realist, someone who knows life doesn't turn around with one song but still believes in trying. The chorus, with its call to "let the light back in," could sit comfortably beside Taylor Swift's 1989 era or the more pop-leaning work of Paramore, yet it lands with a sincerity that keeps it grounded.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.ibb.co/wFw3BLNW/NY-Wish-1.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="NY-Wish-1" border="0"></p>
<p>Refreshingly, Amelina doesn't treat vulnerability as weakness. In an age of algorithmic confidence and curated perfection, she leans into feeling too much. Her lyrics don't posture; they process. Every song feels like a voice note sent to the future self that might need to hear it. There's something courageous in that simplicity: a belief that truth doesn't need to shout.<br><br>Listening to "A New Year's Wish" is like watching a film about your own life, one where the ending isn't tied in a bow but full of possibility. It's easy to imagine it soundtracking some coming-of-age montage or the closing scene of some teen drama-maybe something halfway between Heartstopper and The Edge of Seventeen. There's a sincerity here that modern pop sometimes forgets, a kind of emotional directness that recalls early 2000s optimism but updated for now.<br><br>Even the holiday undertone feels smartly handled: rather than leaning into tinsel and sleigh bells, Amelina uses the idea of New Year as metaphor-a clean slate, a promise that even after heartbreak or chaos, something luminous can grow again. It's not a holiday song in the traditional sense; it's a human one. What's striking about her recent trajectory is how fast she's learning to balance craft and feeling. There's the clear mark of someone who studies pop structure but trusts instinct more than formula. Each track she's released builds its own small world, linked not by sound but by spirit. Together, they map out a story of growth-from the cautious energy of "Step by Step" to the full-hearted drive of "A New Year's Wish." Her sound has become a kind of cinematic diary: snapshots in motion, always glowing with color and rhythm.<br><br></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
